Okabe? What are you doing this early?
Hiyajo...
I have to ask you something.
What?
Have you given up talking funny now?
Due to our D-RINE, Amadeus was lost, but...
...we still meet Hiyajo,
but apparently for different reasons.
Even as worldlines change...
"Yesterday"
...that fate which links us,
those connections...
Do they change to bring us together as well?
Mayuri?
Hello?
Suzu is... Suzu's in trouble!
Suzuha is?
Yeah! She's heading to the time machine
to go one year in the past...
She's leaving, but she can't come back!
Why did you...?
Huh?
Why did you have to go talk about it?
There's no time.
I can't even find out and
confirm what exactly has changed.
Today is double sevens day!
The only thing that matters is
that they leave in the time machine.
Orihime-sama will greet you in a miniskirt!
Kagari?!
Why is she so early?!
Okabe?
Kagari's still after the time machine.
I've gotta find her... and stop her!
Lintahlo.
What are you doing in a place like this?
I suspect...
You know more about the time machine
than I gave you credit for?
Where's Kagari?!
Eh?
After she escaped the facility...
...I know she met up with you and your crew.
How much of the truth do all of you know?
I see...
It's different since the
D-RINE took away Amadeus...
Could this Professor Leskinen not
have completely brainwashed Kagari?
That's...
Professor Leskinen.
I know things about
the future you can't even imagine.
You wish to know about it?
I'll tell you everything.
Moeka!
Huh?
Okabe!
I'm fine.
You need a doctor!
There's no time for that!
I need you to help me!
Lab Member 005...
...Kiryu Moeka!
Ouch...
D-Don't do this!
Kaga--
Kagari...
I won't let the past be changed.
I won't let me meeting
with Mommy be undone.
Nobody's getting the time machine.
Suzu... that's Kagari?
Why?!
Mommy Mayuri...
Is Mommy trying to change the future too?
Just like Big Sis Suzuha wants to.
Does Mommy want to make it
so the two of us never meet?
Kagari...
I don't want that!
However terrible the future is, I don't care!
It's the only future
that means something to me!
What's wrong, Kagari? Can't shoot?
You little...!
Kagari.
Please, let's stop.
It's dangerous! Stay back, Mommy! I have to!
B-Big Sis Mayu...
M-Mommy?!
That was scary! I was holding my breath!
But, I'm glad that you didn't shoot, Kagari.
Mommy!
Listen...
Kagari...
You see, I'm going together with Suzu...
...aboard the time machine into the past.
To open the eyes of someone special to me.
You can't...
It doesn't matter how hard
Mommy and Big Sis Suzuha try!
Nothing good will come of it! It won't work!
There's only enough fuel to go one way!
You can't come back!
You don't even know... what will happen...
Kagari...
It might be reckless... It might be hopeless...
But, Okarin is different.
Okarin has the power to change the future.
No, I think everyone has it inside them.
But Okarin uses that power
to guide us all the right way.
Which is why I want to give him
the push on the back that he needs.
If it's just that, I should be able to do it.
It's the only thing Mayushii
can do for my Hikoboshi.
Hikoboshi...?
That day, if my Hikoboshi
had come back to life...
Mommy's... Hikoboshi?
Kagari.
You should come with us.
Eh?
With us into the past... to change the future.
The future doesn't have to be sad,
nor does anyone have to die.
Instead, we'll all make a future
where everyone can be happy together!
Let's go.
Kagari... together.
Mommy...
Do it for me too!
Okarin?
Moeka?
Uncle Okarin!
Listen... I've come here from the future.
Using the time leap machine.
This place is about to become a war zone.
You have to hurry and
leave in the time machine!
That can't be...
The professor doesn't know about...
He's knocked unconscious right now,
but it's only a matter of time!
Okarin...
Lab Member 002, Shiina Mayuri!
Make Operation Arc-light a success!
When I'm all pathetic...
...slap some sense into me!
Okay! Leave it to me!
Kagari, come!
Mommy...
Moeka!
I can't hold them long! Hurry!
Kagari, let's go!
Mommy...
Tsk!
Okarin.
Okarin... You're fine
with never seeing Mommy again?
You won't be sad?
What are you talking about?
Mayuri's my precious hostage.
I'll go to wherever she is and bring her back!
Kagari!?
Kagari
Go! I won't let them anywhere near you!
Kagari!
Hurry!
Big Sis Mayu!
Kagari!
Mommy's Hikoboshi!
I'm trusting you... Because you
said I could meet Mommy again!
Leave it to me!
It came after all...
Okabe!
Mommy!
I see it...
This time...
There's nothing to fear!
This is it!
This instant!
"Radio Kaikan"
"Akihabara"
"1 new RINE message"
Listen well, you fools!
Schrödinger's box has opened!
The time machine you bastards
sought to obtain no longer exists!
It has gone through space-time
and has completely disappeared!
Writhe with anguish and tremble in fear!
I, Hououin Kyouma...
...against you fools
and even fate, I will prevail!
No matter what... I will find Steins Gate!
That...
...is my...
...choice!
Arc-light of the Point at Infinity
- Arc-light of the Sky -
Eh? Huh?!
Th-There's two time machines?!
Uh, it's from me!
"Incoming Call"
"Mayuri"
Eh?
Wh...
What the heck?
I guess... I'll answer it.
Hello?
Who's this?
Please, listen to what I have to say.
Do you love Hououin Kyouma?
Eh?!
In one minute from now,
Okarin will return but...
...he will have failed in saving Makise.
So...
No matter what it takes...
You have to confront
your Hikoboshi and open up his eyes.
My Hikoboshi?
Yes.
Hououin... Kyouma.
Okarin's heart will be shattered,
but you've gotta him back on his feet.
Just saying his name won't be enough.
Thirty seconds left!
Remember the exact moment
Hououin Kyouma was born!
The moment Hououin Kyouma was born...
Feelings spanning 26 years
and one more are entrusted to you.
I believe...
...in Okarin, my friends, and in myself.
So please believe too.
The rest is up to you.
Tutturu!
Wait!
Um...
Big Sis Mayu! We have to go!
Does Steins Gate...?
Does Steins Gate really exist?!
Yeah.
I'm sure it does.
The second one's gone too...
Who was that call even from?
"Incoming Calls"
"Mayuri"
"Lukako"
"Daru"
I'm sorry, Big Sis Mayu.
It's looking hopeless.
Yeah, there's no fuel, right?
If we stayed it'd cause a paradox,
so we had to jump...
This might be it for us.
We could get thrown into some random era.
One year later... A million later...
Suzu, thank you.
Big Sis Mayu?
For bringing me along with you today.
I'm sure the other Mayushii and
my Hikoboshi can take care of the rest.
I'm so jealous of Uncle Okarin right now.
If I had Reading Steiner...
...I could remember everything,
even when worldlines change.
Big Sis Mayu being younger than me...
This moment right now...
I won't get to talk with
Suzu for another six whole years.
Oh, except...
If you're just being born,
I guess you can't talk much.
Hey, Okarin...
When the world seems like darkness...
...and you're afraid of the shadows.
Don't close your eyes.
Don't give up.
Don't kill off Hououin Kyouma.
That way, my feelings might reach you.
Even if traveling hundreds
and thousands of hours...
...just like the light of that star.
Mayushii will wait at the lab,
however long it takes...
Waiting for you, and all the others.
Let's meet again in Steins Gate.
--I killed her... I killed Kurisu... I killed Kurisu...
--It's okay. This isn't his blood.
Okarin?
It's Okarin's phone.
An e-mail?
Open it.
--But...
--Just do it.
"You have new messages"
"Inbox"
"Subject: (No subject)"
"Turn on the news..."
Turn on the news...
The news?
Despite a fire in the cargo bay,
the airplane carrying Dr. Nakabachi...
...managed to land in Russia,
to which he recently defected.
--Oh! That's Mayushii's Metal Upa!
--WTF?!
What's it doing in Russia?
That paper is the start of it all...
"Mayushii's"
This pits the world's superpowers in
an intense race to develop a time machine.
Ultimately, it leads to world war.
The lives of 5.7 billion people are at stake.
Save Makise Kurisu!
Change the worldline!
I can't.
It's just like what happened with Mayuri.
However hard I try, it'll always end the same...
Remember the exact moment
Hououin Kyouma was born!
With Kurisu dying.
I know.
I know how insane this time loop is...
I know how cruel of a fate it has in store...
I knew...
I knew this would happen...
I'm tired...
I've had enough...
For you, billions and billions of heartbeats
are nothing at all; just the blink of an eye
Greetings...
...me from 15 years ago.
are nothing at all; just the blink of an eye
If you've opened this message,
Although I'm trapped by
the past and lament the future
then that means you've failed to rescue Kurisu.
inevitability won't allow for
even a speck of a miscalculation
It must've been painful for you.
But that pain also gave me determination.
Our dreams and futures that
form and expand into "infinity"
So I couldn't afford to undo it.
allow us the right to be vain,
Now we can move to the real focus of our plan.
The plan is this: save
Makise Kurisu and enter Steins Gate.
while the two hands
point out what is "finite"
I was also the one who named
the target worldline "Steins Gate."
All of which leads to a cruel
contract and choice to make
I'm sure you know the reason for that name too.
Hacking to the Gate
So, now, with each passing
second, I'll cross worldlines
It doesn't really mean anything.
Isn't that right?
Hey, you sure about this?
to protect that smile on your face
Yeah, probably...
Won't Okabe Rintaro in
2010 be embarrassed by this?
Then, once again, into a
time loop without sadness
Don't worry. He was even
more amazing back then.
I don't even wanna imagine.
I will now outline your
final mission: Operation Skuld.
I will be swallowed up as a lone observer
You must change the outcome
without altering established past events.
So, now, with each passing
second, I'll cross worldlines
Deceive your original self.
Deceive the world.
That is the only way you can reach Steins Gate.
to protect that smile on your face
Good luck.
Then, once again, into a
time loop without sadness
El Psy Kongroo.
Cut! Nice, that was perfect, nya!
I will be swallowed up as a lone observer
Now all that's left is to send it
with a D-Mail to the past.
Luka.
Right.
The video just now goes to Kyouma in 2010.
And the one Itaru took...
...goes to Suzuha in 2011
after you depart on your trip.
You really wanna do this?
What's wrong?
Because, you're manning the first run
of an experimental time machine.
You say you're supposed
to die this year in 2025.
But that doesn't mean
you should just throw your life--
I have no intention of doing so.
I fully believe that we will succeed.
But...
What if you interpret it like this?
In 2025, Okabe Rintaro doesn't die, but...
...he boards the first version
of our time machine...
...and leaves for another space-time.
Disappearing from this worldline is...
...essentially the same as dying, is it not?
That's some crazy positive thinking.
Though, it holds up as a theory, right?
"Mad Scientist: Trick world.
Connect all
Potentials."
The world can be deceived.
My friends, thank you
for following me till today!
As you know, on that day in 2011...
...a time machine left
for the past but was lost.
I leave now to find Mayuri and Suzuha!
The Kerr black hole tracer
will help me find their locus.
It should lead me straight to them!
Okarin.
Take this.
Are you sure?
Yes... Please give it to Mommy for me.
All right.
Let me ask you one last time...
Does Steins Gate...
Does it really exist, you think?
It does.
For sure.
As of now, the operation begins!
Its name is...
...Operation Altair!
Do you think... he'll succeed?
Of course. Kyouma can do it, nya.
That's right. He makes the impossible possible.
That's what makes Okarin our Okarin.
Okarin...
The universe has a beginning, but no end.
Infinite.
Stars have beginnings too,
but meet an end of their own making.
Finite.
History has shown that those
with wisdom are the greatest fools of all.
Fish that live in the sea know nothing of land.
If they had that wisdom,
they, too, would be ruined.
For humans to exceed the speed of light...
...is more foolish than
for fish to start living on land.
This is the story of those who
fought against God's final ultimatum.
This is the epigraph of their obsession.
Suzu!
Mmm!
Sorry to keep you waiting, you two!