If you were here, you should've said something.
You'll scare someone standing around like that.
Happy New Year.
It's just a simple greeting...
Or maybe it's too late to say Happy New Year?
Anyways, this is a shock.
You never show your face anymore.
Th-That's no way to start off the year!
This is a world of unreality,
Nothing more than an imprinted vision.
The Point at Infinity
Where those values lie overwritten by this inert universe
If God in his arrogance reigns through lightspeed unseen,
Then I alone
will be the miraculous...
the fatal... minority.
I can fly high
All those moments and places
If you think they're special,
Then you shouldn't try
to leave the past behind.
Those invaluable scenes
will eclipse the heartache
As each and every light forms to yield Zero.
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
Sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Happens to me sometimes too.
You were thinking of her...
About Mayuri...
Eh?
She always comes to mind when I'm in the lab.
You hear footsteps, the door opens...
and you half-expect that greeting of hers again.
Okabe?!
Okabe?
Sorry about that.
No, I am.
I said something I shouldn't have.
Now that I think about it, you haven't
stopped by here ever since Mayuri.
Y-Yeah?
Ever since then,
you've practically fallen off the grid.
Hashida too, but not nearly as bad as you.
Is it true then? Is this an Alpha worldline?
Where's the PhoneWave?
You're the one who demolished it,
don't you remember?
Okabe?
I think... I need to go outside
and get fresh air.
Okay... Hang in there.
The city and people feel the same...
It's no different than yesterday.
But, in this Alpha worldline,
there's one reality...
That is, no matter what I do, convergence
will always result in Mayuri's death...
...in this worldline.
"From: Daru" "To: Okabe Rintaro"
"She's being taken to the hospital right now.
They say it's probably a heart attack. At least, that's what the paramedics said. Her parents are on their way to the hospital too."
She's being taken to the hospital right now.
They say it's probably a heart attack.
Even if somehow,
we escape the grasp of SERN...
...as long as we're in this worldline,
Mayuri will be killed by the world.
That's why... That's why I...
And yet, why am I back here?!
Why did Reading Steiner kick in?!
There wasn't a D-Mail!
I didn't use the time leap machine either!
"Another Earthquake in Russia"
Okarin?
Huh?
Daru?
It's rare to find you in Akiba these days.
Welcome home, nya!
Welcome, Masters!
I'm back!
I brought Okarin with me today!
O-Okabe?!
Lukako?
Kyouma!
Missed you so much, nya! Kyouma!
Have I really not come in that long?
No, you haven't...
For a while there, I didn't visit much either.
Um...
Nice to meet you, I'm Fubuki.
I was one of Mayuri's
cosplay friends, so she was dear to me.
Fubu-nya has been helping out at
the cafe ever since Mayushii left us, nya.
It's been tough, but I figured
Mayuri would be happier this way.
Here's a picture of us at Summer ComiMa.
The outfits she made us were so cute,
we took a photo together to look back upon.
She... was spunky as ever.
Nothing at all seemed wrong with her...
She was just, being herself...
Fubu-nya, remember what I said?
Mayushii would be worried
if you keep on crying, nya...
Okay, Fubu-nya?
What if...
What if there was a world...
where Mayuri was able to live?
What if that world... you knew was out there?
Huh? Daru?
Step outside, Okarin.
Hey!
Okabe...
Wh-What's your problem?
There's things you can say
and things you shouldn't say!
A world where Mayushii was able to live?!
You're the one who couldn't
make that decision, Okarin!
Echelon's data... We had it cracked
and everything, but you stopped it!
I... couldn't press the key?
Yeah...
You kept saying it, over and over...
I'm the one who killed Mayushii.
I'm the one who made that choice.
Why did you trash the PhoneWave
and time leap machine?!
If you were going to regret it later,
you should've kept it all intact!
Even Miss Makise told you so...
Kurisu did?
She said we had a chance!
That we can try it again!
That there must be something we can do!
"Television CRT Workshop"
Hello, this is Makise.
Hashida? It's been a while. Happy New Year.
Happy New Year to ya.
What a surprise.
You practically never call me, Hashida.
I ran into Okarin.
I see...
I bet he came to the lab too, right?
Yeah...
Did he say anything?
Yeah, he's still not over Mayushii.
He asked what if there was a world
where we knew she could live.
And then?
I got mad... Couldn't believe he said
that after everything that happened...
Do you think...?
Kurisu?
You knew I was here?
Of course I knew, it's you.
I see...
Just kidding.
GPS.
You had something like that?
So you don't know after all...
Okabe, you...
...came from another worldline, didn't you?
"Dual of Antinomy - Antinomic Dual -"
That spot you're sitting in...
That's where Mayuri always used to sit.
The guy who gave up on her...
He would never sit down in her spot.
I guess that was his way
of burdening the guilt.
Plus, you had no idea about the GPS either.
True, but what's it for?
I won't say.
That's...!
I remade it.
I call it PhoneWave Revised. No... I
suppose it's PhoneWave (Revised).
You made it again?! What for?
To send a message into the past.
No...
In order to change worldlines.
Okabe, I want you to use this and
go back to the worldline you came from.
What do you...
Where you're from, Mayuri lives...
Rather, you're from a worldline
where you were able to keep her alive.
You... saw right through me?
Of course. I've watched you for
so long it's... I mean, not in that way...
Well, it is, but...
Anyways, you're Okabe Rintaro
from another worldline.
There's nothing more to say.
Go back.
By changing worldlines,
it's true that Mayuri's able to live.
But, even a world like that changed so easily...
It changed back again
without me doing anything...
It's true... This time I did nothing at all...
And yet, why did it end up like this?
I did that to you...
I took the you who loved me
and made you disappear...
And yet... And yet...
You're telling me to kill you again?
I can't... I can't do it...
Hashida?
Where's Okarin?
He said he'll be back.
In the end, we should've known
Okabe could never forget Mayuri...
But, Miss Makise...
No, never mind...
"Yushima Seido"    "Achievement"
Made up your mind yet?
Of course you haven't...
The trains are running, right?
Meet me at Akihabara Station in an hour.
Why?
There's somewhere I want to take you.
Hard to spot you without your lab coat.
Where are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
What?
It's just, we never rode
the train together like this...
Quit ogling at me or I'll report you.
But I'm innocent.
The law states even a gaze can
be considered sexual harassment.
Amadeus has got nothing on you.
Amadeus?
Oh, the artificial intelligence.
How do you know about that?
Did I ever tell you?
Through Hiyajo and Professor Leskinen.
Huh?! You know Maho?!
What the heck happened in your worldline?!
What are you so angry about?
I'm not angry! Hmph!
Right after that, she was
unable to access Amadeus.
Hmm...
What happened to Amadeus?
I don't know...
But from a rational standpoint, I can't imagine
AI having anything to do with a worldline change.
A coincidence, then?
Amadeus has all my memories stored within it,
which means my time machine
theory would be there too.
It would?
In theory, I denied their existence though.
...time machines are not possible.
However, that is not to say
they are impossible altogether.
Kurisu... Amadeus answered me differently...
I was hoping Daddy would look at it, so I...
You're stealing my theory?
Okabe?
I'm all right.
I can't believe you made
friends with Maho.
I bumped into her at a seminar.
Then you must know how rude
and stubborn that girl can be.
So clumsy too...
That part of her hasn't changed.
I take it you were her feisty junior then?
How rude! I was a very courteous junior.
I always went out and
bought her drinks, like jasmine tea...
"Shiina Family Grave"
The others must be visiting too...
You were a complete wreck after Mayuri died...
You stopped going to lab and college,
and stayed here all day till the sun went down.
It was as if...
...you were waiting for someone
to come and take you to heaven...
I couldn't do anything for you either.
After all, you did it so I could live...
Kurisu...
But, that all ends now.
It has to end now.
At this rate, you'll be crushed by guilt.
It's the same there...
Even if I go to a beta worldline...
That feeling doesn't change...
It's you I sacrifice, and I--
Get a hold of yourself, Okabe Rintaro!
Stop making that face...
If you're the Hououin Kyouma I know,
you've gotta be confident and strong...
That's all just a big act! It's a lie!
It's only something I did to cheer Mayuri up...
All you wanted was for Mayuri to smile...
That's all that matters.
And I feel the same way too.
The decision you made was not wrong.
The only thing wrong is this world...
This worldline...
That's why you have to return, Okabe Rintaro.
You're here because this is only a dream.
Return to reality.
A dream?
Yes...
Let's go back... To the lab.
Before you wake from your dream,
promise me one thing.
What's that?
When you get back, forget all about me.
There's no way... I can't...
Do it, even if you can't... That's what I want.
It's not about emotions, it's Amadeus...
Eh?
I don't know what caused
your worldline to change this time.
But, it's obvious time machines
are involved somehow.
But, the PhoneWave...
I can't make any claims
about myself in your worldline,
but in this one, I completed my
time machine theory only after meeting you.
Since I can't guarantee
the same won't happen there,
it's dangerous for you two to interact too much.
It's a pinky promise.
Lie, and I'll stab an electrode
into your hippocampus!
It's a pinky promise!
That was lame.
Shut up.
"Don't come in."
"Send message?"
"Send | Cancel"
Hey...
Eh?
Do you remember? How we first met...
Grabbing and tugging my clothes like that...
I thought you were some sort of pervert.
I see...
From her perspective, is that how we first met?
I...
Wait...
Everything's ready.
All that's left is to send that message, and
you'll go back to the worldline you came from.
Okabe?
Huh? Yeah...
If I send this, I'll go back to that worldline.
A world where Mayuri lives...
A world where I don't lose her...
But instead, I lose her right there...
Kurisu is gone, because I kill her...
My most... most precious...
Okabe?
"Send message?"
"Send | Cancel"
"You're always on my mind"
is a gentle lie that everyone knows
I'm so glad I met you.
Kurisu?
"Don't come in."
"Send message?"
"Goodbye"
"I want to be with you forever"
"Send message?"
"Send | Cancel"
is it love if that's what I feel?
From the miraculous, fated encounter
we head once more towards that place—
I stretch my hand to the twinkling stars in the night sky
Both the memories and warm days revive
Overflowing at that moment, at that place
Your words, the tears and laughter
Even if these memories are rewritten
They'll sway in my heart, just like déjà vu
"Inbox Received"
"From: Okabe"
"Don't come in."
Okabe!
I feel the same! I love--