U-Um...
It's great that Kagari
finally got her memories back.
Yeah... It sure is.
Mommy...
Um...
Hey, Kagari-san.
Chan!
Eh?
It's Kagari-chan, right?
K-Kagari-chan?
What is it, Mommy?
Want to eat a banana with me?
Banana?
How about I feed it to you instead?
Huh? That's okay, I can do it myself...
Aww...
When I used to feed you before,
it made Mommy so happy.
Th-Then, could you do it for me?
Yup!
Say ahh!
Okarin...
What?
What do you think? Could this be
a possible Yuri breakthrough?
It's a tough one...
U-Um...
Could I ask you something?
How is Mayuri her mommy?
Well...
Mommy, I love you!
This is a world of unreality,
Nothing more than an imprinted vision.
The Point at Infinity
Where those values lie overwritten by this inert universe
If God in his arrogance reigns through lightspeed unseen,
Then I alone
will be the miraculous...
the fatal... minority.
I can fly high
If that moment, if that place was
something you thought was special to you
All those moments and places
If you think they're special,
Those invaluable scenes
will eclipse the heartache
As each and every light forms to yield Zero.
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
Wow! This is for me?!
Yup!
I'm so happy! Thank you, Mommy!
Sure!
I think it's pretty amazing how well
Mayushii grasped the situation.
I feel like it's less that she grasps it
and more that she's just accepting it...
She's Mayushii's... daughter?
That's right.
Huh?! Sh-She can't be!
Mayushii hasn't gave birth to a kid yet!
I'm saying it's not like that.
She came here along with Suzuha from the future.
From the future?
Mommy took me in because
I didn't have any living relatives.
Mayushii did?
But, Mayushii doesn't remember that at all...
Of course, you wouldn't.
From your perspective,
that all happens in the distant future.
Mommy!
I'd worry for her sanity if
she wasn't skeptical, you noob.
That's true.
Okarin!
Look, look at this! How cool!
Hmm?
Ta-da!
Oh?
Mommy gave it to me!
They match! Neat, right?
Yeah, it sure is.
Man, Kagari.
Your personality sure changed a bit.
Because her memories of the
future with Mayuri came back?
It's like you're so cheerful now...
and you're so lively now.
Eh? You think?
I guess this must be her original personality.
Mayushii thinks this Kagari-sa--
Kagari-chan is wonderful too!
Really? I'm glad to hear it!
Ah! Where's Big Sis Suzuha?
Now that you mention it...
She actually left a little while ago.
Oh, shoot!
I've got to hurry back to work!
Gotta go, Mommy! Bye!
See you later!
Hmm?
In the end, I guess only her
childhood memories came back.
Wasn't she around six years old
when she became Mayushii's daughter?
Supposedly.
But after that, in the year 2036,
she time traveled to the past
with Suzuha when she was 10.
Suzuha had to use the IBN 5100
in order to fix the Y2K problem.
So, she swung by 1975
before time traveling to 1998.
But that's where Kagari
got separated from her.
And the last thing she remembers
is 12 years later in 2010.
From after she was found collapsed
at the border of Chiba Prefecture.
Then the other day,
the shock from that accident may have
brought her childhood memories back again.
But from age 10 to 22, there's a 12-year void.
Yeah...
Even for how peaceful a place Japan is,
there's no way a 10-year-old girl
could survive here alone.
It's only normal to think somebody,
somewhere, was taking care of her.
Even so, we've got no information to go on.
And Miss Kiryu is still investigating,
but there's not a clue to be found...
Until she remembers what happened
on her own, is there's nothing we can do?
If only there was a hint
or something we could look into...
Um...
I'm so sorry for coming late...
Huh?
Boss? Are you there?
He went out.
I see! In that case, I could've
spent more time with Mommy.
J-Just kidding! I would never skip work!
Oh, yeah. Big Sis Suzuha.
I got a matching smartphone case from Mommy!
Yeah? Good for you.
And um, she said we'll go out somewhere for fun.
Why don't you come with us too, Big Sis--
No, I'm good.
Why not?
I don't have time to screw around.
Could it be... that you hate me or something?
Why would you think that?
Because, you say stuff like
that with a scary face.
I was born with this face.
Besides, I have a mission to do.
You looked happy enough
stuffing your face with curry.
Well that's... You can't fight
on an empty stomach!
Hmm?
What's that face mean?
I was born with this face.
I don't care if you play with
your mommy, but keep me out of it.
Must be nice to be you...
You've had all the time in the world
to play with your mom and dad in this era.
Say what?!
It's true! You've been with Uncle Daru
and Yuki for half a year already!
But when it comes to me, I'm not allowed
to spend time and have fun with Mommy?!
You little...! Do you have any
idea how hard it's been for me?!
I spent a ton of precious fuel
just searching for you!
I'm sorry, but--
Not once did you try to contact me!
And then you finally appear
but conveniently forget everything!
It's not like I... I didn't forget
because I wanted to.
Besides, if it's anyone's fault,
it's yours for abandoning me!
That day, if you hadn't gone running off like
you did, I wouldn't have been left all alone!
Wait, Kagari... What did you say?
You heard me! When we were walking
that day, you disappeared on me!
After that was so...
I was so helpless...
Oh?
The hell you two standing around for?
If your hands are free, go clean something!
Keep slacking like that and
you ain't getting paid.
Kagari's memory seems odd?
Well, that's what I've heard from Suzuha.
It's like, the stuff that Kagari
remembers seems to be different
than how Suzuha remembers it going.
Then again, it's from when she was little,
so her memory of things might not be perfect.
That's true, but...
Hmm?
Kagari?
Ah, Mommy.
What's wrong?
Ever since my memory came back,
everyone looks so troubled...
I'm thinking... maybe it's better
if I hadn't remembered?
Kagari...
The causes of memory loss?
Yes. What's more,
only part of it won't come back.
Don't you find that odd?
Yeah, that does seem a bit too convenient.
The thing is, I'm no expert.
I'm fine with that.
Please tell me anything you can think of.
To list off the normal reasons,
you can have an accident, illness,
or stress and emotional shock.
That about sums it up.
But if it's not one of those,
could a third party have meddled
and done something artificially?
Is that what you're thinking?
Well?
I don't know...
But... it might... be just that.
Hmm...
In that case, only one thing comes to mind.
And that's?
Brainwashing.
Mind control.
"Mother Goose of Diffractive Recitativo
- Diffraction Mother Goose -"
"Fun for All Ages with Mozart"
"July 17 - August 28
Uh...
You're... still living here?
That's it?
Mmm.
"Found one"
"Within a 5km range of where
Kagari Shiina collapsed"
"Just one place"
"A building not on records
and shouldn't be there"
"Congrats"
Uh-huh uh-huh.
There's really something there?
We won't know for sure unless we go.
What do you think?
"Radio Kaikan Akihabara"
Well, that doesn't seem like you at all.
Yeah... I'm thinking I said too much.
In a way, I think it's because I'm envious.
Of Kagari?
Yeah...
If I could forget the whole mission...
Live freely, spoiled by everyone...
If you want to be spoiled,
here's looking at you, kid.
Dummy.
Then again...
If you regret what you said,
why not just apologize to her?
I'm not very good at that
sort of thing. It's the timing...
If only... I had an opportunity.
So, yeah. That's why
I'm thinking of throwing a party!
A party?
Yup! To celebrate Kagari
getting back her memories.
Kagari?
Yeah! But, I don't know...
Do you think Kagari would like that?
It's a great idea.
If you're planning it, I'm sure she'll love it.
Really? Then I'll let everyone know
and start making preparations!
Mayushii's gonna be busy!
"Ready to investigate"
"Can leave tomorrow morning~
Long drive is going to be a pain"
"Fun for All Ages with Mozart"
Tomorrow night?
Yeah. Since it's a Sunday,
can you come to the lab at five?
Of course, I can.
Oh... But if you're there, I'll ask
the boss to let me go early and come--
Ah... You're not allowed to come early.
Eh? Why not?
Well that's... a secret!
I've got it. Must be a party.
Eh?!
Wh-Why say that?
Because, whenever you act
suspicious like this, it's always a party.
So? Am I right?
W-We'll just see about that...
A-Anyways, you can't come before five o'clock!
Okay.
Oh, and...
Mind if I invite Suzu?
Why are you asking me that?
That's because... You and Suzu
haven't been talking much lately.
I don't know what happened between you, but...
Both you and Suzu are very precious to me,
so I just want you two to get along.
Mommy...
All right.
Big Sis Suzuha has been through a lot too.
Mmm...
Tomorrow, when I come
and meet her, I'll apologize.
And hopefully, we can talk
things through from the top.
Yeah!
Looks like somebody splurged yet again, nya!
The food and drinks are all taken care of, nya!
They'll deliver right before it starts, nya!
And we've got enough plates and cups.
Hello...
Suzu! Thanks for coming!
Y-Yeah...
Thanks for the message.
By the way, where are the others?
Daru is out shopping for a
few things with Yuki and the others.
Okarin has been gone on
some business since this morning,
but he said he'll be back for the party.
In that case, it's brainwashing.
Brainwashing?
I don't know the exact method how they're
able to make or break memories as they please.
But using drugs or some sort of technique,
they say memories can be forcibly repressed.
What I'm saying,
is that it's not entirely impossible.
If there's guys out there who
did something like that to Kagari...
"Congrats Kagari!"
Hello!
Welcome!
You all made it, nya!
Whew... No more shopping, I beg you...
Yoo-hoo! We're here!
Hello!
Thanks for having me!
Miss Nae! Welcome, Miss Nae!
Hello, Mr. Smileybear.
Bear?
Wh-Whoa! Aren't you going too fast?!
Mountain days are short.
If we don't hurry, it'll get dark.
And dark... is dangerous.
Huh? Eh? Ahhh!
Can you please try to drive safe?!
All right. It's safer if we get there faster.
Noooo!
"Sweets Akihabara"
"Mansei Bridge" "Kanda Post Office"
"Shohei Bridge" "2 Chome Sotokanda"
"Kanda Shrine"
This way.
Eh?
It's really up ahead?
This is...
It seems like it was used until recently.
Huh? It's got to be years since anyone--
A guise.
Eh?
It's scattered around to look like that,
but the glass and fragments are relatively new.
It's been half a year,
maybe one year at the longest.
Want to investigate deeper?
Let's go.
Thank you very much.
It's a bit early, but...
No big deal!
I wonder if Big Sis Suzuha will like it or not?
So, what are you saying, Doctor?
Kagari still needs more treatment?
She may appear to be completely healed, but...
In order to completely cure
her PTSD brought about by war,
it takes a significant amount of time.
But I hate the treatment.
It makes my head hurt.
Can you tough it out a little more?
Mommy will be right with you, okay?
Okay... I will.
Come on, Kagari.
Let's do our best again today.
I... hear it...
The voice... of God...
Kaga-nya is late, nya.
She promised to come straight here...
I wonder if something happened?
Mayushii will try calling again.
Right.
I'm going to look for her.
Suzuha!
Come to me
Embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
"No signal"
Okabe.
There is peace, the truth within us
What's up? What was that sound?
I found a switch,
Emptiness erodes your heart
pressed it, and found this.
A hidden passage?
Coz you're free from pain and sorrow
Future is just too bright to show you ways
Okabe.
Wake up now...it's time to lead new souls
In here.
"Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy"
"I miss you"
Orbit of photon and universe
"Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy"
"I miss you"
Orbit of photon and universe
"Mommy"
"Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy"
I am just the part of its plan
Th-This is...
With eyes unaware of the distorted sky
Kagari was... here after all?
Where is it the people walk to?
But... Who would have done this?!
And for what purpose?!
The last game
Hello?
Thank goodness you picked up! Okarin!
What's wrong, Mayuri?
Listen, it's Kagari! Kagari is...
She's missing?!