Go back... To a world where Mayuri lives...
It can't be...
Mayuri!
Mayuri?!
Okarin?
Huh?
Looks like you're finally up.
Hot damn!
You had us all worried
when you collapsed like that!
Collapsed?
I did?
This is a world of unreality,
Nothing more than an imprinted vision.
The Point at Infinity
Where those values lie overwritten by this inert universe
If God in his arrogance reigns through lightspeed unseen,
Then I alone
will be the miraculous...
the fatal... minority.
I can fly high
All those moments and places
If you think they're special,
Then you shouldn't try
to leave the past behind.
Those invaluable scenes
will eclipse the heartache
As each and every light forms to yield Zero.
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
Nakase and I did, in the lab?
Yeah...
The hospital stays closed for the
New Year, so we were freaking out.
Is that right?
Did I go back to the original worldline?
Here.
Hmm?
--Makise Kurisu...
--Eh?
Eh?
Do you know Makise Kurisu?
Yup, I know her.
That's the person you have
inside of your phone, right?
Amadeus, or something...
Don't scare me like that...
Speaking of which, how's Amadeus?
We avoided the takeover,
but it's being restored.
The thing is...
What happened?
We found out a thief broke
into Maho's room.
And that's not all...
There's talk about a gas explosion at the
Wako office, so we're not allowed to enter.
With timing like that, it's possible
somebody planned it all out.
Any idea who did it?
No clue...
The attackers from before, maybe?
Oh, you're awake now!
Has your fever come down?
Yeah, it's fine now.
You feeling better too, Okarin?
Huh? Yeah...
The doctors are saying it might be
that new form of encephalitis.
It's probably nothing to worry about.
A new encephalitis?
They say it's going around lately,
giving people bad fevers and such.
But, I wonder why you two collapsed
at the exact same time?
Without any external stimulus,
the fact that it happened is hard to believe.
I knew it! It has to be!
You're still on that?
What, what?
Kaede seems to think Okarin
is my soulmate or something.
Huh?
It's true, Fubuki! When you came to,
all you talked about was Okarin!
I told you, that was only because of the dream!
Dream?
I had this very realistic dream...
Well, but Mayushii...
It was a dream! It was just in the dream, but...
Mayushii was gone...
And I was with Faris in her cafe.
And then, well... Okarin came...
Memories from an Alpha worldline...
Could it be Reading Steiner?
Hmm, well...
You're not showing any more symptoms,
but we'll schedule a follow-up.
We'd like for you to come back next week.
Sure...
It's great that they let you leave, Okarin.
Fubuki has to stay a little longer, though.
Don't worry! She's spunky, so I bet she's okay!
--You think? Maybe you're right...
--Okabe.
--Yeah!
Why did you mention Kurisu back there?
Well, it's just...
I had a dream...
A dream?
By the way, where's Hashida?
Oh, Daru said he had to leave
to take care of something.
"All right."
"OK!"
"There's something I need you to look into."
Yeah?
"Monday, January 3rd 2011."
"Is Russia Testing Nukes?"
"Growing Suspicion Puts Nations on Guard"
Anything else?
Yeah... Okarin wasn't showing
any problems, so he got discharged.
Uncle Okarin and the others were attacked,
and later those two collapsed...
How was he when he came to?
Not really any different than usual.
But he did say a name... Miss Makise's.
Makise?
See you!
Okay! I'll message you later!
"Television CRT Workshop"
Here, coffee.
Thanks.
Now that I think about it, with the thief
breaking into my hotel and the fire fiasco,
I haven't had anything since last night.
All we have here is chicken and bananas...
Oh, should I go buy you a bento?
I'm fine. I'll eat after
I get back to the hotel.
You're going back?
The professor asked the same thing.
He said I might want to change my hotel.
I'm sure it's safer that way.
Though, I don't know where to go.
What about here?
I can't intrude like that.
Considering the attack just went
down here, it's not exactly safe...
"I checked out the Wako City office~"
"Nothing to report"
"So sorry"
Nothing to go on...
Right.
Eh?
Whoa! Wh-Where did you come from?!
Hmm?
A guest of yours?
Y-Yeah...
When did you?
"I've been here for a while!"
"I know I don't stand out much, but you're
making me feel invisible! You hurt my feelings~"
"Hmph! Pout!"
You were there all along?
I was.
"Hmph! Pout!"
"Know who the attackers were?"
"Nope~"
"Or what they're after?"
"No clue~"
What's up? Why aren't you talking?
Uh, well...
Hmm?
"Aww, shucks!"
"Can you keep on investigating for me?"
"OK!"
I made coffee... Huh?
Did your guest leave already?
And I even made coffee for them...
I'm back...
I will... save this worldline.
I'll protect this world where Mayuri lives...
And without using the time machine!
I'm sure that's what she wanted too.
It's all I can do...
Hiyajo.
Eh?
Do you think you could hold off finding a hotel?
I've got an idea.
So that's why you came, nya?
Yeah... We think having her
stay here is our best option for now.
But it's so sudden...
It's not fair to ask you.
Faris doesn't care at all, nya.
I knew it.
See what I mean? I told you Faris
wouldn't have a problem with it.
You can use the guest room, nya.
Stay forever! Maho-nya should
sleep over for as long as you're in Japan!
Maho-nya?
We've got Kuroki here, so it's super safe, nya!
--Kuroki? Hold on, wait!
--Come on, this way! Let's take a bath together!
Now we can all rest assured.
So... Kagari is with Lukako, right?
Yup! I just heard from him a bit ago!
He'll make sure she doesn't go outside,
so he said not to worry.
For the time being, I've done everything I can.
Now just to figure out who raided
the lab, and what they're after...
Suzuha?
"I need to talk to you alone”
“Waiting to hear back"
Suzuha?
I'm right here.
Sorry for calling you out here like this.
What's this about?
The thing is, I'm terrible
at steering conversations.
So forgive me,
but I'll get straight to the point.
What?
Did the worldline change?
Wha--?
What makes you say that?
Given the situation, plus what you've
told me about Reading Steiner and whatnot.
And if I tell you?
You may not think it,
but it matters a lot to me.
Suzuha...
Answer me. That's an order, Okabe Rintaro!
"Pandora of Eternal Return - Pandora's Box -"
I'll ask you once more.
Has the worldline changed?
Is this a different worldline than before?
Don't worry.
This worldline is the same one we were in.
For real?
Yeah... We did move to another worldline
temporarily, but I think we're back again.
So it did change after all...
But right now, I don't know the reason why.
Earthquakes... in Russia.
Eh?
They're not because of nuclear testing.
It's from Russia and
America's race for a time machine.
Sooner or later, that competition
will spark the beginning of World War III.
Russia... and America?
The way they said it, it has to be...
That's phonetic code.
Phonetic code?
For military use.
More specifically, by the Western world.
Is that how it is?!
"Another Earthquake in Russia"
Which means back then...
I'm such an idiot...
I kept worrying about what to do,
but I never had time for that!
What will you do then?
You're coming with me, back to July 28th.
And if I refuse?
I won't allow you to.
They're experimenting
with time machines as we speak.
What if the worldline changes as a result,
and the path to Steins Gate is closed off forever?
What if... it's already too late?
Could you choose?
Could you make the decision
between two worldlines?
You're willing to let this worldline
go completely to waste?!
Shut up!
Suzuha...
The next one will hit.
Please...
July, 2010...
Using the PhoneWave (name subject to change),
I realized I could send mails to the past...
But in the end, all that did
was change the worldline.
To get back to the original,
I trampled over countless memories.
I took things that happened and undid them all.
I sacrificed more than you can ever imagine,
just to finally get back to this worldline!
And now, if I go back to that summer...
The nightmare will repeat all over!
And you're fine with this worldline as it is?!
World War III will start,
and billions of people will die!
You can't escape it!
That's what this worldline is!
And what if we only make the situation worse?
That's...
What if we do manage to change worldlines,
but all that's waiting for us is a hopeless
future worse than the one you know?!
Even if we can change worldlines,
we can't manipulate the future.
Suzuha.
Dad...
I kinda figured this would happen...
What's with the gun?
You should know, Dad!
We don't have time for this!
At this rate, World War III will...
Even if you force Okarin to come along,
do you think that'll solve anything?
That's...
From the moment I started researching time
machines and worldlines, I realized something.
Trying to control worldlines and
the laws of causality is no simple feat.
Then... What can we do?
That's the whole reason
we're researching, right?
Dad...
One of these times, I wish you
would listen and do as your father says.
Just leave it all to me.
I'll figure something out.
I'm a super hacker, and don't you forget it.
I... don't know what to do anymore...
I don't know what's right...
Mm-hmm.
Help me, Dad...
Help me...
Please... Dad... Help me...
Dad...
World War III...
Using the information we've got,
can we somehow change the future
without using the time machine?
It's a tough one...
But thinking something impossible without
due consideration is the downfall of a scientist.
That's what you'd say... If it were you...
Hmm?
Oh? What's this?
If you came to beg for more time to pay--
I want to continue our conversation.
You...
Seriously?
Yes.
Who knows? It's not enough info to go on.
If you can tell me which organizations
use phonetic codes, that might help.
Well, there's probably thousands
in the west alone. However...
However?
If some group was responsible for that attack,
I can't imagine their name being public.
Either they're a group whose
name is kept under wraps,
or a group that seems innocent enough
on the surface to not suspect of foul play.
For example?
You really gonna make me answer that?
Whatever... You knowing
makes no difference to me.
To be honest...
If I had to take a guess, assuming
that whole story you told me was true...
"Show only Japanese results" "Use search options"
DURPA... Defense Ultimate
Research Projects Agency.
Created by the Department of Defense
as an organization for military research...
Stratfor...
A private American think tank... Called a shadow
CIA that can predict large-scale terrorism.
Russia's time machine research is based on...
Dr. Nakabachi's paper?
You're going to steal it, Daddy?!
If America connected the dots...
Their hunt for data would
lead straight to Makise Kurisu...
Why not raid Viktor Chondria University then?
They could easily tap
into the research computers.
Why would they come all the way here?
When they attacked the lab,
they were after Kagari...
Because she came from the future?
Are they after the time machine she came in?
Even if that's true, they won't ever find it.
Why not?
If their time machine research was based
on a time machine from the future,
it would make a huge time paradox.
It can never happen.
Which means...
...a thief broke into Maho's room.
And that's not all...
There's talk about a
gas explosion at the Wako office...
Is that how it is?!
You know what?
I believe that someday,
Okarin will stand to take up command
and lead everyone to where we need to go.
What time is it?
It'll soon be a brand-new day.
Think he'll get in?
Hmm?
Uncle Okarin... in the time machine.
When the time comes, he will.
And then, Hououin Kyouma will be reborn.
I rise from the ashes like a phoenix!
He'll be delusional like the good old days...
After all, the Future Gadget Laboratory
only exists because of Okarin.
Dad... Do you realize how embarrassing
the things you're saying are?
Oh fudge, you're right...
I'd rather die than say that to his face...
I think... I'll write a letter.
I need to tell Uncle Okarin I'm sorry...
And that I'll keep at it.
That's a good idea...
And while you're at it,
write one for Daddy please!
With some cute photos too!
If I feel like it...
Hey, now... What's with the dejected reply?
I mean, we don't have
time for stuff like that...
Because Russia started
time machine experiments?
There's that too, but it's the fuel...
I kinda used a lot of it up
searching for Kagari...
Can't we swap out the battery?
Nope... I had Big Sis Rumi bring me
one of those big batteries they put in trucks,
but it died in a second.
How much more can we jump?
Half a year, maybe once or twice...
And that's it.
What if the battery dies while traveling?
Who knows?
Lose control and get stuck beyond
the event horizon for all of eternity?
Don't say stuff that might jinx it!
Sorry.
Mmm...
Though, I wonder what that would be like?
Would it be peaceful like
it is right now, for all eternity?
If it were, that's not so bad...
Hiyajo--
What's the matter?
What happened here? It's a disaster...
Disaster?
If you ask me, it's quite pleasant in here.
Hasn't it only been one day?
It's too dangerous to go outside,
so I've gotta do my research here.
What's up?
Uh, well...
Kurisu was researching a time machine theory?
Yeah... And they're most likely
after any trace of her research.
Possibly, that theory of hers is inside Amadeus.
Do you know if she had anything?
For example, notes of her research,
or stand-alone data?
If there's something like that,
it could explain the attack.
There's...
...nothing.
I see...
Amadeus...
Come to me
Embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
Coz you're free from pain and sorrow
Future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now...it's time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just the part of its plan
With eyes unaware of the distorted sky
Where is it the people walk to?
The last game