K-Kagari?
Wait!
Kagari...
Where is it?
The precious gift... Mommy gave me.
Precious gift, huh?
Big Sis Rumi...
Well, nya?
Hmm... I've got maybe a week left.
Feel bad for the others, though.
Suzu-nya, what's that?
Ah...
This is a treasure of mine.
Oh, is that you?!
Which means the one next to you is...
Yup. It's a photo with Mom.
Why do you look so grumpy in the picture, nya?
To be honest, I don't really remember.
Yeah, I don't remember...
By now, I've forgotten...
Suzu-nya...
Oh?
Uh, Mo— Yuki-san?
It's been a while.
My brother?
He's doing all right, I guess.
Oh, I'm glad to hear it.
I haven't heard from him at all lately,
so I wondered if he's feeling
under the weather or something.
I see... Well, if he's fine, that's good.
This is a life of fantasy,
Unaffected still by illusions.
Worldlines without end
are all deceived by an antinomy paradox
If I can dominate these emotions,
orbital ordering replacing even common sense,
Then my suffering
alone
is the gap to cross in this algorithm
I can fly high
Signs of love, words of love...
The memories flow back with total clarity
Never again will I forsake what lies beyond,
I want always to be by your side, hand-in-hand,
As this quantum entanglement forms Zero
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
I can't wait to see Maho-san.
Try not to miss her. Don't forget she's so...
Hiyajo-san.
Long time no see, you guys.
Marbled Port-Cutlet Sandwiches
Chicken & Rice
Maho-san seems to be doing well.
Yeah, apparently she came to help the Professor.
What a busy girl.
I wonder if Kagari-chan is doing well too?
Me too. I know Daru and
Suzuha were looking for her...
Yeah...
By the way, where's Hashida-san?
I guess he had something important to talk
with Suzu-nya about, so he couldn't come.
Hmm...
What the hell, Dad?!
Wh-What's that scary face for?
Put your hand on your heart and think about it.
Hand on my heart?
If you keep doing crap like that,
Mom's really gonna get taken by somebody else!
Eh? Say again? What do you mean?
I saw it...
I saw Mom talking all friendly
with some other guy.
Amane-shi was?
When's the last time you saw Mom?
Um, when I went to visit Fubuki-shi...
Since then?
Why don't you meet her more often?!
B-Because! I've been so busy
with the time leap machine and stuff...
You could find the time if you wanted to!
Sorry...
What if this keeps up and
Mom ends up marrying someone else?
Hmm... Maybe it's no big deal?
It was probably just some guy asking
for directions or trying to sell her something.
And if it wasn't?
If you're that worried about it,
why don't you just go and ask her?
How come you're not the least bit concerned?!
At this rate, I might never
end up being born in the future!
But doesn't the fact that you're here
right now mean you'll be born for sure?
Hmm?
Is that... Amane-shi from the future?!
Ooh! Loli Suzuha is lovely!
That isn't the point! Look closer!
Eh?
Why are you so faded out?
It's been like this for a while now.
—That's just like Back to the—
—Dad!
Wh-What?
You have zero confidence, Dad.
It's because you lack confidence
that instead of making the first move,
you're waiting and hoping for her to.
Am I wrong?
That's...
No future awaits those
who refuse to take action.
Eh?
That's something you
told me a long time ago, Dad.
I said all that?
But, that's—
Listen to me!
If you and Mom aren't getting along,
I might be in trouble! I mean it!
Tutturu! We're here!
Huh?
Luka-kun and Moeka-san too?
What's going on here?
Big Sis Mayu...
We're going to need your help.
Eh?
Um, so... Before their date tomorrow,
you want Daru-kun to learn
how to have confidence in himself?
I'm no good at things like that,
which is why I need everybody's help.
Did you use that photo, nya?
Big Bro!
Y-Yes?!
Our mission will now commence!
The operation objective:
Concluding their date tomorrow,
Hashida Itaru will confront Amane Yuki
and confess his feelings for her.
C-Confess?!
That's crazy talk!
That's not what I want to hear! Try again!
Suzu-sama! Yes, ma'am! Suzu-sama!
The poor girl wanted to see you so badly that
she was begging “Let me come to Japan too!”
I said no such thing.
By the way, Lintahlo... How is that report
we discussed the other day coming along?
Well, I have it right here.
Oho? You impress me.
Maho-san!
Help me!
Suzuha-san?
It's nothing special, but here it is.
Lintahlo.
Modesty isn't always a good virtue in practice.
Especially if you're hoping
to go far in America.
Sorry, I mean...
Thank you.
I'll have to put aside some time tonight
to sit back and read this report of yours.
If it's good enough, you might be
able to transfer before you know it.
Great.
And I'm sure Maho would love that too.
Professor!
Incoming Call
Mayuri
What's up?
Ah, Okarin?
Um, a bunch of us are gathered at the lab right now,
so I was wondering if you wanted to join us?
At the lab?
Yeah... Will you come?
Sorry... Maybe another time.
I see... Okay, no problem!
That's too bad. Keep it up, Okarin!
If you wanna be a popular guy, you've gotta
know all the tasty places to go, nya!
So without further ado, we'll be drilling good
restaurants and manners into your head, nya!
Faris-sama! Yes, ma'am! Faris-sama!
Yuki-san is a huge cosplayer, right?
So, I'm thinking if you wear
something different than usual,
it might make her heart flutter, you know?
Mayuri-sama! Yes, ma'am! Mayuri-sama!
To be honest, the most important thing
is to understand a woman's heart.
How do I keep the conversation
going?
Keep the conversation
fun and exciting.
How do I keep the conversation
going?
Keep the conversation
fun and exciting.
Well, Big Bro?
Feeling confident yet?
Huh? Uh, yeah...
I can't believe you had me come here for this...
You're kidding me, right?
Maho-san! Where's Okarin?
The professor made me leave without him.
Will you help us?
It's a pain for me too
if Hashida-san stays like this.
Fill me in on the details.
Actually...
In other words, he needs more
confidence dealing with women.
What's that?
For now, let's just say an experimental
system with an improvement or two.
But basically, it's something
of a sleep-learning device.
Hashida Itaru.
Believe it or not, you're a lady's man.
Not even Don Juan could compare
to your charm and success.
I-I'm a successful man...
Now...
Open your eyes.
Yuki-san.
Hashida-san?
Bring the usual.
Very well.
You come here that often?
Because I'm a successful man.
R-Right...
Was that any good?
Perfect, nya!
I don't know... Do you think it's going well?
It has to be! I know it!
Maho-nya's idea is sure paying off big time!
Well, I never thought it'd be so effective...
Wow! This is beautiful!
It is, but...
You're even more beautiful.
Thank you...
What a romantic mood!
All that's left is for Big Bro
to deliver the final blow!
Look, nya!
Um, today was—
Yuki-san.
Umm, Hashida-san?
I have something to say, Yuki-san.
Uh...
Yuki-san, will you...
Will you...
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic Line
I failed...
Dad, get a hold of yourself.
It's not like you were rejected, right?
No matter how you look at it,
she's gotta hate me, noob!
Will you...
Oh no... Look at the time...
Eh?
I need to get going.
Huh?!
I had so much fun today. Thank you.
Uh...
I knew it was pointless...
Deep down inside, she doesn't
want to be asked out by a guy like me.
But I was all cocky and misread the situation
and had the nerve to hold her hand...
Yeah, and just look at my body...
My hands are sticky and sweaty and nasty.
I bet she was thinking to herself...
Eww! Disgusting! Let go of
my hand already, you slimy pervert!
No! Mom's not that kind of person!
I knew it was too good
to be true from the start...
Think about it! Why would such a cute
girl ever decide to marry a guy like me?!
That just doesn't happen, it's common sense!
Amane-shi will end up with somebody else...
Don't say stuff like that, Dad!
But you're the one who said it was happening...
Dad...
Sorry, but I need some time alone...
Suzu-san, I'm sorry.
Big Sis Mayu...
No, this all happened
because I doctored that photo.
I went too far as well...
No...
It's not your fault...
It's my fault.
Yeah...
Just like then...
Mom! Mom!
Suzuha!
Watch out!
M-Mom?
Dad?
Could we talk maybe?
Yeah.
The future that I came from...
It wasn't such a peaceful world.
I never spent much time together with
you and Mom. There wasn't a chance to.
So...
The truth is...
I just wanted to see it.
My mom and dad who gave
birth to me, getting along together...
That way, I'd feel like
I'm heading down the right path.
I thought that'd be the proof I needed...
I'm sorry.
Her talking to some other guy
and me disappearing was a lie.
I lied to you.
Well, I kinda figured you were.
Huh?
Yeah, I knew...
Dad...
It doesn't matter if you
were lying or telling the truth.
I just... wanted someone
to give me that push on the back.
I was being selfish.
I'm the one who needs to apologize.
Dad...
Amane-shi?
Sorry about today.
Yeah, so hey...
Tomorrow, do you want
to meet up with me again?!
Yeah... Yeah, yeah.
Later.
Yuki-san
Call Completed
Dad...
I can't compete with you, Dad.
Good grief...
What the heck am
I supposed to do all on my own?
Amane-shi!
Today was lots of fun. Thank you.
Right back at you. Thanks for
hanging out with me two days in a row.
Amane-shi?
Personally, I think you're wonderful
when you act like yourself.
Uh, um...
Dad...
I-I...
I think of you and feel...
...Moe Moe Kyun!
Dad...
Thank goodness...
With this, I can...
Think we can meet today?
There's so much I want to
talk about.
Think we can meet today?
There's so much I want to talk about.
Lintahlo. Sorry to keep you.
Oh, no. It's okay.
Forgive me. Work at the hospital
has been one problem after another.
But I did look over your report.
There are a few areas that need polishing up,
but your viewpoint and ideas are interesting.
Do you have time to stay
and answer some questions about it?
Sure, that's fine with me.
Your brother cares for you very much.
Yeah... I couldn't wish for a better family.
So, my brother...
Please take good care of him.
Me too.
Itaru-san makes me
Moe Moe Kyun too, you know?
Suzuha... I'm so happy I gave birth to you...
Thank you.
H-Huh?
This is weird...
I'm... Why am I...?
It's okay. You don't have to say anything.
Aren't you going to be in it?
It's fine, it's fine!
Her and I will take plenty together from now on.
I'm taking it.
Are you sure?
If I keep bugging you two any longer,
I'll feel like a third wheel.
Shall we?
Okay.
Thank you, Mom...