Without further ado, we would
like to demonstrate said AI.
Amadeus.
The theories of researcher Makise Kurisu
served as the foundation for this system.
Please look to the screen.
My apologies.
It will take a short while
for the system to launch.
Please wait a moment.
What, is it broken?
Is it even possible to store
memories as data in the first place?
How do you think they took memory samples?
From a medical standpoint,
this is pure nonsense.
It's impossible to rewrite
digital data back into the brain.
This is completely insane.
I read the paper that was published in
Science, but I don't believe a word of it.
Especially not when the lead
author was some 17-year-old girl.
Listen here, Mister.
Objection!
How do you know it can't
be done if you've never tried it?
The world is full of technology
that people considered impossible at first!
We only have those things today because
of researchers who pushed the envelope!
Criticism like yours accomplishes nothing!
Excellent.
It is people like this bold man who we can
thank for the continual progress of science.
He may have what it takes
to become the world's third Einstein.
Tsk.
However, scientists must
always strive to remain calm.
Shouting out loud should be reserved
only for when our experiments succeed.
Thanks for your patience.
A much better interpreter will now
take my place on the screen behind me.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Ladies and Gentlemen.
I am Hiyajo Maho.
More specifically, my existence stems from
hers as of 78 hours and 22 minutes in the past.
In other words, I operate based on Hiyajo Maho's
memories from roughly four days ago.
I noticed somebody scoffing in the fifth row.
Yes, you wearing red checkers.
I can guess what you're thinking.
If I were pre-programmed ahead of time,
these sorts of responses would be nothing special.
Or perhaps...
Could the me over there be controlling
all of my actions with the computer?
But the majority of you
are probably thinking this:
That preserving memories
as data is an impossible feat.
Though, in that case...
If that were true, what does that make me?
Amadeus...
Tell you my credit card number?
I'm not telling anyone that.
What age did I stop
taking baths with my dad?
Shall I report you for sexual harassment?
No, I can't tell you what
pajamas I wore one week ago.
I don't remember.
For an AI to interact like that...
And what's more, to have emotional
responses and forget trivial information.
It's as if she's--
I'm not cut out for this sort of party.
It's you, from the reception desk...
Um...
I'm Okabe Rintaro.
You were Hiyajo, right?
It's a strange name, isn't it?
Pretty common in Okinawa though.
Uh...
Oh.
I-I brought something to wear for today.
Or had intended to...
I'm terribly sorry about earlier.
Eh?
That is, for interrupting your seminar.
Don't worry about it.
If you hadn't stood up and said something,
it would've ended up much worse.
Also, you don't need to be formal with me.
If you say so.
Your seminar today was incredible.
Perfecting AI like that is something else.
Thanks... is what I'd like to say, but...
Unfortunately, it's far from complete.
Is it really?
We have loads of issues.
For example, even if we can implant
extracted memory data inside someone,
it's pointless unless the brain can use it.
When people try to access their memories,
the signal goes from the
frontal to the temporal lobe.
Top-down memory search signals...
I'm impressed you knew!
In order for the transmitted signals
to be utilized by the temporal lobe...
And then, by sending the copied
pseudopulse to the frontal lobe...
The memory search signal will function properly.
Isn't that right?
Tell me... Did you reach
this conclusion on your own?
I-Is that odd?
One of my colleagues proposed
exactly the same theory as you.
And the thing is, she never
published that idea anywhere.
You reached the same conclusion as her,
and you're not even in neuroscience?
A coincidence?
No...
Eh?
Everything I said,
Kurisu once lectured me about.
Kurisu did? When?! Where?!
Back when she came here
as an exchange student.
We became friends and
talked about things like this.
She... was your friend?
That's right.
Sorry if it seems like I was hiding it.
No...
If anything, I'm grateful.
That you became friends with her.
Though mostly all we did was argue.
That's so like her.
She would never admit defeat,
no matter what.
Yeah...
And argue for the sake of arguing.
Even said she'd rip out
my frontal lobe sometimes.
I can imagine.
Right?
You need to discipline
your younger researchers better.
I admit, mistakes were made.
My apologies.
I'm sorry...
Weird, right? To do this out of nowhere...
No...
You two... were close?
It's not necessarily that, but...
Your nose too.
You don't have to tell me.
So this is where you've been.
Oh, it's our Mr. Einstein!
Glad you could make it to the party.
Is this some kind of Japanese lover's quarrel?
Give her an authentic Japanese bow!
No, this is--
You've got it wrong!
I cried on my own...
We were talking about Kurisu, and I just...
Kurisu?
Are you telling me that you
and Kurisu were acquaintances?
U-Uh, yeah.
I see...
So you met her when she stayed in Japan...
I'm Okabe Rintaro,
a student of Tokyo Denki University.
During the seminar...
Did you raise your voice in defense of Kurisu?
No, that was...
Actually, that might have been part of it.
In that case... Maho?
Don't you think we should introduce
Mr. Okabe to our friend? Her?
Her?
Professor! But he's an
outsider and just a student!
If he was friends with Kurisu,
he's hardly an outsider.
We should feel blessed that
they met here and embrace it.
Hold on a second.
I'm not following any of this.
Introduce me to who?
It's not a person.
He means Amadeus.
From your demonstration earlier?
That was Amadeus using my sampled data,
but I'm not the only one.
We have data for another researcher as well.
Another?
"Wako City South Gate"
Amadeus is storing Kurisu's memories too?!
Up until now, only Maho and I have
talked with her for all of our data, but...
Our conversations are running dry, you see.
What do you say?
It's best if you thought it over.
I don't know your
relationship with Kurisu, but...
The closer the two of you were,
the crueler meeting Amadeus will be for you.
The memories of her, eight months ago...
Welcome.
"Brain Science Institute"
We're planning to start a new research
organization with neuroscientists all over the world.
Right now, there's not much but the prep room.
And the professor?
It's Sunday today. He's off.
You said you want to do this... Are you sure?
You two were closer than I thought, weren't you?
The Amadeus here will talk
and sound exactly like she would.
That makes it easy to be deluded.
It's as if you're talking
to her and she's still alive.
However, the Amadeus you'll meet is constructed
from her memories that were taken in March.
She's not the girl you
became friends with, nor is she alive.
Those are the facts, as painful as they are.
Yeah...
The more you talk with Amadeus,
the more that truth will sting.
You'll realize that she's gone forever
and there's nothing you can do about it.
I know...
That's why I came...
To come to terms with that.
I see.
Go on and sit down in that chair.
Don't peek at my password, all right?
All yours.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
I came this far and now I'm getting cold feet.
It's still not too late.
Run while you still can.
That's not very nice.
I'm just looking out for you.
In that case, you could
have phrased it a little nicer.
Just like Kurisu.
You experiment-loving girls are all so...
Uh, never mind.
People spending all their time
on experiments forget how to be nice.
If I'm not mistaken,
that sounds like slander to me.
I'll sue you for defamation.
My bad. I'll get you Dk Pepper,
so cut me some slack.
So cheap.
What's so funny, Senpai?
She... was right there...
Right there... beside me.
With her voice...
With her looks...
Go ahead.
Okabe Rintaro?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Makise Kurisu.
It's a pleasure.
"Epigraph of the Closed Curve -Closed Epigraph-"
This is Okabe Rintaro.
We met after our seminar the other day.
He seemed very interested
in Amadeus, so we had him come.
Really? For you to do that,
he must be something special.
Um, Okabe?
Are you a neuroscientist as well?
His major is different,
but he's talented for sure.
Even the Professor took a liking to him.
Psst, Senpai.
Hmm?
Could you scoot closer
to the speaker for a second?
Eh?
Please, just do it!
What the heck?
Could it be that...
Huh?! You've got to be kidding me!
You don't have to be embarrassed...
Regardless, quit saying weird things!
What did she say?
None of your business!
Right!
Don't say anything stupid, got it?
We didn't invite Okabe
here to talk about nonsense like that.
The more you evade it,
the more suspicious it is.
I'll infect you with a virus!
Just kidding! I'll say no more!
Sheesh!
This is one of my problems with Amadeus.
Sorry about that.
Feel free to talk with her if you like.
Y-Yeah.
Forgive me.
Ask me about anything or everything.
I'll answer as much as I'm able.
Let's see...
Do you think one...
could build... a time machine?
A time machine, you say?
Yeah...
Hmm.
Why ask that? What's the point
of asking about time machines?
It's just a thought experiment.
Hmm.
I wonder...
My personal belief is...
that time machines are not possible.
However, that is not to say
they are impossible altogether.
My belief is that time machines...
You don't think... it's a bunch of nonsense?
It would be rather hasty to assume that.
There are a number
of time travel theories, but...
They are nothing but speculation.
All of them are unrealistic.
Even so, we might be missing that
one critical discovery to piece it all together,
don't you think?
So they're not possible yet, but...
They're not impossible altogether?
Mm-hmm!
Well?
The answer she gave was somewhat
different than when we spoke before...
Hmm...
Is it due to the differences
in the Alpha and Beta worldlines?
What awful pronunciation.
Shut your trap, Christina!
Christina?
Uh, erm... No, forget it!
But I'm curious.
It was nothing! Just drop it!
You're clearly worked up about
something. Is Christina--
Give it a break, Christina! I mean, Kurisu...
Why do you call her Christina?
Would you people get off my back?
Answer me.
Give it a rest!
No, I'm curious.
Isn't Amadeus pretty amazing, Lintahlo?
Tester?
Yes.
We want you to talk with Amadeus
from time to time so we can use it as data.
You'll be able to do so
until I return to America.
All we ask is that you come to
visit twice a month to submit a report.
I have to report?
There's no quota or anything to worry about.
You can talk to her whenever you feel
like it and give us your honest reaction.
With Kurisu...
If you're not up for it,
don't hesitate to decline.
I can understand if it's too
heartbreaking to speak with an AI
in the likeness of your deceased friend.
I...
Are you sure about this?
It's coming to the point where you and I are
running out of things to talk with her about.
Plus, I'm curious to see how Amadeus changes
interacting with someone on the outside.
I knew this was going to happen.
Did you?
Yeah...
From the moment
I found out he knew about Kurisu.
I hope we can meet again, Okabe Rintaro.
There's somebody out there
who knows a Kurisu that I don't...
Senpai? Senpai?
Shall I grab that for you?
I'm fine, I don't need any help.
It looks like you do.
Here.
Senpai?
You really need to fix
that rotten mouth of yours, Senpai.
Why?
What will you do if he hates you?
I told you to quit bringing that up.
But this might the last
chance you have in your life!
You're the one who needs
to learn some manners.
Operation?
Yup!
Daru and I thought of a big
operation to cheer up Suzu!
Eh? You guys are putting something together?
To be honest, Mayushii is a little scared
of Suzu, but she's a really nice person!
When Mayushii is half-asleep,
she sneaks over and puts a blanket over me.
And she's always helping
with Luka and the others too.
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
So we're thinking of throwing Suzu
a big Christmas party as
a present to help her cheer up!
A party, huh?
Can't come?
It's not that I can't,
but I doubt Suzuha would like that.
I bet she'd be upset I came.
I don't think that she will.
Suzu wants to patch things
up with you too, I'm sure.
You should answer it.
Mayushii will wait for you.
Sorry.
Finally decided to pick up
after ignoring my calls eight times?
Well, you see...
If you don't feel like talking,
I suppose it can't be helped.
Hmph!
It's just, with you being a tester, I thought
I'd get to chat with people more than I used to.
Yeah... Her moodiness and spunk...
Her fierce curiosity and refusal to lose...
Why aren't you saying anything?
In any case, call me whenever you feel like it.
But I'm a busy person too,
so I might not be able to answer.
Without a doubt...
It's Makise Kurisu...