Theoretically, it is possible.
However, that's just in theory.
The mental burden alone will
be colossal... to go back to 2011.
Even with the improvements that
make it possible to leap two weeks at once...
...in order to go back one year,
you'll have to time leap over 20 times.
Part way through, it'll be 48 hours.
A leap will take you just two days back.
Which means...
It'll take some 3000 time leaps...
That's an absurd amount...
You're really going?
Yeah.
I have no other choice...
...if I'm to change this world.
Looks like you're set on going.
Long time no see, Okabe Rintaro.
[Kurisu]?!
The entire time you were in a coma,
she was monitoring you day and night.
Amadeus was?
I can't exactly fight,
so it's the least I could do.
But still, for 11 whole years?
Time is irrelevant. That sort
of supervision is no work for me.
Also, she'll be your partner
for your long time leap journey.
No matter how many times you leap back...
...up until 2025, each time you wake up,
she'll be right there for you.
When you woke up this time,
you broke my terminal though.
After you wake up...
...if you tell me you came via time leap,
I'll do what I can to help.
Just say you wanna get back to 2011.
What?
Nothing, it's just...
I remembered a conversation
like this from a long time ago.
No longer... will I run.
Mayuri once said...
...it wasn't right to push everything on me.
Somewhere along the line,
her kindness became my excuse.
However...
I only stand here right
now because of everyone.
Because they were there...
Because they never gave up, I'm here.
It wasn't forced on me alone.
Because I want to carry it too.
It's everyone's future.
Ready?
Do it.
Rinascimento of Image Formation
- Return of Phoenix -
Okabe? You're awake?
Okabe, don't move so quickly.
For the past 11 years,
you've been out cold in a coma.
You shouldn't be--
Listen to me...
Hmm?
I time leaped here
from two weeks in the future.
Huh?
Time leaped...?
Curse you, five-hours-from-now me...!
Listen...
I used the time leap machine to
come here from two weeks in the future.
I met Daru and Hiyajo too.
It's now the year 2036, and I heard
all about what the world's become...
And you...
And you... You've been watching
over me for the past 11 years.
Eh? U-Uh...
I-I find it hard to believe, but...
Believe me. It's the truth.
You're really... from the future?
I need a favor.
Okabe?
Kyouma!
Sorry to worry you two.
Okabe!
Kyouma!
Okarin!
It's true, you really woke up!
Daru, Hiyajo...
Did you hear from Amadeus?
Y-Yeah.
Are you serious? To go back to 2011...
I know full well that it'll
take about 3000 time leaps.
But, you're really...?
Okarin.
Please.
I guess this means you'll be having
this same conversation over and over.
Every time you time leap...
Not only that, but he'll taste the pain
of waking from a long sleep each time.
You sure about this?
Okabe...
Lukako.
Y-Yes?
There's no such thing as a fixed future.
Never give up.
A path will open for sure.
Okabe? You're awake?
--You say, "Don't move so quickly."
--Don't move--
And that "For the past 11 years,
you've been out cold in a coma."
You...
You won't be able to
leap like you have till now.
Because two weeks before today,
you're not even here.
Where was I?
I don't know.
Two weeks ago, you were caught
by the peacekeeping squad.
It wasn't until yesterday that we
rescued you and found you in a stupor.
So... other than today
and that one day two weeks ago...
You won't be able time leap.
Doubt you'll get a chance to take
a call once you're captured either.
You can't until you're
rescued and carried here...
...and you're connected to the
monitoring terminal and Amadeus.
Sorry.
If only we were quicker by one more day
and got you out of there sooner.
We could've sent you off
with plenty of time to spare...
In that case, I'm equally at fault for not
improving the time leap machine.
The best I could do was two weeks.
336 hours isn't nearly good enough.
It's frustrating.
That's not true.
I'm actually grateful you
managed a two-week time leap.
Even Kurisu was stuck
with 48 hours as her limit.
You should be proud of yourself.
Yeah!
That's not my only worry.
If the time leap machine alters
the worldline even slightly...
...this current situation might be ruined
and you actually could end up dead.
It might change the past.
I know.
Even so, I'm going back.
I've come 11 years since 2036,
done hundreds of time leaps,
and with the help of my friends
from year after year, reached where I am.
Okarin!
I'm glad you're all right!
Yuki and...
Listen here!
You've all fought with all of your hearts,
no matter the time or place.
So please, don't give up!
The future...
...I'll show you it can be changed!
Do it!
Here we go!
Okarin!
Kyouma! We're heading
for the rendezvous point!
Hurry there, nya!
Faris...
Okabe?
Isn't the operation in progress?
Listen to me.
I time leaped here from the future.
Huh?
It might be hard for you to believe,
but there's no time.
Trust me, I need your help.
Wh-What?
Today... I end up getting caught by
the Bureau, tortured by them, and die.
What should I do?
What can I do... to escape from that fate?
We know why you get caught.
We heard it directly from you.
Okabe Rintaro dies in 2025.
Up until now, you've used that
to your advantage and lived.
If today is that day...
...the worldline convergence you've had
as your ally finally turns the tables on you.
No matter what you do...
...the worldline will converge
and you'll end up captured.
Even so...
Okabe.
Think you can give me ten minutes?
I've got a plan.
All right.
In that ten minutes...
...memorize this map with the enemy positions.
Huh? What's the meaning of this?
Typically, I'm the one navigating you to safety.
Even the concept of time,
indicated by two hands,
But if we assume this is a trap,
there's a high probability that
the fact that I'm with you
is responsible for your death.
is distorted by whoever observes it
So...
Uninstall the Amadeus app?!
Just in case, remove your radio battery too.
Knowledge bestowed by God
It might be enough to confuse them.
must have its limits, an absolute boundary
Also...
Use them as decoys?!
I refuse to--
Calm down!
It's sheer coincidence resulting from ignorance
You came here from 2036,
time leaping the entire way.
an uninvited miracle
Right?
Yeah...
For this once-locked gate
Therefore, you've witnessed
they're alive in the future.
They can't die here.
all rules are now off
B-But...!
Open the eyes
It's okay, nya, Kyouma!
As I reach out at the speed of light
the pulse of my memories
Kuu-nya filled us in.
We're all running circles around the city, nya!
leaps into unfathomable logic
Kyouma should run straight for Akiba
and get to the time leap machine, nya!
Open the eyes
Once again, the universe
hides logic without order
It's too dangerous! You can't--
Okarin!
This is where you've gotta believe in us, dude.
in which individual points
said to be comprise infinity
Daru...
borrow improper power to replay over and over
The target's marker disappeared.
They're gone from GPS.
He had to have disconnected Amadeus.
Teams 1 and 2, head for that area, pronto.
Our priority is capturing the target.
Ignore the rest of Valkyrie if needed.
0 is the past, 1 is the future
As long as Okabe Rintaro--
Target acquired!
Wait, this is...?
What's wrong?
There're multiple Okabe Rintaro markers!
Two? Three?!
They're coming up all over the place!
With countless lines running in parallel
What's that mean?!
I-I don't know!
Out of nowhere, Amadeus just popped up!
Lintahlo...
I'll no longer give up.
0 is the past, 1 is the future,
and now is nowhere
I'll no longer lie to myself.
I'll no longer pretend I made the right
choice... and I'll no longer compromise!
It's an undeniable logic
They've all been desperately battling on,
driven by the hope to change our world.
Open the eyes
With countless lines running in parallel
and choice leading to sacrilege
I'll believe in their hope.
our own existences come into doubt
Hope... will be my strength!
I'll show everyone we can reach that place!
The sceneries reflected in
your eyes all converge together
Okarin.
Uncle Okarin.
Okabe.
Kyouma!
Okarin.
Okarin!
Okabe.
I will!
Okarin?
What's going on?
Daru...
--Huh?
--Hiyajo.
Punch me!
Eh? A-Again?
--Wh-What are you talking--
--No need to hold back.
Think of all the anger
you've pent up because of me.
Your feelings for Suzuha...
Take it all and punch me with it!
What's this about?
It's deserved.
I've had my head buried in the sand.
I've been running in fear and I deserve it!
Are you really... sure?
Hashida?!
Yeah.
Do it!
Ah!
Uh...
Okabe!
Eh?
That did the trick...
--I expected no less a slug
from my favorite right arm...
--Eh?!
--I expected no less a slug
from my favorite right arm...
I... have time leaped back from the future.
Eh?
Okarin?
You're so wrong, Daru!
Huh?
That laugh!
My name is...
...Kyouma!
Kyou... ma?
Yes.
Lab Member 001!
The founder of this lab...
The seeker of chaos, the destroyer
of this world's ruling structure...
The mad scientist...
...Hououin...
...Kyouma!
O-Okabe...?
--Okarin!
--Eh?!
You, the Loli!
--Huh?
--Yes, you!
Who else here is a Loli but you?!
Bring my lab coat! At once!
--Wh-What the heck?
--Aha!
Behold my sacred, silvery armor!
The moment my hands slide through
these sleeves, I truly awake from my slumber!
Um, Hashida? What's this?
He's gone back... to the old Okarin!
Eh?
When he's nutty and nonsensical...
and has out-of-control delusions!
He's back to our leader, Okarin!
You both complete time leap machine.
--Eh?
--My being here is proof of that.
Loli!
Don't call me that!
As of today, I grant thee
the title of Lab Member 009!
You are now a hand of Hououin Kyouma
and shall aid our operations!
Hiyajo Safina.
Wh-Who the hell's that?!
As of now, I call a round table meeting!
Summon all lab mems immediately!
What's going on, nya?
Who knows...?
Um... Could you explain
why we're here today, Okabe--
It's Kyouma!
A new operation is about to commence.
For it to succeed,
all lab mems must do their part.
Where's Mayuri and Suzuha?
Moe-nya sent a message that she's busy, nya.
Uh, Shiina and--
Never fear.
It's all within expectation.
Nevertheless, the operation will continue.
--Oh! So the red star I saw
yesterday in the western sky was...
--I hereby name it... Operation Vega!
Recover Amadeus' data?
Yes, confirm if you must.
She's already left messages on @channel
and Leskinen has taken her away.
Huh? The professor? Why would he...?
It's real! The occult board got hacked!
The Organization has showed its hand
and is jamming phone signals in Akihabara.
However... Faris!
Nya?
Deploy the neighborhood
watch around Radikan!
They should spot several
suspicious foreigners in the area.
Relay us info on all of them!
We'll have to rely on pay phones!
Roger, nya!
R-Radikan?!
I know that Part-Time Warrior
and Mayuri are heading there.
W-We've gotta stop them!
Even if we stopped them, it'll likely end
the same way because of convergence.
If there's any way to stop them, yes...
Eh?
Yes, it's me.
Right... The operation has one sole objective.
To ensure Mayuri and
Suzuha are safely sent to the past.
I know... I won't repeat that mistake again.
El...
...Psy...
...Kongroo...
Mr. Braun!
Huh?
What's with you? The second
I think you're almost normal...
I don't have time to explain the details.
This phone outage is the Organization's doing.
Stratfor.... DURPA...
I seek your assistance, Mr. Ferdinand Braun.
Well?
Just like Okarin said, it's been taken away.
But if I can just find out where...
I'll leave your tea right here.
Thanks.
Don't mention it. I can't do much else...
That's not true at all.
Remember what he was saying earlier?
Lukako, I need you to
support the mechanic members.
Support?
Yes... It's a vital mission requiring
consideration and a stout heart.
I wondered why everyone was so
happy to see that Okabe back, but...
I think I see why now.
Hell yeah!
Make no mistake, I found it!
Mission complete!
Urushibara, get the word out!
Right!
You have one missed call.
Hello, Kyouma?
Hashida just found Amadeus
and should recover it shortly.
He said not to worry.
Good, with this...
Wait for me, Mayuri...
I will save you.
Suzu...
Ouch!
Stay still. That ricochet may have
just grazed you, but you're still bleeding.
Excellent!
To think she'd clean up all on her own...
The future's brainwashing
techniques sure are incredible.
You're...
You did this... to Kagari!
That's right, Valkyrie's Hashida Suzuha.
Kagari was a spy long before the
day you left on your journey with her.
That is, courtesy of the future me.
Your anger is justified, though
I don't have the time to entertain it.
I'll make it easy on you.
Soon, you won't have to think
about the bitter future or painful past.
Or perhaps... you'd like
for me to wipe clean your mind?
That's right. A little tampering
with your brain and...?
What?
Lintahlo...
Uncle Okarin?
Okarin!
How is it that you're here, Lintahlo?
Who told--
Kagari won't be coming.
Because... we've already restrained her.
You may not have realized it, but we've
taken measures around Radikan.
This is a world of unreality,
Mr. Leskinen.
You may have thought yourself as a
god who could see through everything, but...
Nothing more than an imprinted vision.
...I'm afraid to say all
your schemes have been foiled.
Lintahlo, what are you...?
The Point at Infinity
Where those values lie overwritten by this inert universe
What do you think you're--
Okarin?
Lab Member 002... Shiina Mayuri!
If God in his arrogance reigns through lightspeed unseen,
Operation Arc-light.
I time leaped to come here.
Then I alone
I know all about it.
Okarin...
In less than 30 minutes,
this place becomes a war zone.
will be the miraculous...
the fatal... minority.
Hurry!
Uncle Okarin!
I'll somehow deal with Kagari!
I can fly high
All those moments and places
If you think they're special,
Take care of Mayuri.
Okarin...
All right.
Then you shouldn't try
to leave the past behind.
Those invaluable scenes
will eclipse the heartache
With this, they should make it in time.
The time machine will vanish
to the past... following history...
As each and every light forms to yield Zero.
With this...
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
Impossible! It's too early!
Mayuri!