"Kinomoto Coffee"
"Yuzuriha"
"Pastas" "Espresso"
"Tutturu~
Where are you, Okarin?'
"Aha, the usual cafe~
Omw~"
Suzuha!
Dad...
Why in the world are you
still out in this downpour?!
It's been several months
since Kagari vanished...
We tried to track down her whereabouts
using all possible means, but...
In the end, we just couldn't locate her.
"I went back to the place again"
"Can't get in"
"Why not?"
And the facility Moeka and I found...
"File attachment"
We never found out exactly what it was for.
She was... brainwashed?
We don't have definitive proof though.
Since we can't explain Kagari's background,
we couldn't recruit any police help either.
Okarin.
Mayuri?
Will you be okay, Okarin?
Eh?
I wondered if you brought an umbrella.
The rain comes out of nowhere.
It sure has lately.
Because it's the rainy season. It happens.
True, that.
Summer's not far off...
That's true.
Summer's coming.
Yeah.
I can fly high
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
Yo, Maho. What's up?
Morning.
Huh?
Hiyajo? Are you okay?
A sleepy Maho! What a turn-on!
If you're contacting me again,
I'm guessing... You're actually serious?
Of course we are!
Like I told you before, if we end up
not being able to use the time machine,
we'll need the time leap machine for sure!
And you think it's doable?
I got it to the point before Okarin broke
it apart and threw it in the trash, but...
It's not even close to stable.
Of course not.
How did they compress an absurd amount
of memory data to be sent into the past?
Until you figure that out, it's pointless to--
That's why we're here talking to you!
We need your help.
Since we can't ask Uncle Okarin,
you're our only hope.
Don't think I can do everything
just because I'm a scientist.
Before you had Makise Kurisu.
You had the brains of that genius.
But...
I think you're a genius in your own right.
Spare me the lip service.
Well, I've got work, so...
Is that a no, then?
I'm hanging up.
Salieri can't compose the songs Mozart did...
Hmm?
Was I... talking to them looking like this?!
"Recognition of the Elastic Limit
- Presage or Recognize -"
I wonder... Do you think this is okay?
If Okarin finds out, he'll be furious.
Would you rather convince him?
Impossible! He'll scrap it as soon as he hears.
See?
But, you know...
Okarin's always looks dead
serious when he says it...
"Don't even think about changing the future."
I've gotta imagine he's got
a good reason for saying that.
True, I can understand where he's coming from.
But, is letting World War III and
this worldline happen the right choice?
I sincerely doubt it.
I'm sure Okarin would agree with you too.
In that case, why won't he take action?
He's got the time machine
he needs to find Steins Gate...
He's got the ability to remember other
worldlines through Reading Steiner...
So why has he given up?!
Why won't he at least try?!
Why?!
I don't think he's given up yet.
I think, someday Okarin's going to be
reborn and go all "Mwahahahaha!" like before.
You've been saying that for over half a year.
Well, that's...
We can't count on Uncle Okarin.
We have to do something ourselves.
Sorry... I said you could leave it to me,
and now look where we are.
No...
I know how hard you've been
pushing yourself, if only for me.
Hmm?
It's from Mayushii.
Eh?!
What's wrong?
She says Miss Fubuki is back in the hospital!
I'm going to see what's up.
Mom will be there, right? Good luck.
This is not the time to be concerned about that.
But, what if it ends up with me not being born?
I-I will not let you down!
See you later, Dad.
R-Right! I'll do my best!
Isn't that...
"AH Tokyo General Hospital"
Oh!
Ah...
Mayushii! Okarin!
Fubuki, are you all right?!
Huh?
I'm fine, I'm fine! So get this...
They just asked me to come back
to the hospital again for another exam.
And silly Kaede here...
Because Fubuki sent a message saying
she'd be in the hospital for a little while...
I said a little while, didn't I? Come on...
In other words, there's no need to worry?
Thank goodness.
Okarin! Mayushii!
Daru?
You came too!
Yo, what's up.
Hashida.
Oh?
Good evening.
Huh? U-Um...
H-Hello.
Huh? Didn't Miss Fubuki collapse?
Jeez, not you too!
And why does everyone
need their own private room?
I'm telling you, it's a necessity.
That's what you keep saying,
but I don't think it's possible.
Then find a way to make it happen!
Professor Leskinen?
It's been a while.
Lintahlo!
Wait, don't!
Professor? You know this man?
Yes! He's the world's third Einstein.
Lintahlo here will be transferring
to my university in September,
and I'll eventually have him
join my research team.
At Viktor Chondria University?
Well, no. That is my ultimate goal, but...
Mayushii, Mayushii.
Okarin's transferring overseas?
Even so, the fact that you're able
to study overseas is impressive!
Keep up the good work!
I don't think it's set in stone yet,
but Okarin's doing his best to study!
I will. Thank you.
I see...
Huh? The hospital director?
You lied to someone that important?
I didn't lie to anyone, Lintahlo.
Though I might have told him September...
I didn't say of which year.
Is Hiyajo here too?
Curious, are we?
Uh, well, I guess...
Unfortunately, she's back in America.
However, I will tell her that
you were asking about her.
Take care now.
Honestly, the only
reasonable assumption is that
they sent the memory data
somewhere to be compressed.
Considering the places she's
affiliated with capable of that...
But, make one wrong move
and you'd be disgracing the dead.
One wrong move and
this will turn out nearly the same.
"One new message"
"Professor Leskinen"
Professor?
Eh? Okabe?
What the heck?
Did something happen?
Oh, that's right. The professor's in Japan now.
I guess he must've ran into Okabe.
Wish you were there?
Why would I?!
U-Um, your eyes are bloodshot.
Lack of sleep.
Still, he's such a weird guy, isn't he?
Why's that?
I thought so from the very beginning.
For starters, the first thing he asked was
if time machines could be built or not.
Do you think one...
could build... a time machine?
Senpai?
Hey, you have Makise Kurisu's
memories from spring of last year
before she went off to Japan, right?
I do, but... Why ask that all of a sudden?
What if... Suppose if...
If you found out a way to make a time machine...
A time machine?
And everything needed to make it was
right in front of you, what would you do?
That's a silly question.
Isn't it obvious?
However...
The one who makes it all possible says this...
"Time machines are the work of the devil.
They must never be made."
I see...
I might just hesitate...
After all, who knows what happens
when you interfere with the past?
What would even become of us in the present?
We haven't the slightest idea.
You're right.
Though...
Even so, I would put it together.
Using it or not would be the tough choice.
She dropped this half a year ago?
No, that can't be...
She came... here.
"Miss Fubuki is A-OK"
"Good to hear
And how about Mom?"
"Coming home"
I think I'll go rinse myself off.
Don't move.
If you try anything funny, I'll shoot.
Put your hands on your head.
And slowly walk toward the door.
Stop.
It's so hot and yet you
can stand wearing that outfit.
Why don't you take off that helmet of yours?
K...
Kagari?
I hear the voice of God...
K-Kagari?
Where is it?
The precious gift... Mommy gave me.
Kagari...
You have it, don't you?
Give it back!
It's hard to believe you're the same girl
who was always bawling in the time machine.
I'm surprised.
Big Sis Mayu... was crying, you know.
Mommy... was?
Now behave yourself.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Big Sis...
It hurts! You're hurting me!
Big Sis! It hurts!
Suzuha, what's up?
You left the door wide open...
Eh?
Dad, watch out!
Kagari!
Go ahead and hurt my Dad if you dare.
I don't care who you are...
I will kill you!
Kagari!
Just now... that was Kagari... wasn't it?
Yeah...
Why would Kagari...
Did you see, Suzuha?
Eh?
I think... she was crying.
Ouch...
I-I'm sorry.
Don't you think you should go to the hospital?
I'm fine. I just got grazed.
To think the woman in
the motorcycle suit was Kagari...
It wasn't.
The person that attacked
you guys was somebody else.
When it happened,
Kagari would've been at the shrine.
Then...
I think... Uncle Okarin's
guess was right in the end.
Kagari was brainwashed and
is being controlled by somebody.
Brainwashed, though? By who?
12 years ago...
Somebody must've found out Kagari came
here by time machine and captured her...
What's wrong?
I hear the voice of God...
I hear... a voice...
The voice... of God?
Eh?
It can't be... At that point,
Kagari was already...?
Um...
I'll get a hold of Okarin and
let him know that Kagari showed up.
Uncle Okarin...
If he hears that Kagari is back, he'll probably
go searching for her like crazy again.
But, as you just found out,
Kagari is far too dangerous right now.
Besides, if it is brainwashing,
I might have a hunch or two about Kagari.
Probably, in order to save her...
In order to save Kagari,
we'll have to use the time machine.
I'm such an idiot! Why did it
take me so long to remember?!
He tormented my Valkyrie
comrades one after another!
The Bureau's...
...Professor!
Suzuha...
Dad?
I'm gonna try asking Maho again.
Huh?
To come here, and seriously get to work
developing the time leap machine with me.
Don't you worry.
I'll do whatever it takes to get
it finished, no matter what!
To Japan?
We can't do anything without your help.
It's to save the world.
Plus if you come, I get to see loli
Maho in summer clothes! Huff huff!
Pure-white one piece and high socks, yummy!
Dad!
Ah, sorry. My vivid imagination
got the best of me.
But seriously now, without you, I'll never
be able to restore the PhoneWave.
You really intend to fix it?
I'll say it again.
We need your help.
Will you at least let me think about it?
I never pried into the details...
But, Makise Kurisu and Okabe Rintaro
must have, in some other worldline,
gone through trial and error over and over.
And somehow, they successfully manipulated time.
She succeeded.
Makise Kurisu built that machine.
Can you believe it? To get a paper
published at such a young age...
It's magnificent! Your talent is the real deal.
Now that the world has acknowledged you,
I imagine work will get very busy for us.
I just wanted to open it.
To prove I could see inside.
To show I could do that much.
But, make one wrong move
and you'd be disgracing the dead.
I wonder... What should I even do?
What's the matter, Senpai?
Something troubling you?
If you're fine with me, I could lend an ear.
Thanks.
Senpai?
--Kurisu! Help me find something! An old magazine!
--Huh?
Huh? Um... Okay!
That and...
I can find my way there all on my own.
Not by searching through
your work for all the answers.
But by going down that same path...
and reaching it myself.
And so, I will head back there again.
To the city where Makise Kurisu's life ended.
The reason itself is
hard to put into words, but,
I think, if I had to give an answer...
There was one person who acknowledged
Mozart's talent above anyone else...
It was Salieri.