Hey, Suzuha! Is lovely, my daughter, there?!
What's this about “lovely, my daughter”?
It means you're my beloved daughter.
That's not what I'm talking about!
What? You having problems?
No, don't ask.
If you know too many details,
I told you it'll cause a time paradox, so...
You can have this back too.
Damn... Y-You found it.
Nice try at a disguise, but you'll
have to do better than that.
Well...
If I don't have this, how the hell do I
figure out how to build that in the future?
No cheating.
You can do it. If you couldn't,
I wouldn't be here.
Made up your mind?
Yeah...
I see...
The problem for me is,
I'm too happy being here in this era.
It makes me want to stay here forever.
I know that dream can't come true,
but I find myself thinking that.
Who's there?!
Mayushii?
What's up?
Suzu...
Did something happen?
You came here from the future, didn't you?
Everyone knows about the future but me...
Big Sis Mayu...
I want you to tell me...
about Mayushii... and Makise Kurisu...
This is a life of fantasy,
Unaffected still by illusions.
Worldlines without end
are all deceived by an antinomy paradox
If I can dominate these emotions,
orbital ordering replacing even common sense,
Then my suffering
alone
is the gap to cross in this algorithm
I can fly high
Signs of love, words of love...
The memories flow back with total clarity
Never again will I forsake what lies beyond,
I want always to be by your side, hand-in-hand,
As this quantum entanglement forms Zero
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
Hope you like Okinawan Tea.
Where'd Daru go?
We don't have snacks,
so he went out to buy some for tea.
That's good, right? Talks like this
are usually better with less people.
You're going to sit in on it too?
Yes, I'm a scientist.
I might be able to help
give a logical explanation.
So... Maho knows too.
I have a rough idea from what
the three of them told me.
Before that, I need to ask you...
Why do you want to know now, all of a sudden?
That's...
Up until now, I was afraid
of knowing the future.
But...
But?
Yesterday, I ran into Okarin... Okarin said...
Don't think about anything...
That things were fine...
But, Okarin seemed incredibly sad...
Ever since last year he's been very, very sad...
So that's how it is...
The thing is, I don't think hearing will
solve anything. Uncle Okarin is...
I know that, but...
Even so, I want to hear.
If I never hear for myself,
I know I'll regret it someday.
All right. Just so you know, none of us carry
our memories over from other worldlines.
At best, I can only put together
what Uncle Okarin's told me.
Did Makise Kurisu...?
Did Makise Kurisu sacrifice
herself to save Mayushii's life?
I don't know if sacrifice is
the word to be using or not.
However, it's clear there were
at least two worldlines.
Makise Kurisu lives and Big Sis Mayu
loses her life in the Alpha worldlines.
And... Makise Kurisu loses her life and Big Sis
Mayu keeps living in the Beta worldlines.
Here, the worldline that we're in
right now is a Beta worldline.
Is that all there is?
Are those two worldlines all there is?
There is more.
Rather, I want to believe that there is.
The Steins Gate worldline definitely exists.
Steins Gate?
A world where neither of you lose your lives,
and the conflict over time machines
that starts WWIII never occurs.
Dad in the future told me about it.
It's the unknown worldline
we're trying to reach.
Uncle Okarin lived the same summer
over and over trying to find the way there.
He thought there had to be
a way to save both of you.
But...
So... It's all because Mayushii
stopped him that time...
It's not your fault, Big Sis Mayu.
Honestly, Uncle Okarin was
a total wreck back then.
He has an ability to remember all
worldlines called Reading Steiner.
Because of that, he retains his memories
of many people across many worldlines.
The feelings they tried to hide...
Things they never achieved...
The fear of suddenly losing
those who should exist...
Just retaining those memories is
plenty enough to damage the heart.
Which is why, back then, I'm actually
grateful that you stopped him.
But, if Mayushii hadn't
stopped him, Okarin would...
Okarin...
That's just like how Big Sis Mayu
was in the future too.
You stared sadly up at the sky and said...
That day, if my Hikoboshi had come back
to life, it might have changed everything.
Sorry to keep 'ya!
You sure took your time.
Where did you even go?
I splurged a bit. Ginza, baby.
And why's that? Is it someone's birthday?
As a farewell.
Farewell?
Check it out. I got the
shortcakes you love so much.
Getting two was easy-peasy.
D-Don't say I love them, okay?
By farewell, you don't mean...
Yup... I decided to go today.
If I keep dawdling, I'll end up not able to reach
last year's July 28th when Makise Kurisu died.
Last year's...
You don't have enough fuel to come back, right?
Think you'll succeed?
I don't know.
That's why I wanted to get
the time leap machine all ready.
So we can try as much as needed.
Suzu, you're going back to the past?
What will happen when you do?
Who knows?
I won't be coming back here, that's for sure.
Worldline convergence might mean an
irregularity like me is straightened out.
Straightened out?
Suzu, wait! You can't go! Don't!
Suzu! Daru!
Suzuha... Go get 'em.
Okey-dokey!
Thanks for the cake.
Daru...
Well... Commence mission!
Are you fine with this?
That's right... You're Suzu's
father, aren't you?
I don't like this! You have to stop her!
I'm... not stopping her.
“Think we can meet today?
There's so much I want to talk about.”
“Sorry about yesterday.”
Okarin?
Mayuri?
Hello?
Suzu is... Suzu's in trouble!
Suzuha is?
Yeah! She's heading to the time machine
to go one year in the past...
She's leaving, but she can't come back!
Why did you...?
Huh?
Why did you have to go talk about it?
You tried to find out! I told you!
It's better that you don't know.
The time we have is—
What's wrong?
“No Signal”
This whole past year...
I always kept thinking to myself...
Why did the me 25 years from now
send Suzuha back to this era?
I think I wanted her to see it...
This world...
That's what helped me make up my mind.
To finish my duty like Suzuha set out to...
To do the things only I can do...
What things?
Twenty-five years from now, this dude
makes humanity's very first time machine.
But I... What can Mayushii do?
I want to help, but I can't do anything...
You're the one who got Okarin
back on his feet. Isn't that enough?
That day...
Hmm?
If my Hikoboshi had come back to life...
...it might have changed everything.
That's...
Mayushii's Hikoboshi was...
...ever since then, so very alone.
This past year, he's been missing something...
And I want him to find it...
I want him to be himself again...
I want it so bad I could cry...
I wish it so much, I could scream...
I... I love Okarin.
Probably just as much as Kurisu did.
No, that's wrong...
Much more... Enough that Kurisu
could never compare.
I love him that much!
But...
But... I love Hououin Kyouma even more!
When I felt like disappearing forever,
he said I had to stay in this world.
I... I want to see Hououin Kyouma again!
I want to hear that arrogant laugh of his again!
Even if that means I can never be Orihime.
Even so...
For me, there's only one Hikoboshi!
It's Okabe Rintaro, and nobody else!
In that case...
If that's Mayushii's choice, then...
you know what you've gotta do.
Mmm.
Mmm!
Daru... Maho...
For today only,
Mayushii will stop being a hostage!
“Altair of the Hyperbolic Plane
- Beltrami Pseudosphere -”
“Taito Chuo Chiyoda Bunkyo Shinjuku Minato”
What's going on? All the carriers are out...
Today is double sevens day!
Orihime will greet you in a miniskirt!
Mayuri!
O-Okabe?
Daru! Where's Mayuri?!
Eh? U-Uh, that's...
The phone's aren't working!
Why not?!
I've been looking it up, but it seems like
there's a disruption in the Akihabara area
that hasn't been fixed yet.
The net works, right?
Y-Yeah... But it must be covered-up or something
'cuz none of the sites are talking about it.
And, well... I connected to @channel,
but the occult board got hacked or something.
Hacked?!
“Attention Salieri's Neighbor (1000)”
This post is...
“It appears that we twins will be
temporarily driven from the place we belong.”
“002 KuriGohan and Kamehameha”
“It appears that we twins will be temporarily
driven from the place we belong. Which is why we may not be able to come back here anymore.”
“003 KuriGohan and Kamehameha”
“Our Father and God has at last discovered
how to unveil our most sacred domains. Furthermore, we are ‘good’ children who cannot lie to our Father.”
how to unveil our most sacred domains.”
“004 KuriGohan and Kamehameha”
“Thus, we may tell Father the secrets of
manipulating time and where they're at. I deeply regret not being able to hold onto them tighter.”
“005 KuriGohan and Kamehameha”
“I thought we could become good friends
with you, but I think this is goodbye. So, please convey this message to the one I respect most.”
“Thus, we may tell Father the secrets of
manipulating time and where they're at.”
“006 KuriGohan and Kamehameha”
“I always considered myself to be
the very definition of mediocre. However, you were the person I always strove to be, and you... You are the true Amadeus.”
Our Father and God?
Yeah... Look!
“Please convey this message
to the one I respect most.”
“I always considered myself to be
the very definition of mediocre.
“However, you were the person
I always strove to be, and you...
“You are the true Amadeus.”
Any idea who did this?
Without a doubt. Amadeus [Kurisu] wrote this.
Seriously?
Can you try to access Amadeus?!
Y-Yeah...
What's this mean?
What?!
All the data is completely missing!
“Driven from the place we belong”...
Just like she said!
Then, the secrets of manipulating time
and where they're at means...
It can't be! Kurisu's memories?!
Impossible! They broke the protection
on Amadeus' deep memory data?!
Y-You don't think...
Does that mean someone knows about
the time machine existing now?!
Y-You're kidding...
Daru? What is it?
O-Okarin!
Mayuri and Suzuha are?!
Suzuha went to change the future alone...
and Mayushii went after her.
“Suzuha”
“Daru”
“Lukako”
“Calling”
“Mayuri”
“Connect—”
“Hang up”     “Redial”
Mayuri!
Is it hopeless, as long as the time machine
exists?! Will it keep happening?!
Let's get to work, C203.
Suzu!
Don't try to stop me, I...
No...
I'm coming too. Take me along.
To August 21st of last year.
August?
Yeah...
To when Okarin and Suzu time traveled...
I want to go right after that.
If it's not that moment, there's no point.
And you're that confident?
Mmm.
We can't come back, you know.
Are you fine with that?
I can't pretend my Hikoboshi never found me...
I can't pretend the future me
isn't filled with regret.
All right.
Mayuri!
Where do you think you're going?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Why did it come to this?!
I came to terms with how it ended this way!
Why?! Why did it come to this?!
If you come any closer, I'll shoot.
Mayuri, you don't have to do anything!
Don't go and ruin it!
If you do, all the sacrifices
everyone made will be for nothing!
Kurisu's death will be for nothing!
I can't... I can't let that—
Okarin!
He's fine. It just grazed him.
I can't...
I... I...
Okarin...
Even so!
Even so...
Let's not pretend some things never happened.
Mayuri...
Even when it rains, it's not like
the stars disappear from the world.
Past the rain clouds,
they're still shining brightly.
That's why I... I'll push away the
rain clouds that loom over your sky.
Mayuri...
You just wait.
Mayuri!
Are you sure about this?
Mmm.
Sorry.
The blood's already stopped, so don't worry.
What do you intend to do?
I've said it plenty. Finish my mission.
I'm going to change the future
for all the people I love.
Though I do have my doubts...
Uncle Okarin...
Goodbye.
“One new message”
“Open”        “OK”
From Dad?
“From: Barrel Titor”
“To: Amane Suzuha”
“Subject: Operation Arc-light” “(No body)” “Movie file”
A D-Mail from 2025?
Yo, Suzuha. It's your dad.
It's the year 2025 here.
Dad...
If this video mail reached you, it means you...
rather, you and Mayushii discovered
another path to Steins Gate.
You may not realize it, but the two of your
choices altered the worldline slightly.
The worldline?
In other words, I'm not from the worldline you
left from, but a Hashida Itaru from another world.
However, my love for my daughter
will ever be the same.
Moving on to the point of this video mail...
Now for the details of Operation Arc-light.
Big Sis Mayu!
Put down your gun and get on the ground!
Suzu!
Keep quiet. If you scream,
they'll probably just shoot you.
I'm a girl, you know. Be a little considerate.
Targets 2 and 3 secured.
Target 1 secured.
However, there's a lock on it.
Biometrics, huh?
Stand.
Fine.
Suzu...
If you try anything, I'll shoot.
I know.
It's on. We're good!
Big Sis Mayu, run!
Big Sis Mayu...
K-Kagari?