“Ongoing Terrorist Attack in the City”
“Public Safety Warning”
We'll now take you to our coverage
of the terrorist attacks taking
place in the heart of the city.
It's like a scene out of war here.
The entire front of the station and
Chuo Dori has been closed off completely.
Are the attacks still ongoing at the moment?
We don't know for sure at the moment,
but sources tell us additional
terrorists may be lying in ambush.
The government is urging all 23 wards to
remain indoors until the situation is under control.
This is a life of fantasy,
Unaffected still by illusions.
Worldlines without end
are all deceived by an antinomy paradox
If I can dominate these emotions,
orbital ordering replacing even common sense,
Then my suffering
alone
is the gap to cross in this algorithm
I can fly high
Signs of love, words of love...
The memories flow back with total clarity
Never again will I forsake what lies beyond,
I want always to be by your side, hand-in-hand,
As this quantum entanglement forms Zero
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
The Tokyo Disaster Response
Department continues to urge—
This is seriously happening, right?
Yeah...
Suzuha and Mayushii are...
Is it possible they managed
to jump into the past?
Hadn't the time machine started up?
You saw it too, Hiyajo.
Did you really not finish
the time leap machine yet?
Unfortunately...
We might still have time!
Hurry up and finish it!
The time leap machine
can jump back up to 48 hours!
Going two days back puts us at—
But how?!
If I could do it, I would've long ago...
Makise Kurisu might have done it, but I can't.
Makise Kurisu might have known how,
but I don't! It's the truth!
I get how much we need it, but I...
Don't give up! This is—
Enough with the bullshit!
Daru...
Maho was giving it her best shot,
especially knowing that Suzuha
was trying to change the future!
But you're the one who was against it, Okarin!
And yet, now we shouldn't give up?!
You should've said so from the start!
That way, Mayushii would be...
Suzuha would be...
Hold on!
Let's all calm down...
This is no time for
the three of us to be arguing.
Okabe.
I want you to tell me what Kurisu was working
with when she made the time leap machine.
What did she need? How did she
end up sending the memory data?
Hiyajo...
Honestly, that's the
one question I didn't want to ask.
I wanted to do it on my own, but...
It's no time for that anymore.
We hacked SERN.
SERN?
Yeah. We hacked into SERN,
used the LHC to make a micro black hole,
and compressed the
memory data to 36 bytes.
For real?
That might actually be possible...
It's easy to say, but actually doing it?
Daru should be able to.
Can you?
Well, I am a super hacker.
The problem is, the microwave
doesn't seem anywhere stable enough.
It's the 42-inch CRT.
Only when it's turned on will the
PhoneWave (name subject to change) work.
But why would a CRT...
The electron gun?!
That's the solution we discovered with Kurisu.
Okabe?
There's something I need to verify.
If something comes up, call me straight away.
I'm pretty sure that
signal interference is gone now.
Where do you think he's going?
We don't have time to find out.
We're going to need help.
Hey!
What's the meaning of all this?
You were going on about
America and Russia before, weren't you?
What's happening?
It's too late to do anything now, so...
I'll ensure it doesn't come to this.
H-Hey!
What's wrong, Dad?
Nae...
Nothing.
World War III...
It's not like I didn't believe
all the things Suzuha told me...
But, it felt like something so far off
in the distance, it didn't seem real.
But it's...
No injured or dead civilians
were found in the wreckage.
Ugh...
Well?
Just a little more. No...
Hopefully a little more.
What are they trying to do?
I don't really know either,
but our pals need refreshments
if they're going all out, nya!
Right.
Okabe?
Okarin, nya!
You guys came?
When trouble's going down in Akiba,
I won't just sit back and watch, nya!
I asked Moe-nya to keep an eye out
and say if anything else happens, nya!
I feel like the lab was packed with
more people... More lively and fun...
Sweet!
Broke in!
Really?
I haven't actually hacked anything yet, but...
At this rate, might take till morning.
I see.
So? Where did you go?
Radikan.
Suzuha and Mayuri's bodies were never found.
What's that mean?
It means we're not certain
they actually died, that's what.
I see...
Is there a problem?
No...
Once we hack our way in,
the time leap machine will essentially be done.
Right.
But even if it's complete,
we won't be able to verify it works
without someone testing it.
Yeah, we were hesitant about using it
back when Kurisu completed it too.
Fortunately, it worked according to theory.
That's only because it was Kurisu.
But I...
You're not confident in
the things you make yourself?
Of course not.
Why not?
Because I'm not Kurisu. I'm no Mozart.
Please convey this message
to the one I respect most.
I always considered myself
to be the very definition of mediocre.
However, you were the person
I always strove to be, and you...
You are the true Amadeus.
That's...
Her final message.
Remember her post on @channel?
There's no saying she meant me, okay?
Wrong. I was referring to you, Senpai.
Kurisu?
Here. Right here.
You're all right?
Yeah. The professor froze my data temporarily,
but before I knew it, I was here.
Did Daru...?!
Huh?
When he found out Amadeus' data
was moved, he was searching for it...
All while hacking SERN?
For Daru, it's a walk in the park.
I'm sure he wanted to help you out too.
Aren't you a popular girl?
You. Shut. Up.
You can do it. I know you can.
You don't even know what we're trying to do.
Nevertheless, I know you can do it, Senpai.
Believe me when I say it.
I'm Kurisu's memories
turned into data, and I say so.
Kurisu?
No... Sorry, I must have fallen asleep.
I'm not surprised,
considering you've been working
nonstop since the day before yesterday.
Well?
It's done... or, should be.
Are you really using it?
Yeah.
Even though you hated it so much?
I made a promise to her.
To protect this worldline.
Because... her sacrifice meant
everyone else could be saved.
But now that I see that's not true...
Makise Kurisu must
have meant so much to you.
Loved by God, huh?
In the end, she's the true Amadeus.
Soon, I will use PhoneWave (name subject to change) Unit-02 and time leap.
I thank the tireless dedication of my comrades
and their will to always keep fighting.
Amadeus.
What is it now?
You saved us all.
Eh?
Back then, if not for your message,
we never would have made it in time.
Huh? But in the end you ended up
helping me out, and I'm just a system anyways.
Even so.
[Kurisu].
Wh-What?
Thank you.
You too are a worthy member of our lab.
E-Enough already, just go!
Embarrassed, are we?
I'm not embarrassed!
I will never give up.
Tens, dozens, hundreds of times I could fail...
A thousand, ten thousand,
millions of times maybe, but I will save them.
Suzuha, Mayuri, and Kagari too.
This is the first step.
Altair of the Cyclic Coordinate
- Time-leap Machine -
Did it... work?
“2011/07/07 (Thu)”
July 7th... 3 o'clock?
I should still have time!
Okarin...
What's going on?
Quick!
We've gotta hack into
Professor Leskinen's computer...
...find Kurisu and Hiyajo's Amadeus data...
...and delete it all, plus backups!
Huh?
What are you even talking about?
It's the spark that ignites World War III!
—Eh?!
—Also, in case we need it,
finish the time leap machine!
Hold on!
Okarin, don't tell me...
Yeah, I came from the future.
Using that same time leap machine.
Using this? It got finished? But how?
I don't have time to explain right now.
This whole area is about
to become a war zone.
War zone? What are you—
As proof of that, all of Akiba
is about to lose phone signal!
Anyways, you two gotta
use the wired network
to find out where
Amadeus' data was hidden!
Whatever you do, don't go
near the Radikan.
Radikan? That's...
I already know Suzuha and
Mayuri are heading there now.
You're really... from the future?
When you and Daru left last time,
you got captured.
So please, just don't leave
the lab until I come back!
Okarin...
W-War?
I find it hard to believe, but...
“Unable to access.”
“Please verify network connection.”
What hour and
what minute did it all happen?
When did Mayuri and Suzuha
get to Radikan?
I don't know the exact times.
It feels just like then...
Where reality seems like part of
a dream, repeating over and over...
This vague, ominous feeling...
It should be a dream when in fact,
it's real and actually happening.
It's like living in a nightmare
where I know all the bad things to come.
Where the world enjoys to rub
in the guilt of my unspeakable sin.
This inescapable despair...
Slowly becomes a downward spiral...
Mayuri!
Okarin...
Wait! Don't go!
If you come any closer, I'll shoot.
Suzu...
I'm sorry, but we don't
have time for this. Get in.
I came from the future!
48 hours in the future!
So I know what's going to happen!
In less than an hour,
this place turns into a war zone!
War zone?
Yeah. America's Stratfo finds out
about the time machine
and comes barging in, then...
The time machine gets destroyed!
You're just making stuff up.
Right now,
you're thinking if I get any closer,
you'll shoot a bullet that grazes my left leg.
You actually did shoot me, so I know.
In that case...
In that case, no time to spare!
We've gotta go!
If we get delayed and they show up,
we won't be able to go back to the past!
It has to be now!
Go back and do what?
Operation Arc-light.
August 21st.
Go back to the day Uncle Okarin gave up and
convince him to search for Steins Gate again.
That's what Big Sis Mayu wants.
Mayuri does?
Yeah, so let us go.
Mayushii is a lab member too.
And since my Hikoboshi is down
in the dumps, I'll give him a good old slap.
That's why I've decided to go.
“Dear Okarin.
Tutturu! It's Mayushii!”
I... love Hououin Kyouma.
But, guess what?
“I wish to meet my Hikoboshi”
“Mayushii”
I love Okabe Rintaro even more!
Okarin...
All right.
Hurry! If you leave now, you can make it!
Kagari?
It can't be! It's too early for her to be here!
Get in!
Kagari, it's me!
Uncle Okarin!
Get in the time machine!
But...!
I'll handle this myself!
All right!
I'm counting on you,
Lab Member 002, Shiina Mayuri!
Make Operation Arc-light a success!
Right!
Hurry up!
Hurry! Hurry!
I hear the voice of God...
Kagari?!
Professor Reyes?!
DURPA?
Hurry up.
We're all set!
Fire.
Stop...
Stop it!
Why?
Why... did this...?
But why?
Is the time machine blowing up a convergence?
So that no matter how many times...
No matter what I do to try and avert it...
Just like back then...
It's like a scene out of war.
The station has been closed off completely.
Okabe! What happened?!
Some serious shit is going down.
What about Suzuha and Mayushii?
No matter what...
Okarin!
No matter what, I have to!
You're really time leaping again?
Yeah...
I made up my mind.
No matter how many dozens or hundreds
of times I fail, I will save everyone.
Okabe...
I'm sorry if I make you do
this time and time again.
When you go back, tell me that my future
self promised to help as long as it takes.
I've heard something like
that before, from Kurisu actually.
That sounds like something she'd say.
Mayuri... Suzuha... Kagari...
An end like this, I will never allow.
I will never allow it!
Leap!
Vibration unreachable emotion
Hello Amadeus, I'm waiting for your call
This place, as if all is layered
Is a multitude, The world in the world
Time is irreversible,
and yet those unknown sectors
Fly past flash-forward, why? Vision of a kiss
So incredibly close, an outrageous distance
Overlapping logos,
infinite 0 or 1, I'm right here
Tell you my feelings I keep inside,
through solitude I carried them
Innumerable infinite universes
Which is why, just for now,
for your tomorrow, for your sake
Please, don't repeat the
desecration of the celestial God
There is inside world-line
There is inside world-layer