Kagari-chan?
Kagari-chan!
Mommy?
How are you feeling?
Is my treatment for today all done?
Yup! You did great today!
Such a good girl!
And for the good girl Kagari-chan,
I have some special news!
News?
Yup!
All of the paperwork is finally out of the way.
I'm sorry that it took so long,
but starting today...
...I get to be your real mommy!
We can live together now!
Mommy!
Sheesh! You're such a spoiled one, Kagari-chan!
♪ There's just one thing I'm searching for... ♪
♪ The laughter of the stars. ♪
What song is that?
Hmm?
I'm glad you asked.
It's a very precious song to me.
Precious?
That's right!
It's all thanks to this song that Mommy
and Kagari-chan were able to meet.
Really?
Yup! That's why you should give it
your best and try to memorize it too!
Because someday, you'll meet
somebody precious to you too.
I want to learn that song too!
Teach me Mommy's precious song!
Okay! Should we sing it together?
Yeah!
♪ There's just one thing I'm searching for... ♪
Yup! Good, good!
♪ The laughter of the stars... ♪
♪ Twinkling in the wind... ♪
Mother Goose
of Mutual
Recursion
♪ Twinkling in the wind... ♪
This is a world of unreality,
Nothing more than an imprinted vision.
The Point at Infinity
Where those values lie overwritten by this inert universe
If God in his arrogance reigns through lightspeed unseen,
Then I alone
will be the miraculous...
the fatal... minority.
I can fly high
If that moment, if that place was
something you thought was special to you
All those moments and places
If you think they're special,
Those invaluable scenes
will eclipse the heartache
As each and every light forms to yield Zero.
There is no God. Wonderful new world.
Okabe-kun!
Professor Izaki?
I must say, that report of yours
was pretty darn impressive!
Th-Thank you.
Weren't you thinking about studying abroad?
Y-Yeah, tentatively...
To be honest, you had me worried,
but based on your work as of late,
you might just pull it off.
Keep it the good work.
I-I will! Thank you!
Hey, Kagari-san? Want some
Juicy Chicken Number One?
—It's Mayushii's favorite food ever!
—Oh!
—You don't mind?
—Hmm...
—Nope! It's super tasty,
so I wanted you to try some too!
—Hmm, hmm...
Thank you. I think I will.
You're very welcome!
Want some, Daru-kun?
Date
The best spot to take your date
things that we recommend
Sure, I'll eat some.
Akihabara Picks
All right! Gimme just a minute!
♪ There's just one thing I'm searching for... ♪
♪ The laughter of the stars... ♪
♪ Twinkling in— ♪
Huh?
That song... I know it.
Kagari-san?
Eh?
Long ago... Somewhere...
Somewhere...
Kagari-san?
Eh? Whoa!
Kagari-san! Hang in there!
Kagari-san!
Mayuri! How's Kagari?!
Okarin!
You said she collapsed again?
Right now, she's sleeping.
Suzuha...
Can I have a word?
It's been a while.
Yeah...
Just so you know, I'm...
...not aiming to reach Steins Gate.
Eh?
I can tell without you saying.
Sorry.
I wonder if they'll ever come back?
Huh?
Kagari's memories.
Right...
But the girl's a war orphan.
Never knew her parents' faces...
Had nothing but painful memories, I'm sure.
But, her meeting Big Sis Mayu
changed her life forever.
Because of Big Sis Mayu,
she finally learned how to smile.
When she ran away from me...
...she pointed a gun at me.
Saying if the worldline changed,
she couldn't meet Mommy anymore.
She was just 10 years old...
She might get her memories back,
or she might not.
But for her, I wonder which
is the happier outcome?
If her memory does come back,
she might remember something about the
people who attacked her, so there's always that.
Either way, I plan to do all that
I can do, and that hasn't changed.
Take care of Kagari, all right?
♪ There's just one thing I'm searching for... ♪
—♪ The laughter of the stars... ♪
—Mommy? Mommy!
Mommy!
—Huh?
—Eh?
U-Uh, um...
Did it... happen again?
You all right?
Yeah...
Mayuri left just a bit ago.
Guess they didn't have enough people
to cover the lunchtime rush.
Mayu-shi was worried sick about you.
I see...
Feel a little better now?
I heard a song.
And then, my head just...
A song?
You've heard that song before?
Yes.
It's not one you heard lately?
It's not, I don't think.
A song...
What do you think, Okarin?
You never know. It might be a hint that
leads to getting your memories back.
Really?
If it's not too hard on you,
it's something we could look into.
Oh, it's fine with me.
I'm okay now.
Hey, how was your checkup?
I'm as healthy as I've always been.
It's been half a month, for crying out loud!
Okarin-san doesn't have to keep
going in for checkups, so why do I?!
You should be happy to have no problems.
But I do have problems!
I put on fat during my hospital stay
and it just won't come off!
Hey, what do you say we hit up some karaoke?
Uh, sorry but...
I kinda have plans after this.
Ah, shoot! I need to hurry!
We'll do karaoke another time.
Yuki-san, in front of—
Ouch!
Jeez, I can't believe how clumsy she is!
For real.
Kagari-san! Are you better now?!
Yes, I'm sorry to have worried you.
No, Mayushii is sorry for not
being able to stay at your side!
A song?
Yes, it's that song you were singing earlier.
I feel like I've heard it somewhere.
Do you remember where you learned it from?
It's possible that song is a hint
to get Kagari's memories back.
Um, let's see...
Mayushii first heard that song from Suzu-san!
From Suzuha?
Yup! I sometimes hear Suzu-san singing
that song while looking out the window.
So unfortunately, Mayushii doesn't
know the name of the song.
Maybe it's a song that's popular in the future?
Sorry I couldn't be of any help.
No, thank you for telling us.
Hey, Okarin? Are you planning to visit Suzu-san?
Hmm? Yeah, to check with her.
Can Mayushii come too?
Really? Are you sure?
You see, it's hard to explain, but...
When I look at Kagari-san,
Mayushii just wants to do everything I can to help!
So, please?
Mayuri-san...
What about work?
The peak has passed, so it's fine, nya!
Anyways, I'll give Suzuha a ring.
She might be working.
If that was the case,
she should be on lunch break.
I passed Suzu-nya outside a bit ago.
Really?
Hmm? Suzu-nya?
Big Sis Rumi?
What's with the scary-looking face?
Well, it's...
I'm about to head into battle.
Battle?
That's what she said, nya.
Don't tell me...
Recruiting Warriors!
Monster Plate!!
Eating Contest!!
Recruiting Warriors!
Monster Plate!!
Eating Contest!!
Go Go Curry
Incredible... Can you believe it?
This month's eating contest winner is...
Our first three-time winner,
The Silent Slaughterer!
And I'm not even stuffed yet.
Huh?
Eat what you can when you can.
It's an important rule to live by
for survival on the battlefield.
You had me worried there.
Aw, man...
Can't believe you heard me singing.
It's very cute of you!
Please spare me, Big Sis Mayu.
Do you remember where
you heard that song, Suzuha?
Mo—
I mean, Yuki-san was singing it.
Yuki-san was?
If you heard it from Yuki-san,
you mean in the future?
Yeah... Mom was always singing
when she cooked our meals.
So, it's possible that Kagari learned
it from you or Yuki-san too?
Not possible.
Kagari was adopted by
Big Sis Mayu only after Mom died.
I never sang in front of Kagari either.
Kagari from Mayuri... Mayuri from Suzuha...
Suzuha learned it from Yuki-san...
This is just like the telephone game...
No good?
Yeah, maybe Yuki-san is working.
Oh well. We'll just have
to wait until she calls back.
Um, Okabe-san?
—Over there...
—Hmm?
Hey, it's Yuki-san!
Wait... She's together with... Daru?!
Ooh!
There's some sauce on the side of your mouth.
Eh?
I-I'll wipe it myself!
D-Don't try cleaning my disgusting face
or it'll ruin your handkerchief!
I got it. Hold still, okay?
It's not disgusting at all.
Hey, hey! Are they on a date?!
It's a date!
So those two are seeing each other?
That rascal, saying he had somewhere to be...
What to do, Okarin?
Well, we can't get in their way.
We'll ask later. Is that okay, Kagari?
Yes, though...
Hmm?
Ah...
We're sorry for intruding...
Don't be. Like they say, the more the merrier.
Right?
Yeah, sure...
So, about that song...
Well you see, I sometimes help out
teaching at a baking class.
Hmm?
Yuki-san makes the most
delicious sweets you'll ever have!
Yeah?
Should we make some together next time?
Yes, of course!
H-Hold on.
What does that have to do with the song?
One of the students that comes
to our class is always singing it.
They sing that song?
Yeah.
Before long, it got stuck in my head.
And that person who
sang it is someone we know?
I'm not so sure. I'd say they're
some 20 years older than us.
Not seeming very likely then.
That's right. I thought
it'd be easier just to ask.
Sure, I'll put him on.
Eh?
Hello?
Uh, sorry about this.
This is Okabe, a friend of Amane-san's.
Okabe?
Right. To be honest,
I just wanted to ask about that song.
That voice... Is that you, Rintaro?
—Huh?
—It's me! Me!
That voice! It can't be!
Excuse me? Don't tell me you forgot
the beautiful voice of your own mother.
I can't believe the lady turned
out to be your mother...
In class, we all just use
everyone's first names.
Well? What did your mother have to say?
That's...
Okabe Green Grocer
From you!
Eh?
I'm telling you, you're the one who sang it!
I-I did?!
What are you talking about?
I don't even know the song!
Remember? Back when you were in middle school
and Mayuri-chan was down in the dumps?
It was around the time
you started acting all weird.
Uh, what was it again?
I'm a macho psychologist!
Stop it.
Anyways, that's what you used
to sing all the time in the bath.
I did?
Akemi
End call
That's right! And because of you,
I can't forget it!
Um, what exactly does this mean?
I don't know.
I can't recall ever singing
that song in the first place.
Have you heard him sing it, Mayuri-san?
Mayushii doesn't remember that either.
We're all stuck in the same spot as Kagari now.
Um, did I hear that right about
Mayuri-san being down in the dumps?
Well, stuff happened.
Hey, Okarin. Do you think we should go?
Go? You mean there?
Yeah. You never know!
Maybe you'll remember something!
Grandma will be so happy
you came to visit, Okarin.
We're going to see your grandma?
Yup! And I'll introduce you
to her too, Kagari-san!
And tell her you're Mayushii's beloved friend!
Mayuri-san...
This is...
Well, Okarin? Do you remember anything?
No...
I see...
You'll talk to your grandma, right?
Oh, right!
Sorry. I'll only be a minute.
It's been a while, Grandma.
Guess what? I made a
new friend named Kagari-san!
—This is like a ritual for her.
—But the thing is, Kagari-san has amnesia.
—A ritual?
To lose all your memories of the past,
that has to be so sad...
I wonder if she'll get them back?
It'd be nice if they came back...
Whoa! Mayuri, it's raining! Let's take cover!
It sure came pouring down...
We're totally drenched!
We should've brought umbrellas.
I know! We can go to Mayushii's house and—
Kagari-san?
This is...
Mommy...
Kagari-san?
This is...
Kagari?
Kagari!
I miss you!
I miss you, Mommy!
Mommy!
Kagari-san?
M-Mommy?
Thank goodness! You finally woke up!
Mommy...
Kagari?
Mommy!
There's just one thing I'm searching for...
Huh? Huh?!
I missed you, Mommy!
The laughter of the stars
M-Mayushii isn't a mommy.
No... Mommy is mommy.
Twinkling in the wind
The mommy I love so much!
Mommy Mayuri!
You can grab it if you reach out your hand
Did her memories actually come back?
I finally found you!
Finally!
Fish swim about
U-Um...
Enveloped by the gentle rain
It's okay.
I've always wished to bring my cheek
It's all right now.
Mommy!
Closer to your warm, broad back
Just close your eyes
And surely you'll see
A guiding light to save a lost one like you
Just listen carefully
And surely you'll hear
A song to gently awaken a slumbering one like you
I've always, always
Always, always
Been by your side...
And forever...
I will always, always
Always, always
Be by your side...
To protect the smile of a gentle one like you
♪ There's just one thing I'm searching for... ♪
—♪ The— ♪
—U-Um...
Uh, um...
That was beautiful just now...
That song.
It's Mommy's.
Huh?
The song of the mommy I love.
Runaway K-6205.
Shiina Kagari has been found.