Are you sure this is the place?
CosplayMedia@Akihabara♪
We’re open!
Come on in!
Without a doubt.
But this is the first time I’ve been here too.
They said they see us. We’re to enter
near the maid uniform on the right.
It’s like a secret passage.
This must be it.
KEEP IT CLEAN
Daru?! What are you doing here?
That’s my line, dude.
To think you’re the one who was analyzing it...
And that Maho-tan made the request...
Even I never saw it coming!
Could you please stop adding “-tan”?
It feels insulting to me.
channel
Why? It’s so cute!
So much for keeping
this part-time job a secret...
I had no idea you did stuff like this too.
Is that it?
Yeah. When I booted it up, it surprised me too.
This is Makise-shi’s computer, isn’t it?
This world is a false reality
It’s merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn’t merely something that’s expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
Pandora of Forgotten Existence
So, you two were in contact this whole time
without knowing who each other were?
I had heard about a computer guru
I could trust who did analysis on the side.
Except, they wouldn’t meet face-to-face.
What did you expect?
But when I checked out the computer,
I guessed it might be from her.
So, is it analyzed?
Not yet. If I get like three more days...
Abort it. Right now.
Huh? What do you mean?
Inside that computer may
sleep something so terrible,
it’ll bring the entire world to its knees!
Nice chuunibyou, bro!
I-I’m not kidding! I’m serious!
This concerns Suzuha too!
Suzuha?
Yeah! You should know! If the time machine...
Never mind...
Something you can’t talk
about with me around, huh?
Sorry...
All right.
I should probably leave then.
When you’re done, come get me.
Okarin, shouldn’t you just tell her?
But...
You don’t want her to know that badly?
It’s not that...
But, if I tell Hiyajo-san, she’ll...
Time machine...
And they’re most likely
after any trace of her research.
Possibly, that theory of hers is inside Amadeus.
Because I... Kurisu...
All done?
No... I’m thinking I’ll tell you about
that which has and will happen.
You sure?
Yeah.
At this rate, it’s unfair to you.
But, you have to promise me one thing.
Hmm?
Don’t say to save Makise Kurisu.
Don’t even think it!
Okarin says something urgent
came up so he can’t make it.
I see...
Yeah... We talked about eating
with everyone if he had time for it, but...
Kagari-san, you really like
that commercial, don’t you?
Huh? Yeah...
Clear Kouhi! Now with
50% less sugar! On sale now!
50% Less!
Kouhi
50% Less Sugar
No way...
So, you don’t believe it?
It’s less that I don’t believe it
and more that it boggles my mind.
The theory is one thing,
but you made a real time machine.
Making an actual one is still some ways off.
What we completed was the PhoneWave (name subject to change)
that sends mails to the past
and the time leap machine.
That’s similar enough.
No matter the method, to think you’ve
successfully manipulated the past...
The time machine...
The fact that Suzuha-san is here
means it must be somewhere, right?
And what if you knew?
Eh?
That’s...
That’s why you said not
to think about saving Kurisu!
Yeah... The past cannot be...
Rather, time must never be manipulated. Never.
But, if we somehow saved Kurisu,
this situation wouldn’t—
I told you, it’s not that easy!
When you change the past, all assumptions
you had of it go right out the window!
It can take away someone’s joy and success,
and sometimes it’ll strip the
world of their existence altogether!
No way...
The thing is...
Countries and organizations would do
anything to get their hands on a power like that.
It’s more fearsome than any weapon ever made,
which is why we must eliminate that possibility.
Without even seeing what’s inside?
The mere possibility
it exists is enough to spark war.
People will die.
By then, it’ll be too late.
But, this is proof that Kurisu once lived.
It’s her legacy...
But, make one wrong move
and you’d be disgracing the dead.
No! That’s not my intention!
I know!
Even so, I’m saying we can’t deny
the possibility of it happening.
What will you do?
I understand.
Let’s destroy this PC.
Hiyajo-san...
Seriously?
What about my payment?
I already preordered an eroge
coming out at the end of this month...
You’re despicable.
Why?
Who dares ruin our important conversation?
That’s...!
What? They already tracked us down?
Okey-dokey.
Abandon ship.
You two make a run for it.
Run for it?
They’re already inside!
Quiet, or they’ll hear you.
This way.
I can’t believe it’s come to this...
That was one of my favorite hideouts too!
Where are we?
Behind that last building.
If we got this far...
Hiyajo-san!
Do exactly as I say.
Wait! You’re after this, right?!
Start by letting her go!
We’ll trade you for her.
Don’t! You can’t hand it over!
Hiyajo-san, don’t put up a fight.
It’s no bluff. You’ll really die if you resist.
But...
This computer...
It’s so secure that hackers all over the
world threw in the towel trying to crack it.
And if you do hurt her,
you’ll never know what’s inside!
Why believe you?
It’s your choice.
Let her go and I’ll hand it over.
Once the three of us are guaranteed safe,
I’ll tell you the password.
The world line hasn’t changed...
In other words, Daru and I can’t die here.
In that case...
Don’t trust me?
I’ll be your hostage, so just let her free.
Okabe-san...
Well?
Let her go first!
Get down!
Nearby residents reported possible gunfire
to the police, and upon further investigation—
Gunfire in Akihabara
Are you okay, Hiyajo-san?
Yeah, but are you sure about
not going to the hospital?
They’ll ask how I got hurt. Besides...
Open your hand.
Eh?
Huh? That’s weird... It won’t open.
Huh?
This is... Kurisu’s...
When did I...?
I’m sorry...
Hiyajo-san.
I’m sorry.
I couldn’t... protect it.
I’m sorry...
I’m sorry, Kurisu...
Are you sure you’re okay, nya?
Yeah, the blood stopped anyways.
Where’s Daru-nyan at?
He’s heading to other hideaways.
Said he has to give
his work buddies a heads up.
Did you... want this?
Let’s disinfect you,
even if the blood stopped, nya.
There’s medicine and bandages in the box.
I knew it was different.
In this world line, SERN and the
Rounders aren’t involved in any of this.
Which means...
Mr. Braun thought it was America.
So, either DURPA or Stratfoc.
And then...
The Russians came and opened fire.
Maho-nyan sure is taking her time in there.
I... still can’t believe it.
Huh?
Th-This is bad...
The sudden shift of tension to relaxation
made my muscles go completely limp!
Maho-nyan! How’s the bath?
Nya! What’s wrong, nya?!
Faris-san!
Oh-no, nya! It’s Maho-nyan!
Maho-nyan’s dying, nya!
—Gotta hurry and carry you to bed!
—Wait! This isn’t—
What do you—
Hey, uh! Faris-san!
I’m sorry.
It’s okay. I know it’s not
your fault in the first place.
But, at least forget what you saw.
I’ll do my best.
In times like this, just say that you will.
Otherwise, you’ll get an electrode
stabbed into your hippocampus.
She said that over there too?
Only when she was fed up dealing
with blockheaded professors.
I could see that happening.
They were petrified.
Thought she might snap
and do it for real someday.
I’m gonna go.
You shouldn’t be limp for much longer,
so try to get some sleep.
Okay.
Later.
Okabe-san?
It wouldn’t be a bother if I asked
you to stay longer, would it?
I’ll leave when you fall asleep,
so get some rest.
Sorry for making you do this.
No... After all that happened today,
anyone would feel scared.
I guess that’s true.
Do you think Salieri was glad to find out?
Or did he have regrets?
When Mozart died...
Hiyajo-san...
You warned me against disgracing the dead.
When you said that, I realized something.
That maybe I had.
After she died and I acquired her computer...
I told myself it was her will.
That Kurisu wanted this.
That I had to carry on her legacy.
That I had to pass it on.
But...
In that moment,
I realized I was just frustrated.
I just wanted to open it.
To prove I could see inside.
To show I could do that much.
So you obsessed over it?
I think so.
It’s like part of me wanted to break in
and find out the secrets she hid, just because.
Deep down...
I wonder...
It’s true.
Mozart never wasted a second
concerning himself with Salieri.
He devoted himself to
making great music, and that’s it.
But, Hiyajo-san... In the end,
you agreed to destroy the computer.
That’s because you—
Plus, you shed tears for her.
Saying you couldn’t protect it,
and that you’re sorry.
Doesn’t that prove where
your true feelings were?
You think too highly of me. I’m not...
Otherwise, you wouldn’t have held
onto a piece of her computer so tight.
At least, that’s what I think.
Looks like you’re fine now. You’ll have
trouble sleeping with me here, so I’ll leave.
If you need anything, just shout.
Hey...
After you made the
time leap machine with Kurisu,
you repeated the same
period over and over, right?
Yeah...
Were you and Kurisu...
No, forget it.
Good night.
Maho! You poor girl!
Professor! You’re choking me!
You’re choking me!
Professor! I’m dying! Dying!
Thanks for sending us off,
Lintahlo and everyone from the lab.
By the way, when do you think
you’ll come to our lab, Lintahlo?
Huh? You mean...
The professor is seriously planning
to invite you to Viktor Chondria University.
Me?!
It’d be a shame to let the young
Japanese Einstein slip away!
We’re counting on you, Lintahlo.
Right! I’ll study hard and make sure I get in!
You’re okay with this?
Yup! If Okarin wants to go there,
Mayushii is all for it!
Yuki-san? What happened to your hand?
Silly me nicked myself with a knife.
Want me... to carry that?
I appreciate it!
What about Suzuha-san?
Well, she’s not totally buying it, but...
Now that Kurisu’s computer is gone, we’ve
avoided the clash between America and Russia.
Possibly, but that doesn’t mean
World War III itself is avoided.
Is that okay?
I’ve done everything that I can for now.
You don’t have to worry about it.
Planning a date together, perhaps?
Would you give it a rest?!
Anyways, this means we’ll be revoking
Lintahlo’s access rights to Amadeus.
Won’t you be saying goodbye to her at least?
You’re right. I’ll make it quick.
What?
I thought I’d say goodbye.
Did you say goodbye to Maho-senpai yet?
He sure did.
Th-Then I guess it’s okay.
How many times is it now
that I’ve said goodbye to you?
Huh?
Nah, it’s nothing.
Well, I suppose I’m grateful
you spent time talking to me.
You might be coming to study with us, right?
I’ll try to remember you until we meet again.
What a tsundere.
Huh?! Wh-What’s that?!
Your face is all red.
[Kurisu] is such a shy one!
Professor, it’s time.
Oho, is it?
Don’t tease Hiyajo-san too much, okay?
I know that.
See you.
Someday...
Eh?
Someday, I hope you can laugh
from the bottom of your heart.
See you.
Okabe-san?
Thanks for everything.
You saved my life.
That’s a stretch.
No, it’s true.
I’m extremely grateful.
I’ll be waiting for you over there.
And so, Professor Leskinen
and Hiyajo-san return to America.
Time again moves on...
Without anything changing...
Without repeating...
It moves on.
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
’Cause you’re free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now, it’s time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just a part of its plan
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
The last game