We’re almost to Nerima Garrison!
Keep it up!
They spotted us! Run!
In any case, we’re glad to secure
you alive and well, Okabe-kun.
This is...
Where exactly is this?
Where are my friends at?
Go ahead.
Was that... a dream?
It has to be. There’s no reason
for worldlines to change anymore...
This world is a false reality
It’s merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn’t merely something that’s expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
Hey, are you okay?
This... This feeling...
Was that Reading Steiner?!
Hiyajo-san, where are we?
Huh? We’re on the roof of your lab, silly.
You left during the Christmas party to—
Huh? Wait!
Okabe-san!
Please, no! Please, no!
Mayuri!
Welcome back, Okarin!
When Maho-san gets back,
we can start the present exchange.
Solitude
of the
Mournful
T
ransmigration
Wha?!
Unbelievable...
Hmm?
Pervert.
I’m not.
I got this during the present exchange.
In that case, give it to Maho-senpai.
Have her wear it for you.
That’s sexual harassment, you know.
You think? It might make
her surprisingly happy.
You’re not... angry at me?
Hmm?
Back on the roof,
I hung up on you while we were talking.
Yeah, but you called me
back right after it happened.
Did you forget?
I... called back?
I have no recollection of that...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That was a call from America,
but their signal must have been rather poor.
It took longer than expected.
My apologies for keeping you
here this late in the night, Lintahlo.
It’s fine.
Drawing Crayons
And you even let us join in on your party.
Your crayons are very cute, Professor.
Mm-hmm!
What’s that?
It’s the present I got from Shiina-san.
What present did you end up with, Lintahlo?
Uh... Um, I—
There’s no reason to hide it.
Sh-Shut up!
I’m hanging up.
Looks like you and her
are quite friendly now, eh?
By her tone, she’s really opened up to you.
I’d say our expectations and
hopes may really come true, Maho.
Hopes?
He’s referring to love.
The professor is putting all of his hopes
in that she’ll develop feelings for you.
Love?
But she’s... AI, right?
Amadeus is a system that
preserves a person’s memories
and strives to recreate
a model of their very own brain.
In other words...
The process and framework are the same...
Even Amadeus should be able to love.
No, definitely. At least,
that’s what I’m hoping for.
Granted...
Even if it came to that, Amadeus
could never truly be a real girlfriend.
It’s as if Maho is holding
a grudge or something.
You must have got along pretty well.
Eh?
Otherwise, there’s no way Amadeus would
have warmed up to you in such short a time.
How close were you two?
Were you lovers or something? Yeah, right.
No... I bumped into her at a seminar.
You told me that before.
Is that really all there is to it?
Sorry, I just...
I wanted to know about that side of her...
The side I never knew...
Of Kurisu?
I feel like I know nothing.
And here I thought for a long time I knew her…
I don’t even know
her favorite words or numbers...
I know nothing...
Nothing...
Thanks for staying till the end, everybody!
Then, since we’re done
cleaning and everything,
who says we stop by
MayQueen for some tea, nya?
Right now?
But the city is swarming with scoundrels!
Who cares? Nothing will
stand in the way of us girls.
Us girls?
But he’s a dude!
Oh, sorry.
I can’t because there’s a
guest coming to stay at our house.
Huh? Really? Even though it’s Christmas?
Yes, it’s some guest of my father’s...
He wants me to be there too.
Sorry, Mayuri-chan.
Don’t be!
It’s been a while since everyone came
to the lab! Mayushii had so much fun!
Speaking of which, where is Hashida-san?
Daru-kun said he had to talk
with Suzu-san about something.
He said it was family talk or something.
I wasn’t sure what to expect when I heard
it was sheep fur, but it’s surprisingly warm.
Don’t you like it?
Now you can invite Mom.
I-Invite?!
Yup.
Watching the two of you is painful.
You barely even talked to her today.
Uh...
I can’t be a stud like “Normies Must Die”
and talk her up with so many people watching...
So? What did you want to talk about?
You didn’t leave with the others for a reason.
Yeah...
Something’s been on my mind for a while now.
Suzuha... I want you to look me
in the eyes and tell the truth.
What are you up to?
Up to?
Lately, you haven’t been
around the lab or Radio Kaikan much.
What have you been doing?
Nothing...
Whenever you say it’s nothing,
it’s definitely something.
You can tell me anything.
I’m searching for a person.
A person?
A girl came with me in
the time machine from the future.
Eh?
Except, we got split up.
In Akihabara, 1998.
She said that?
Mm-hmm.
And the girl was 10 years old
when they separated?
That puts her at 22 if she’s alive.
She can’t keep looking forever,
but whenever she time traveled,
she picked up the search again.
She was just about to give up when she
stumbled across a picture circulating on the net.
She said the girl was
wearing something like this.
And she’s been looking for her on her own?
What’s the girl’s name?
She told you, right?
Yeah...
Shiina Kagari.
Shiina?!
Are you serious?!
Yup.
Mayu-shi’s daughter.
Wh-Who’s the father?!
No, no...
She’s not her real child.
She was a war orphan
that Mayu-shi adopted in the future.
So that’s how it is...
According to what Suzuha says,
the peacekeeping squads in 2036 are after Mayu-shi
and me for trying to develop a time machine.
Dad!
Forget about us!
The peacekeepers are close! You have to hurry!
Suzu-chan!
Please, take Kagari.
Big Sis Mayu...
All right.
No! If Mommy won’t come, I don’t want to!
Mommy! Mommy!
It’ll be okay, Kagari-chan.
No!
You’ll have Suzu-chan with you.
I want to be with Mommy!
Mommy! Mommy!
After that, she went from 1975
to 1998 before coming to 2010.
And that’s where they got split up.
Hmm...
Hey, Okarin...
Think you can help with the search?
I know it’s not right to ask—
All right.
Really?
World War III...
A war orphan...
And Mayuri’s daughter,
even though she’s adopted...
Which means in 25 years,
she’s still just as kind.
Exactly... what was that anyways?
If that was actually a worldline change...
Then somebody has made something
similar to the PhoneWave...
Or perhaps...
The Government of Japan
is reaching out to Russia,
The exiled Dr. Nakabachi
Japan-Russia Cabinet Meeting
where Dr. Nakabachi defected last August—
Tokyo Denki University
Need something?
No... I just wanted to hear your opinion.
Is that a bother?
Not really.
Talking with you is a good thing for me.
So? What is it?
Can you think of any good methods to
locate a missing person from 12 years ago?
Hmm, tell me the details.
Uh, well...
I’ve got no info to speak of.
That makes it hard to think of a method...
The best thing would be to ask the police.
Yeah, probably...
That face of yours says you can’t.
You could look at newspapers
or hire a detective.
In America, I’ve heard
they use dowsing and clairvoyance...
If you want to get on one of those crazy
TV shows, the professor might be able to help.
It was just an idea.
Makise Kurisu is dead.
Sorry, I need to hang up.
Oh, okay...
The Y2K problem?
On Sale!
Did you study it?
At the institution.
It was never made public, but the main
problem was this computer, the IBN 5100.
That’s why I’m using this patch program to
make sure the Y2K problem doesn’t happen.
But if we came from the future,
is it okay to do that?
Won’t that change the future we came from?
It’s something we must do to reach Steins Gate.
We came here to change the future.
Change the future?
That’s right.
We can’t let a world like that exist.
It’s all for that.
You can’t...
You can’t do something like that.
I hear... a voice...
Kagari!
Oh, Suzuha.
Well?
I searched through the missing
persons data the police had, but...
Nothing promising came up.
At first glance,
you’d think this world is peaceful.
Metro Police Department
Unidentified Persons Database (Female)
But there’s a surprising number
of missing and unidentified people.
Yeah...
By the way, you talked to Uncle Okarin about it?
Yeah, he said he would do what he could.
I see...
I’ll have to thank him next time.
I think Okarin would like that.
Well? Ignoring me again?
I was in the library.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, I shouldn’t have said that.
I apologize. I’m sorry.
It’s not that big of a deal.
I can’t think that way.
I hate not admitting when I’m in the wrong.
But why the library anyways?
Oh... I was checking out back issues
of newspapers from 12 years ago.
Looking for that missing person?
That’s right.
Hmm...
Would you like me to search?
Huh? You can do that?
Yeah.
The base of Amadeus resides on a server in
the Viktor Chondria University research building.
I’m free to use the research computers
and network for whatever I please.
Need me to look up
information online? Piece of cake.
But, should you be doing stuff like that?
Well...
I-It’s fine if no one finds out!
Besides, you’re not doing anything bad, right?
Of course not.
In that case, I’ll leave the decision up to you.
What will it be?
Let me think on it for a while.
Nya, nya! I spot a Kyo—
I mean, Okarin!
What’s this? Now here’s an interesting pairing.
Luka-nyan’s dad asked if we could go out
and pick up a few things, nya.
One of his guests that came over
is going to be staying with us.
We’re stocking up.
Yeah?
Looks heavy. Need a hand?
Uh, no. I’ll be fine.
Even I can handle this much.
I’ve been sword-swinging every day!
We’re on a task that’s a little awkward
to ask Kyo— Okarin to do anyways, nya.
In times like this, leave it to Faris, nya!
I see...
Hey, didn’t you two grow up around here?
—Nya?
—Huh?
A missing girl?
I’ll have to ask Kuroki about that, nya.
Please do.
That’s over ten years ago...
I’ll ask my father!
Great, thanks.
We should get going, nya.
Right.
Kyouma!
If you’re ever in need or in trouble,
don’t make a gloomy face!
Come talk to Faris, nya!
I see... So, no leads on your end.
Sorry, nya.
No, sorry to ask it of you.
Oh, but I heard about a ghost with twin tails.
A ghost?
It’s some sort of urban legend
that popped up every few years.
All around the Radio Kaikan,
people were spooked by the ghost of a girl
with twin-tails asking if they’d seen a little girl.
Professor Leskinen?
I’m telling you, it’s fine
to stop searching... but thanks.
No... Sure there’s no clues to go off,
but isn’t it too early to give up?
What’s up?
Oh, Okarin.
I don’t want to burden
you guys any more than I have.
In the first place, Kagari is my responsibility.
Don’t be stupid!
A child’s responsibility is also their parent’s responsibility, noob!
Dad...
How was that?
Sounded like a real dad, if I say so myself.
This is when you jump on me
and say, “Papa, I love you!”
Putting that aside...
When in trouble, call in the experts.
If we’re looking for someone, we might
as well bring in a specialist, you know?
I’m against it.
The fewer people that know, the better.
Did you have someone in mind, Daru?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Don’t you underestimate me.
I may be an otaku,
but I know more people than you think.
In any case, I already contacted somebody.
Bam!
Speak of the devil!
Said they can come right over if we want.
Dad!
Just leave this to Daru.
Okay! They’re already close,
so they’ll stop by in a jiffy.
That was fast.
Better than being too slow.
Lukako?
Hello?
Um, Okabe-san?
Sorry, do you have a minute?
What is it?
U-Um...
Actually, I really need to ask your advice.
Are you able to meet me now?
Right now?
Yes...
Uh, someone is kinda
on their way here already.
Can it wait till tonight?
Unfortunately, that won’t work for me...
Sorry, I’ll have to call you later.
Hold on! I’ll open the door!
I got your message...
I’m Kiryu Moeka...
Can I come in?
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
’Cause you’re free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now, it’s time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just a part of its plan
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
The last game