So this is where you’ve been, Big Sis Mayu.
Suzu-chan...
Dad and the others are looking for you.
They said they’re about
to kick off the operation.
Big Sis Mayu?
What if?
What if back then...
...had I reached out this hand...
...would this future be any different?
That day, if my Hikoboshi had come back
to life, it might have changed everything.
What if back then...
...had I reached out this hand...
Christmas
Sale
You are passing down,
sinking through your past...
Deeper...
As you go even deeper, you then see a light.
What color is that light?
Red...
Within that light stands
someone important to you.
Is that person your family?
No...
Then a friend, or perhaps lover?
We’re not even friends...
She and I are...
Ah! Okarin!
What gives? I said you
didn’t have to wait for me.
How was it?
Uh, well...
Turns out hypnotherapy
wasn’t that big of a deal.
He said I’ll be fine.
Really?
Yeah, but I’ll need to keep up
the counseling for a while.
You were right. I’m glad I gave it a shot.
That’s a relief.
Lately, you seemed to be having it rough.
Sorry to worry you.
It’s okay.
Wanna go grab a bite?
My treat.
In that case, can we head over to Akiba?
Luka-kun and Faris-chan
invited me out a bit ago.
Akihabara, huh?
That a no?
No, let’s go.
Wonderful!
I’ll let those guys know we’re coming.
Faris-chan? Guess what?
It’s already December...
It feels like that summer...
...was just days ago.
Um, they said they’d be
waiting here somewhere... Oh!
Luka-kun! Faris-chan!
Tutturu!
Hello, Mayuri-chan.
Oh! It’s Kyouma!
It’s been a while, Lukako, Faris.
Okabe-san...
Kyouma! I missed you, nya!
Hey! Cut it out!
What for, meow?
Kyouma knows he likes it, meow!
First off, quit with the calling me Kyouma.
Nyan? Why?
That’s from the Dark Past.
Is that what you call the dark ages
kept secret by a cult of medieval wizards?!
Not even close.
It’s so good to see you again.
I go to the lab from time to time,
but never see you there.
I’ve been busy with things.
Don’t tell me you’re part
of a secret organization!
No, I’m swamped with college seminars.
Nya?
Plus, club and stuff.
Nya nya?
Okabe-san is in a club?
Researching UFOs and
mythical creatures and stuff?
No, the tennis club.
What?!
’Cuz my associate professor
at college advises the club.
So now you’re doing tennis.
Look out Wimbledon, here he comes.
So, practice is why you’ve been so busy?
N-No, it’s not exactly that intensive.
Then what else are you doing, meow?
If you must know, g-group dates and stuff.
Group...
...dates?!
What?!
Okabe-san is going on group dates?!
How could you?! That hurts! That’s pathetic!
You disgust me, mister! Disgust me!
What’s gotten into you?
Don’t be so mean, guys.
I’m a normal college student, you know.
You’re lewd! So lewd!
Explain yourself, Kyouma!
How could you, Okabe-san?
—Erm...
—A message from Yuki-san!
Something happen?
No...
She said if I’m around Akiba, she
wants to meet up and show me something.
At the lab.
It’s fine.
Let’s go.
Braun Tube Workshop
Grr...
This calls for war!
Commence trolling!
“Normies Must Die-P”
wasn’t our comrade after all!
You’ve been married to “Parthenon,” you fake!
Dad...
Whoa! @channel and Twipo
are already filled with flaming!
I’m late to the show! How could I miss this?!
Listen to me, or else.
S-Suzuha! Stop it or daddy will get angry.
I’m already plenty angry with you.
Right, sorry...
For crying out loud...
All you ever do around here is nap,
play games, and browse the net all day.
But researching time machines
takes it all out of me.
Plus, we’ve got one already,
but you won’t let me touch it.
Because it’s one you invented in the future.
If you saw it now, it’s possible
that might cause a time paradox.
Since it’s guaranteed that I make it, who cares?
Means I can procrastinate now!
I’m telling you, it’s time
you worked on it seriously.
Mom always gets mad at you in
the future for saying stuff like that.
I’d welcome her wrath if
you know what I mean. Huff huff...
Dad!
Please forget I said that.
There’s something you always said in the future.
That this worldline was
the worst one imaginable...
...but having me was the
best thing that ever happened.
I came here to convince Uncle Okarin so
that we could somehow change that future.
And yet, ever since that day,
he hasn’t come back here once.
Someone’s here.
Huh? Could it be Okarin?
No, I hear boots.
It’s Mom.
Eh?!
Suzuha, hide!
Okey-dokey!
Come on in.
Hello!
A-Amane-shi? What brings you here?
Hmm? Mayuri-chan isn’t around?
Mayu-shi? Not yet...
I think I got here a bit early.
She said she would meet up with me here.
Yeah?
Mind if I wait inside?
S-Sure...
Thank you.
Um, is little sister out in town today?
Huh? Little sister? Whose?
Whose? Yours...
Mine? All my little sisters
exist only in 2D form—
Ah! Y-You must mean Suzuha!
Who else would I mean?
Uh, well... Nobody?
Tutturu!
Mayuri-chan!
Tutturu, Yuki-san!
Nyan nyan!
Faris-san and Luka-san came too!
Faris-tan!
Huh? Ah...
This place hasn’t changed a bit.
Okarin!
Can I come in?
New strain of encephalitis
No cases have yet to be reported in Japan.
...hallucinations and memory problems,
prompting the Ministry of
Health to urge caution when traveling.
I-It’s your own lab, so you don’t have to ask.
I suppose so.
Continuing with the news...
Oh! Your clothes are so cute, Yuki-san!
Earlier, Russia experienced
a magnitude 6 earthquake.
I wanted to show you
’cuz I knew you would say that.
Let Faris see it too!
We’ve got Dr P to drink if you—
Wait, Okarin! Where are you going?
Where? Just to the toilet...
Uh...
—Okarin?!
—Okabe-san!
Suzu-san...
H-Hi there.
Missing Link
of
the
Annihilator
Ta-da!
Very cute!
Me like, nya!
A feast for the eyes! I’ll have seconds!
Hmm? Where’s Okarin?
He went with Suzuha-san to the roof.
They wanted to talk about something.
I see...
You didn’t have to pretend
like this in the first place.
Saying you’re Daru’s little sister
only made yourself more suspicious.
Yeah, but I didn’t think Mom
would wanna get to know me so much.
Yuki-san and Daru first met at...
Summer ComiMa.
She was a cosplay friend of Big Sis Mayu,
but in time, she started coming here.
Owowow...
Eh?
Which is how we met.
But you’re the one she gives birth to.
Her future daughter.
Maybe she feels something.
Dad said he’ll explain
everything to her sooner or later.
But man, Daru and that girl...
The fact that I’m here means
that future hasn’t changed.
Such peace...
By the time I’d grown up, you’d only
see scenes like these in photos and videos.
World War III...
Yeah.
Because Dad and the others
were building a time machine,
we were seen as a rebel organization.
But Daru, Yuki-san, and you somehow escaped?
No...
My mom tried to protect me from a military
drone and was mowed down by machine guns.
I saw her get ripped
to shreds right before my eyes.
I was practically bathed in her blood.
Uncle Okarin...
All that lies ahead in this worldline is hell.
The conflict over time machines makes
country fight country and many people die.
It’s a world of nothing but horror and despair.
The lives of 5.7 billion people
are on the line here.
This future...
I’m begging you...
I failed I failed I failed I failed
I failed I failed I failed I failed I failed
Uncle Okarin...
I can’t...
Uncle!
I’ve drifted through so many
worldlines, I’ve lost count...
No matter the worldline, I’ve witnessed
time machines toy with everyone’s fate.
I’ve even seen you meet your doom.
And over and over, it never ends.
Believe me, I learned the
limits of what someone can do.
No matter what I try, I’m powerless.
But you have changed worldlines before.
You said it yourself.
Uncle...
In that case—
It’s no use!
You can’t just change
the past to switch worldlines!
It breaks the rules which govern our universe!
Humans like us can’t just
tamper with the province of God!
The moment we start meddling,
we get punished!
It’s terrible! Enough that you
want to clamp shut your eyes!
Is that your answer?
There’s still time.
I want you to reconsider.
I...
...have not given up.
In the end, I guess Suzu-san didn’t come back.
Yeah...
The two of you didn’t fight, did you?
That’s not what happened.
I see.
Whew! It’s getting pretty nippy, isn’t it?
The lab was so lively for a change, it was fun.
Yeah?
Yup!
Somehow, going to the lab lately
has left me feeling really lonely.
Isn’t Daru there?
Yeah...
But before, Mayushii used to wait
at the lab all by herself for you.
That’s why I shouldn’t feel lonely at all.
I don’t know why, but I feel
so lonely it makes me want to cry.
It’s like, it used to be a lot more fun.
It’s an illusion.
Eh?
An illusion.
The only people that ever came
to the lab were you, me, and Daru.
Yeah, you’re right.
What’s wrong?
1 New Message
Professor Izaki
View mail
Nothing.
From: Professor Izaki
To: Okabe Rintaro
Regarding tomorrow’s seminar
We’re all going out for some drinks after
the seminar. If you’ve got some free time, would you care to join us?
People from Viktor Chondria University
are giving a seminar in Akiba tomorrow.
I was hoping to talk with their professor,
but I guess they’re all out drinking.
I see!
You’re like a full-fledged normie now.
Mayushii will be fine by herself.
Okay.
Sorry to ditch you.
Cheers!
DEC 2010
10 FR–11 SA
UPX Theater
Artificial Intelligence Revolution...
Viktor Chondria University.
Professor Alexis Leskinen.
Viktor Chondria University Professor
Brain Science Institute Chief Researcher
That’s... the college she went to.
I think... I’m dying.
I don’t want to die...
Hey, you.
I’m talking to you.
Which way is the staff room?
Huh?
Uh, this is a college seminar conference...
Of course I know that!
It’s the same thing, over and over...
Over and over?
You’re the fourth person
to tell me that since coming here.
Viktor Chondria University...
Brain Science Institute.
Oh, I get it. You found this and—
Fourth time to hear that too!
Viktor Chondria University has...
...middle schoolers?
If you’re gonna be dumb, do it elsewhere.
There’s no university
that takes middle schoolers.
21 years old?
In other words, I’m a full-grown woman!
Not in middle school, not elementary
school, and not preschool either!
Got a problem?
But... Never mind.
I was in the wrong.
I’m sorry.
Hmph. Whatever.
The same thing happens
no matter what country I go to.
Big surprise.
Did you say something?
N-No, nothing.
Uh, it’s not that way.
Staff room? Go out that way
and it’s the door at the end of the hall.
Thanks.
21 years old, huh?
If Daru saw her, he’d shout,
“Legal loli for the win!”
Kiryu Moeka?!
Why?!
Why is Moeka here?!
No... Not again!
Calm down! This is a Beta worldline!
It’s not like that other worldline!
It’s not...
Is that... the girl from earlier?
Hi, everyone.
Thank you for attending my seminar today.
I am Alexis Leskinen from Viktor Chondria
University’s Brain Science Institute.
I’m his interpreter and assistant, Hiyajo Maho.
Our topic for today is the Artificial
Intelligence Revolution, however...
Before we get into that, there’s
a paper I would like to introduce.
An Analysis of Neural Pulse Signals
in Relation to Memories Stored in the Temporal Lobe
This paper was published by
a female researcher at our lab.
Our memories are stored in the cerebral cortex.
More specifically, within the temporal lobe.
Memories are retrieved
similarly to flash memory.
The brain operates by sending
electrical signals between neurons.
Ultimately, it is the pattern of these electrical
signals which create and reinforce memories.
I regret to say the woman who proposed
this theory passed away at the age of 17.
But using her theory as a foundation,
we were able to construct a special system.
That is, a system which
preserves human memory as data.
Unlike previous programs,
which fall short of possessing identity,
we’ve developed an AI with
data drawn from human memories.
It has feelings and memories, just like a human.
An artificial intelligence with a soul.
The genius of Makise Kurisu and
her theory enabled us to build this system.
Without further ado, we would
like to demonstrate said AI.
Amadeus.
MUWAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA
Ashita no tenki mo
“Tomorrow’s weather
Shiranu mama ga ii to
“Is better of not known,” I say,
Kasa wo motazu
So I don’t carry an umbrella
Namida no ame nara
Any downpour of tears that may await me
Yasashisugiru uso ni kakikaeta
Will be rewritten into the gentlest of lies
Hako ni tojikometa sora no danpen ga
The pieces of the sky enclosed within the box
Mirai no pazuru ni hamattekurenai
Cannot connect to form the puzzle of the future
Mugenkai no suiron wa noizu hakidashite
Static, spat out from my infinith inference,
Kami sae mo azamuku rojikku
Is the logic to deceive God himself,
Yakusoku no ano basho he
Bringing us closer to that promised place...
Bokura wa uchuu mo mada shiranai
We will open the gate of Zero,
Zero no geeto hiraku yo
Still unknown to the universe,
Subete wa tsubu to nari
Reducing everything to particles
Saisei suru
And reassembling it all
Sorenara togiresou na ishiki mo
Even so, I’ll show you
Tsunagitomete miseru yo
I can hold on to this discontinuous consciousness,
Ano jikan ano basho de
And in that hour, in that place,
Kimi no toki ga mou ichido hajimaru
Your “time” will begin once more