I got your message...
I’m Kiryu Moeka.
Um...
Oh, you’re here?
What are you doing, Okarin? Let the lady in.
R-Right...
Here’s some tea.
Kiryu Moeka...
Why?
Why are she and Daru...?
This world is a false reality
It’s merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn’t merely something that’s expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
Solitude
of the
Astigmatism
...to not be human. The bodies, missing
their brains and portions of the cranium,
Mass animal corpses found in America
were discovered to be
chimpanzee and orangutan.
Hmm?
What’s wrong?
N-Nothing.
Calm down...
This isn’t that worldline anymore.
We don’t have any connection to SERN.
Moeka won’t kill Mayuri.
She won’t kill Mayuri...
She won’t kill...
Uncle? You’re not looking too good.
I’m fine.
Daru, care to explain?
Who is this person?
Kiryu-shi, a writer for an editorial.
I’m Kiryu Moeka.
Arc Rewrite
Publishing Department
Editor/Writer
A while back, there was a magazine
covering the urban legends of Akiba.
That’s when she contacted me wanting
to write about my part-time work.
Your work?
You know, the stuff I can’t talk out loud about.
I’m always careful not to leave any trace,
but Kiryu-shi somehow managed to find me.
So that explains your interest in her.
I heard you’re looking for someone.
Actually, we’re looking for a girl
that went missing in Akiba 12 years ago.
12 years ago...
Yeah.
Her name is Shiina Kagari.
She was 10 years old 12 years ago,
so that would make her 22 now.
She’s alive?
We don’t know for sure, but we found
someone resembling her in a recent photo.
Should we really be trusting her?
It’s true that in this worldline,
she shouldn’t have to interact with us...
She has no reason to kill Mayuri either.
But more than likely,
she’s a Rounder in this worldline too.
She can still kill without batting an eye...
Can I take on the job?
You serious?
Though, I don’t know if I’ll find her.
Of course. Not much you can do about that.
You’ll be compensated if you succeed,
but we’ll cover any expenses
you need for your work, all right?
No problem.
You fine with that, Okarin?
Y-Yeah.
Great. You’re officially hired then.
Let’s go, Nae.
’Kay!
Don’t forget your seatbelt.
Right!
Ready?
Yup!
—Off we go!
So? Who was that?
Eh?
You know that person, don’t you?
Huh?
What makes you think that?
You made it obvious.
You know her, Okarin?
No, I d—
What about in the Alpha worldline?
All right.
I won’t pry any deeper,
but I’ll stay on guard from my end.
That’s fine, at least for now.
What’s this about?
She makes me nervous.
I get it! Since Kiryu-shi is hot, stylish, and
checks all the right boxes for a glasses fetish!
Brain Science Institute
I should probably get
a pro to help me with this...
That’s right! No matter how much
I call, he’s just not answering.
What gives? He’s a joke of a tester.
Have you considered he
might have broken his phone?
Dunno, but let’s hope that’s it.
Makise Kurisu is dead.
It’s a rare sight to see you
brooding over something like this.
Professor?! When did you get back?!
Just now.
These Japanese convenience
stores are pretty awesome.
You can eat a different bento every day,
and by the next week,
there’s a whole new selection.
If you keep eating convenience
store food, it’ll ruin your health.
Take a good look at yourself
before judging my eating habits.
So? Where are you going?
Off to Akihabara for a change of pace.
Just admit you’re going
there to visit Lintahlo already.
Th-That’s not why I’m...
It’s not?
I guess I could see him on the way...
On the way? On the way to what?
I told you, for a change of pace!
For this change of pace of yours,
you’re willing to go an hour away to Akihabara,
where Lintahlo just happens to be?
Is that what you’re saying?
I approve.
I-I’m going, but it’s not what you think.
It’s not like that.
It’s not like what?
Anyways, I’m done working today. Goodbye.
Say hi to Lintahlo for me.
This is?
My report.
Well?
Looks like finding her won’t be that easy.
I see...
Hmm? Find a clue?
No, it’s not that, but...
Lemme see.
H-Hey!
During the investigation,
one peculiar discovery was made.
In the past several months,
there is evidence that a party other than
ours has been searching for Shiina Kagari.
What’s that mean?
Just as you read.
Who’s looking for her?
I don’t know.
Is it possible that it’s Suzuha?
I thought the same at first,
but look right here.
The people searching were men.
With a foreigner among them.
Foreigner?
But she’s been gone 12 whole years.
Maybe she made some friends in that time.
Hmm...
Actually, as a kid, she wouldn’t have
lived very long without knowing somebody.
That’s true, but...
With this, at least we know one thing.
Which is?
We know that Shiina Kagari...
is alive in the present.
A foreigner, huh?
I’m pretty sure it was this way...
Right now... I happen to be in Akihabara, so...
I’m going to stop by the lab...
Please, pick up!
Hello?! Okabe-san?!
Hiyajo-san?
Right now, I’m running towards the lab, but—
Hiyajo-san? Hiyajo-san?!
Okarin?
Hiyajo-san?!
Huh?
It can’t be! It can’t be that!
It’s not happening! It’s not!
Hiyajo-san?!
A woman?
Stop it! Let me go!
H-Hold it!
Hands off that girl!
No, don’t!
Whoa! What the?
Hiyajo-san!
This is why I said not to...
Reyes?
Professor Judy Reyes.
She said she came to Japan to attend an
AI conference being held in the near future.
Professor?
Of Viktor Chondria University?
Um, I’m...
Japanese is fine too.
Are you surprised?
So you’re Rintaro.
I heard all about you from Alexis.
Alexis?
Oh, Professor Leskinen.
Her specialty is psychophysiology.
The link of mind and body.
It’s the field of research that studies
how cognitive processes influence
the heart, disease, and so on.
In other words,
her branch of science is a lot more useful
to humanity than the research that I do.
That’s not true at all.
You guys and your Amadeus
might prove to be incredibly useful.
I’m very honored you feel that way.
But it was still cruel of you
to stalk me from the station.
The station? Stalk you?
I did?
Huh? You didn’t?
I just saw you in the alleyway and
thought I’d jump out and surprise you.
Then...
Did I imagine it?
Anyways, bring Rintaro and
we’ll have a nice long chat sometime.
Bye!
No!
I told you, it’s not like that!
What was that all about?
Eh?
It’s nothing...
Okarin!
Something happen?
No, it wasn’t anything.
Ooh, Hiyajo-shi!
Is it just me, or are you tinier
than the last time we met?
You honestly believe something that dumb?
Mmm! She’s becoming
more loli by the minute!
Did we trigger the flag for Hiyajo-shi
to be inducted into the lab
as our token loli character?
Doubt it.
In that case, I’ll settle for calling
her Maho-tan! That’s right, I said it!
What the heck are you on about?
Amadeus did?
Yeah.
She said you won’t pick up
no matter how many times she calls.
Judging by that face,
you’re not answering on purpose.
Yeah...
Let me talk to the professor.
This was only a test from the start.
You’re not obligated to help.
You’re not even getting paid.
But...
I had no idea... that Kurisu had
such a large presence in your life.
I told you already, Kurisu wasn’t—
I can tell by watching you.
Her presence was huge...
What you’re doing... is projecting
your feelings for Kurisu onto Amadeus.
When her voice revives old memories,
it breathes new life into you,
and with it your feelings grow.
But, Amadeus is nothing more than a system.
All that’s there are memories made data.
To have feelings for that...
I know...
But...
Those are Kurisu’s memories, and that’s a fact!
Okabe-san...
I understand that! And how Kurisu is gone!
I know it’s only a system...
But...
Even so...
Please, let me think a little longer.
What are you doing for New Years?
Are you planning a party?
Yup! We’ll all go and visit the shrine,
have a big New Year’s meal,
and hope for another good year!
Burnable
Well, sounds good to me.
I know, right?
I’ll ask the others about it later.
Burnable
Okay, Mayushii is going out shopping.
For ComiMa?
Burnable
Uh-huh! It’s for Fubuki-chan’s cosplay.
She needs a couple accessories.
Oh, right. Not many days left.
Yeah.
Once it’s over, the year will soon follow.
It went by in the blink of an eye...
In the blink of an eye...
INTERACTIVE TRAINING SIMULATION
That summer...
How many times did I live and repeat it?
But, even that year is ending.
Ooh!
It’s snowing!
I wonder if it’ll stick?!
Time goes on.
—Wow! This is wonderful!
—The time that I chose...
Okarin! I’m gonna get going!
O-Okay.
Oh, right.
I think Luka-kun had something
he wanted to discuss with you.
Ah, I completely forgot he called me.
I’ll call him back.
Okay! Tell him hi!
Mayuri
Daru
Lukako
Mayuri
Daru
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
I’ll get a hold of you later.
If you still want to talk,
can you call me?
I wonder if he’s busy?
I bet he’s helping ready
the shrine for New Years.
May I come in?
Lukako?
It’s open.
Thank goodness, you’re here.
Sorry...
If it’s about earlier, I totally forgot.
—I tried to call you just now.
—Huh? You’re right!
I’m the one who’s sorry for not noticing.
Don’t worry about it.
You wanted to talk with me?
Um, yes.
Actually, I...
Um, actually... There’s someone I wanted
you to meet, so I brought them along.
Is that okay?
Someone you want me to meet?
Ku...
Kurisu!
Here you go.
Thanks.
They’re so alike...
But, her voice is different.
Must be a coincidence.
But still...
So, Lukako? Who is this?
Lukako?
Oh, sorry. That’s what I call him.
Because he’s so feminine.
I believe I told you before... That one of
my father’s guests would be staying with us.
Oh, so it was her?
Yes...
My father’s acquaintance
had brought her along.
What’s her name?
Actually, that’s what
I wanted to talk to you about.
Um, do you know anything we
could do to find out who this girl is?
Uh, what do you mean?
Well, she has amnesia...
Huh?
Her name, where she came from,
how she lost her memory...
She remembers none of it.
Are you serious?
I thought if anyone, you would know
a way to bring back her memories.
You always talk about brains and
memories and complicated things...
Anything you can do to help.
I just want to remember who I am.
H-Hold on.
I might talk about that stuff,
but I’m no expert on it.
Besides, regaining memories is no simple task.
Storing it aside is one thing, but...
I see...
In that case, is there any way
to find out where she came from?
I feel bad for poor Kana-san.
Kana? What’s that?
It’s annoying if she has no name,
so Kana it is... or so Father said.
Well, that’s one way to do it.
It doesn’t matter anyways.
It’s just a temporary name.
More importantly...
Do you have anything
that might serve as a hint?
Like... a wallet, a pass, or cellphone.
Nothing like that.
Nothing?
How in the world did you live until now?
There is one thing that might be a hint.
Kana-san?
Right.
This...
Tutturu! I’m back!
It stopped snowing.
Hmm? A guest?
This is...
An Upa!
Hey, hey! Where did you get that Upa?!
Kana-san has never let it leave her side.
If I’m not mistaken,
didn’t this use to be green?
I think it’s the forest fairy version!
The forest fairy?
Yup! It showed up in a movie not too long ago.
See? It’s like my Upa,
but the design is different.
That one has wings!
Then... why does it look so old?
If it’s from a new movie...
I’m home...
H-Hey!
You okay?! Hey!
Kagari...
You’re Kagari...
Shiina Kagari, aren’t you?!
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
’Cause you’re free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now, it’s time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just a part of its plan
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
The last game