Okabe Rintaro!
Don’t move!
What the...
Okarin!
Wh-What’s going on?
Is this... some sort of surprise?
Don’t tell me...
It was you after all?!
Kiryu Moeka!
This world is a false reality
It’s merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn’t merely something that’s expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
Stay put!
K-6205.
Okay.
K-6205, secured.
Kagari-san!
No! Help me, Mayuri-san!
Don’t do it! If you fight back...
Stop it! Let me go!
Hey!
I warned you to keep quiet on the 2nd floor!
D-Dad!
Braun-shi!
Kagari-san!
Get back here!
D-Daddy!
Everything’s fine now. Dad’s here for you.
You’ve got some explaining to do, Okabe.
Who the hell were those folks?
That’s...
We’re back.
—We bought a bunch of drinks for everyone.
—Huh?
What’s the deal?
Why does everyone look so scared?
Whoa! What the heck!? The TV!
Careful where you step!
Where’s the broom and pan?
Eclipse
of
Vibronic Transition
Looks like Mayuri’s group
got home safe and sound.
Maho-tan said she made it back to her office.
She’s staying the night
at the institute just in case.
Good... That’s a relief.
Hey, Okarin.
Those guys were after Kagari-tan, weren’t they?
Yeah...
You know what it seems like?
That group probably knows
that Kagari-tan came from the future.
Can’t help but think...
This whole time she was missing,
maybe something happened to her?
Seems that way.
SERN’s Rounders...
In the past, that same organization attacked
and captured us for developing a time machine.
No, wait...
Even if the worldline changed, Tennouji should
still be the boss running things in Akihabara.
If he’s the enemy,
it’s weird for him to help us.
Which means the one in the
motorcycle suit wasn’t Kiryu Moeka...
But someone else...
I still can’t believe all that happened...
In Akiba? In Japan?
Attacked by a group with guns?
It’s becoming just like Suzuha said...
I’m half-expecting everyone to
jump out and say, “Gotcha! You fell for it!”
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I know the feeling.
But, it happened, and that’s the truth.
I know it... I remember it.
That same scene I relived countless times...
The gun smoke... The screams... The blood...
What’s wrong?
Sorry.
Wanna take a break?
No...
Maybe it’s that? This was the
choice of Steins Gate, or something.
Steins Gate, huh?
Sounds pathetic the more I think about it.
Look, you can’t even stand straight.
Hang on my shoulder.
I’ll be fine.
Just do it, okay?
Hey, do you think it’ll happen again?
Something like today?
I’ve gotta think of a way
to make sure it doesn’t...
We’re unable to complete your call.
The number you dialed is out of the service area
or has been disconnected and is unreachable.
For crying out loud!
Why does the Professor have to go
missing during an emergency like this?
No matter how many times I try,
I can’t connect to Amadeus.
What in the world is going on here?
Hello?
Suzuha, it’s me. How are things there?
The security here is a lot beefier
than I thought... for a shrine.
Maybe Luka-shi’s dad is paranoid.
I know they’ve had a system
in place for a while now.
They had problems with people
trying to sneak in at night.
Even so, isn’t it a bit over the top?
Well, they might’ve asked
Okarin for a little help...
...and I might’ve disguised
a hidden camera or two...
Anyways, after seeing what they’ve
got here, I think we can rest assured.
Okay.
If anything happens, let me know right away.
Right. You be careful too, Dad.
You’re a lot weaker than me.
You can do better than that! Call Papa
a worthless normie pig that can’t even—
Oh, welcome back!
How’s Kagari?
Must be terribly frightened.
She only fell asleep just now.
I see.
I bet you’re tired too, Big Bro Luka.
You should go to bed.
Security-wise, there’s no problem,
so you don’t need to worry.
Suzuha-san, you’re not sleeping?
I’m fine just like this. If anything happens,
I’ll be ready to react.
S-Seriously? You’ll never be rested like that.
It’s okay, I’m used to it.
Mommy...
Mommy, don’t leave me...
El Psy Kongalee...
Um, do you mind if I ask something?
What?
Well...
Why is it that when you talk about Okabe-san,
you refer to him as Uncle Okarin?
Why is it that you call
Mayuri-chan, Big Sis Mayu?
And Faris-san, you’re always
calling Big Sis Rumi...
Even me... Why do you call me Big Bro Luka?
Kagari-san was saying
“Mommy” just now, wasn’t she?
But, right before she fell asleep,
she said a name...
Mommy Mayuri...
That has to mean Mayuri-chan, right?
Why did she say mommy?
It’s better if you don’t know.
Yet again, everyone’s leaving
me out of the circle...
Okabe-san and Mayuri-chan
always look so hurt...
Hashida-san and Faris-san,
everyone’s hiding something from me...
I know I probably can’t be of any help, but...
Even so...
I care too! I want to share in their worries!
Big Bro Luka...
Won’t you please tell me?
The thing about Uncle Okarin...
You’re the only one he won’t tell...
And I think I understand the reason now.
The reason?
He wants at least you to stay
completely a part of this world.
So that all you ever know is
the world as it exists right now.
To him... to Uncle Okarin...
I think... that saves him.
Saves him?
Yeah...
But that’s...
What can I even say to that?
You should probably sleep.
Good night.
Happy
new
Year’s
Open for business
starting the 3rd
Happy
new
Year’s
Open for business
starting the 3rd
Hmph, you finally showed up?
So? What the hell happened yesterday?
I’ve got this.
If I’m right, this should all work out.
What’s up? Didn’t you come to explain?
B-Before that, I want to confirm something.
It wasn’t your doing, was it?
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Why would you think I’d do something like that?
Isn’t it obvious?
I’ve got no idea what you’re talking about.
If you keep spouting nonsense,
I’m raising your rent.
I’m saying that because I know
you’re a Rounder, Mr. Ferdinand Braun.
Or... should I call you FB?
What’s wrong, Dad?
Hmm?
You’re scary all of a sudden.
Yeah? But this is how I always am, you know?
Be a good girl and go outside...
No, watch an anime over there, okay?
Put on those headphones while you’re at it.
Really? Woohoo!
I knew it. You don’t want her to find out.
The woman in the
motorcycle suit that attacked us...
That wasn’t your subordinate Kiryu Moeka.
It wasn’t the Rounders at all, but another...
I can’t help but ask...
What proof do you have for any of this?
Even if I tell, you won’t believe me.
Come on, let’s hear it.
That face of yours says you came ready to talk.
Really?
B-But why didn’t you tell the police?
Well, Okarin-san said to hold off on that.
You’re kidding me! They had guns, didn’t they?
Anyways, he’s got something to tell us.
You’re going to the lab?
Hashida-san said no one’s stupid
enough to attack twice in a row.
The thing is... No, I wish I could come too...
What happened to your arm?
Uh... I tripped and fell over yesterday.
Time machines and worldlines, eh?
It goes without saying that’s hard to believe.
I told you that from the start.
You did, but...
What you said about me is true.
Your facts are essentially spot on,
enough that it’s creeping me out.
I also know that SERN’s secrets
are absolutely confidential.
If a mission succeeds or fails, it’s the same.
They eliminate everyone
who knows their secrets.
You know that much too? In that case—
However, this has nothing
to do with your mission!
Hmm?
Your secrets were never leaked!
I just knew them from the start.
Which means there’s no reason
for them to punish you.
How convenient for you... But you’re not wrong.
SERN hasn’t said anything to me as of yet.
There’s no problem if you keep quiet
about me being a Rounder.
So? What are you after?
You must have a reason
for telling me this, right?
I need to ask a favor.
Shiina Kagari. I want you
to protect the girl they’re after.
Who’s targeting that girl, and why?
I don’t know.
Then I’m done listening.
I’ll pretend you never came, so—
You can’t!
If something like yesterday happens again,
what will happen to your daughter?!
She might be put in danger all over again!
You bastard... Plan to use Nae as a hostage?
I’ll slaughter you.
I’m saying we should cooperate!
If it’s just you alone, you might not
be able to protect your daughter.
By helping you, I’m risking it all for nothing!
That’s not true. There’s plenty in it for you.
You little—
You guys came...
If you let Kagari and me work part-time here,
it shouldn’t be that much work for you.
Evicting all of you from the building
sounds like a better idea to me.
That way, Nae and me stay out—
Both of you witnessed the group
that attacked us yesterday.
I hate to break it to you,
but I think you know what that means.
Dad...
I don’t really know what happened,
but yesterday was really scary
and I don’t like it at all...
Nae...
But...
What’s scarier is the thought of
Dad getting hurt trying to protect me.
That’s why... I like it better
with Big Sis Suzuha and the others...
Nae... Argh!
Just so you know, you two
will be splitting the pay.
We’re not loaded with cash, you know.
Dad!
Cheapskate.
Huh? If you’ve got a problem,
I’m raising your rent!
N-No! Thank you very much, Tennouji-san!
Hmph. So, Okabe.
You better hurry up and
find out who those people were.
If you don’t, we can’t do nothing about them.
Understood.
So, you think that Kagari-san
got wrapped up in some sort of crime
during the time she lost her memories?
Yeah.
In that case, why don’t you contact the police?
Well, you see... She’s afraid of the police.
You never know! The police might
be connected to the crime after all!
Sheesh! I don’t know if I buy that...
Uh, anyways...
They’re only targeting Kagari.
Having said that, you should all
steer clear of this area for the time being.
What? You’re kidding...
But what about Kagari-san?
If they’re after her...
We’ve got two bodyguards on her.
Two people we can trust.
If it’s Suzu-san and Mr. Braun,
they can handle it.
Of course, we’re doing research of our own too.
We’ll find out who they are
and what they’re after.
Yup. That’s a job for yours truly.
Akiba’s neighborhood watch promised
to keep an eye on the streets for me,
so if someone’s up to no good,
we should know it, nya.
Um, is there anything I could be doing to help?
Kagari-san is in trouble, and yet,
I’m just sitting here doing nothing...
Can Mayushii help somehow too?
Lukako, you already sheltered
Kagari-san in your home.
Mayuri, you’ve helped so much already.
You’ve done enough.
Is there anything the rest of us can do?
K-6205...
What’s that mean?
Tennouji-san was saying...
Another Earthquake in Russia
Now that I think about it,
those guys said something odd.
Something odd?
Wasn’t it... Yeah...
K-6205 or something like that.
The way they said it, it has to be...
That’s phonetic code.
Phonetic code?
For military use.
More specifically, by the Western world.
Download Phone.com’s instruction manual for the K6205 here...
List of instruction manuals, instruction manual viewing page, Japanese version,
foreign version, setup manual, detailed instruction manual, instruction manual...
phone.co.jp/.../k6205/index.html  — cache — similar pages
K6205 (Red) rankings
View the cheapest prices of Phone.com’s K6205! Compare the prices of all
retailers nationwide. Lots of product reviews and user comments. You can
shop wisely and save money by comparing different companies’ products...
hikaku-ranking.com/item/K6205  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 01 — Parcot Co., Ltd.
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª8.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 25 kg, ¥13,500
/ m². K6206, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.6 mm, 2.8 sheets / m², 3 sheets
of 23 kg, ¥13,000 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207, Gray — Black — White,
1195ª596ª8.5 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 31 kg, ¥15,000 / m²...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 02 — We’ll take care of your home renovation needs!
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205-02, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª10.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 28 kg, ¥15,000
/ m². K6206-02, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.9 mm, 2.8 sheets/ m²,
3 sheets of 26 kg, ¥14,800 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207-02, Gray —
Black — White, 1195ª596ª9.4 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 33...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Mini Kitchen “K6205” — Kasys Table kitchen renovation
This mini kitchen will fit in a wide range of environments, from small apartments
to single-family homes. Leg-storage-type mini kitchen “K6205”. For compact,
spacious and basic storage plans, mini kitchen “K6205”’s basic type... Customize
the doors of mini kitchen “K6205” to make your kitchen look as good as possible,
and fit your style to a tee... Select the stove type that best suits your home...
The sink is designed for ease of use. Common parts...
kasystable.jp/minikitchen/K6205  — cache — similar pages
Download Phone.com’s instruction manual for the K6205 here...
List of instruction manuals, instruction manual viewing page, Japanese version,
foreign version, setup manual, detailed instruction manual, instruction manual...
phone.co.jp/.../k6205/index.html  — cache — similar pages
K6205 (Red) rankings
View the cheapest prices of Phone.com’s K6205! Compare the prices of all
retailers nationwide. Lots of product reviews and user comments. You can
shop wisely and save money by comparing different companies’ products...
hikaku-ranking.com/item/K6205  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 01 — Parcot Co., Ltd.
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª8.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 25 kg, ¥13,500
/ m². K6206, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.6 mm, 2.8 sheets / m², 3 sheets
of 23 kg, ¥13,000 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207, Gray — Black — White,
1195ª596ª8.5 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 31 kg, ¥15,000 / m²...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 02 — We’ll take care of your home renovation needs!
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205-02, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª10.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 28 kg, ¥15,000
/ m². K6206-02, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.9 mm, 2.8 sheets/ m²,
3 sheets of 26 kg, ¥14,800 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207-02, Gray —
Black — White, 1195ª596ª9.4 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 33...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Mini Kitchen “K6205” — Kasys Table kitchen renovation
This mini kitchen will fit in a wide range of environments, from small apartments
to single-family homes. Leg-storage-type mini kitchen “K6205”. For compact,
spacious and basic storage plans, mini kitchen “K6205”’s basic type... Customize
the doors of mini kitchen “K6205” to make your kitchen look as good as possible,
and fit your style to a tee... Select the stove type that best suits your home...
The sink is designed for ease of use. Common parts...
kasystable.jp/minikitchen/K6205  — cache — similar pages
Download Phone.com’s instruction manual for the K6205 here...
List of instruction manuals, instruction manual viewing page, Japanese version,
foreign version, setup manual, detailed instruction manual, instruction manual...
phone.co.jp/.../k6205/index.html  — cache — similar pages
K6205 (Red) rankings
View the cheapest prices of Phone.com’s K6205! Compare the prices of all
retailers nationwide. Lots of product reviews and user comments. You can
shop wisely and save money by comparing different companies’ products...
hikaku-ranking.com/item/K6205  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 01 — Parcot Co., Ltd.
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª8.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 25 kg, ¥13,500
/ m². K6206, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.6 mm, 2.8 sheets / m², 3 sheets
of 23 kg, ¥13,000 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207, Gray — Black — White,
1195ª596ª8.5 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 31 kg, ¥15,000 / m²...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 02 — We’ll take care of your home renovation needs!
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205-02, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª10.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 28 kg, ¥15,000
/ m². K6206-02, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.9 mm, 2.8 sheets/ m²,
3 sheets of 26 kg, ¥14,800 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207-02, Gray —
Black — White, 1195ª596ª9.4 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 33...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Mini Kitchen “K6205” — Kasys Table kitchen renovation
This mini kitchen will fit in a wide range of environments, from small apartments
to single-family homes. Leg-storage-type mini kitchen “K6205”. For compact,
spacious and basic storage plans, mini kitchen “K6205”’s basic type... Customize
the doors of mini kitchen “K6205” to make your kitchen look as good as possible,
and fit your style to a tee... Select the stove type that best suits your home...
The sink is designed for ease of use. Common parts...
kasystable.jp/minikitchen/K6205  — cache — similar pages
Hmm...
Download Phone.com’s instruction manual for the K6205 here...
List of instruction manuals, instruction manual viewing page, Japanese version,
foreign version, setup manual, detailed instruction manual, instruction manual...
phone.co.jp/.../k6205/index.html  — cache — similar pages
K6205 (Red) rankings
View the cheapest prices of Phone.com’s K6205! Compare the prices of all
retailers nationwide. Lots of product reviews and user comments. You can
shop wisely and save money by comparing different companies’ products...
hikaku-ranking.com/item/K6205  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 01 — Parcot Co., Ltd.
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª8.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 25 kg, ¥13,500
/ m². K6206, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.6 mm, 2.8 sheets / m², 3 sheets
of 23 kg, ¥13,000 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207, Gray — Black — White,
1195ª596ª8.5 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 31 kg, ¥15,000 / m²...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Floor Materials 02 — We’ll take care of your home renovation needs!
Shape, product ID, color value, dimensions (mm), required amount, amount
per case, weight per case, standard price, 750 mm square, K6205-02, Gray —
Black — White, 748ª748ª10.5 mm, 1.8 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 28 kg, ¥15,000
/ m². K6206-02, Gray — Black — White, 596ª596ª9.9 mm, 2.8 sheets/ m²,
3 sheets of 26 kg, ¥14,800 / m². 1200ª600 mm square. K6207-02, Gray —
Black — White, 1195ª596ª9.4 mm, 1.4 sheets / m², 2 sheets of 33...
prcot./collection/detail/...html  — cache — similar pages
Mini Kitchen “K6205” — Kasys Table kitchen renovation
This mini kitchen will fit in a wide range of environments, from small apartments
to single-family homes. Leg-storage-type mini kitchen “K6205”. For compact,
spacious and basic storage plans, mini kitchen “K6205”’s basic type... Customize
the doors of mini kitchen “K6205” to make your kitchen look as good as possible,
and fit your style to a tee... Select the stove type that best suits your home...
The sink is designed for ease of use. Common parts...
kasystable.jp/minikitchen/K6205  — cache — similar pages
I’m only seeing stuff like product numbers.
What about Köchel numbering?
What’s that?
They’re numbers assigned
to each one of Mozart’s compositions.
Then again, Mozart didn’t make 6,000 songs
in the first place, so that can’t be it.
Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart
Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart  (27 January 1756 – 5
December 1791), was a composer baptised as
Johannes Chrysostomus Wolfgangus Theophilus
Mozart in Salzburg, Austria.
He is regarded as the prodigy among the three great
Viennese classical masters, alongside the father of
the symphony Haydn, and the master of music
Beethoven.
iiiContents
Life
iiiiiiiEarly life
iiiiiiiEducation
iiiiiiiMannheim
Wolfgang Amadeus
Mozart
Posthumous portrait painted
from imagination, c. 1819
General information
Bornii 27 January 1756
Diediii 5 December 1791
Genre Classical music
Years active 1761 – 1791
Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart...
What if it’s not 6205 but part 5 of 620?
620? That’s The Magic Flute, I think.
Wow, you’re right.
Um... It is famous for the Masonic
elements and symbolism it contains...
The Magic Flute
The Magic Flute (German: Die Zauberflöte), K. 620, is a Singspiel written
by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart in 1791. The piece marks Mozart’s final
opera before his premature death, and has a Köchel number of K. 620.
It is still considered to be one of Mozart’s greatest operas.
The work contains several lighthearted and comedic scenes, which is
uncommon for operas. It is famous for the Masonic elements and
symbolism it contains.
Contents
History
Premiere
Composition
Roles
Synopsis
Amadeus?
I wonder what’s up?
I can’t connect to the Amadeus server...
Mayuri
Daru
Lukako
Hiyajo-san
Mayuri
Lukako
Hiyajo-san
Mayuri
Lukako
Hiyajo-san
Mayuri
Lukako
Hiyajo-san
Mayuri
Lukako
Professor Izaki
Mayuri
Okarin?
Hi, this is Hiyajo.
Hello? It’s me.
Okabe-san? Did something happen again?
No, I need to ask something.
Make it short. I’m kinda busy right now.
How’s Amadeus? Any luck?
Nope.
I can’t access it.
I don’t want to think it,
but it’s possible someone took it over.
I’m hanging up. We’ll talk later.
Okarin?
Incoming Call
Amadeus...
[Kurisu]?!
Please, help me...
Okabe!
Reading Steiner?!
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
’Cause you’re free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now, it’s time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just a part of its plan
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
The last game
Amadeus... it’s gone.
The worldline changed?!
It changed?!
Is somebody there?
Daru? Mayuri?
Kurisu?