Don’t panic. The world line hasn’t changed.
In which case, Mayuri and Suzuha are okay.
This can’t be where they...
Mayuri...
Howdy, Lintahlo.
Professor Leskinen?
This “vision” we call life
Is yet unaware that it’s an illusion
Even antinomic paradoxes
Can be tricked into existence by an infinite amount of world lines
If the natural trajectory dictated by emotional decisions
Supersedes even common sense
Then my—and merely my—
Suffering, and my mistakes, will still neatly follow the algorithm
Words and tokens of love—memories growing ever stronger
Guarantee I will not leave you behind a second time
I am forever by your side
We’re joined together as one
Out of this quantum entanglement, “0” will manifest
Big Sis Mayu!
Reyes?
What did you do... to Mommy?
Eh?
O-Open Fire!
Don’t be afraid!
Aim for the body! Slow down her movements!
Kagari!
Curious how it’s going up there on the roof?
What do you mean by that?
What are you doing here?
It’s not good manners to answer
a question with a question, Lintahlo.
I’ll dock your grades.
Though, to think you’d
show up here so quickly...
Who was it? Who gave you the big hint?
Maho? No... I suppose
if it’s anyone, it’s [Kurisu].
[Kurisu]?
Our Father and God...
To Amadeus, the professor who created
the system is both father and God...
Did she really say something like that?
Has a nice ring to it.
I feel kinda slick, for her
to praise me as a God like that.
But, she also had this to say...
Our most secret domains were unveiled,
so we may tell Father the secrets of
manipulating time and where they’re at.
So dim, Lintahlo.
If you got a message saying all that,
you should know the answer already.
I’m afraid to say you’re in too deep.
You... Who the hell are you?!
A scientist.
Though, science isn’t
always a charity, you know?
Perhaps you’ve heard of
the company Strategic Focus?
Strat... You mean Stratfoc?!
It’s a private intelligence agency called
a shadow CIA, among other things.
Then you... from the very beginning!
America, Russia...
All the great powers escalate the conflict
to obtain a time machine starting this very day.
I couldn’t exactly act before that point
because everything was to converge.
I’ve been itching with excitement
for this day to finally come.
I take it you know
what I’m getting at, Lintahlo.
What the hell is going on?
How does he know all that?
Was it Hiyajo-san? Don’t tell me she...
No, it can’t be...
Kurisu’s memories in Amadeus are
all from before she came to Japan.
Then who could have...?
The look on your face says you’re dying
to know how I possibly knew all that.
There’s someone, right?
One who knows everything,
being a little messenger from the future...
Kagari?!
Big Sis Mayu.
Suzu-san...
Stay still. That ricochet had to have
grazed you, but you’re still bleeding.
That’s...
Don’t look!
Mommy...
What did you do...
...to Mommy?!
Are they still at it? And here
I told her to avoid making a fuss...
Mayuri!
Kagari?
Don’t, Big Sis Mayu!
What... is this?
Mayuri!
Mommy...
Mommy, this isn’t...
I was... because Mommy...
Mommy...
Mommy... I’m sorry, Mommy.
Kagari!
Mommy...
Stay still.
Suzu-san...
How’s Mayuri?!
Her head is a bit cut up, but she’s fine.
No other injuries.
Good... Mayuri’s okay.
I see... Thank goodness.
Don’t try to talk.
It’s okay, don’t worry about me.
Because, even though I’m like this,
I don’t feel the pain at all...
Don’t try to be tough. Just—
I hear the voice of God...
Telling me it doesn’t hurt...
Telling me not to suffer...
That’s why... this doesn’t...
Kagari... Kagari!
Suzu-san.
Kagari-chan.
Mommy? Thank goodness...
Kagari...
Big Sis Suzuha...
I’m sorry.
Whenever I hear the voice of God,
everything in my head gets messed up.
God tells me... what I must do... and I do it.
I’m... sorry...
—Kagari-chan!
—Kagari!
Looks like I missed the big party.
The future’s brainwashing and enhancement
techniques sure are incredible.
Professor!
You did this... to Kagari!
No, it was more of a joint effort.
By me... and well, me.
I don’t know what exactly
you’re getting at, but...
It’s all your fault this happened to Kagari!
What if I said you’re right?
You bastard!
Good on you for stopping.
Suzuha, I’m sorry...
Suzuha!
Professor...
Maho, isn’t this crazy? Hard to believe, I know.
However, this was all destined
to happen ahead of time.
Destined to happen?
Observation and insight
is what sets scientists apart.
Didn’t you hear what I said?
This is a joint effort between me and myself.
Spanning across time.
Time?!
It can’t be!
13 years ago, when for the
very first time Kagari approached me,
can you guess what she said?
I hear the voice of God.
God?
The future you... is calling me.
Altair
of
Translational
Symmetry
The future... Professor?
That’s right. Can you believe it?
Me in the future sent Kagari back into the past.
All so I could obtain
the power of manipulating time.
The future you did?
Then, Kagari was...
And what an intricate plan it was.
In order to track the movements of the
resistance you form in the distant future...
...I trained countless young girls
and boys to act as spies and infiltrate in.
You’re all so softhearted,
you fell right for the bait.
But see, then came the pinnacle of my plan.
If somehow or another,
you managed to escape to the past...
I made sure to send along a messenger
to my past self... using brainwashing.
I could hardly believe it myself.
But the more and more I researched,
I began to realize her story checked out.
I concluded the time machine was real
and that Kagari actually came from the future.
Then, did you make Amadeus because...
Correct. Because Kurisu goes and dies.
I needed a system that preserved
her precious time machine theory
and all those memories of hers.
Professor! That’s what you did it for?!
You basically let Kurisu die?! Professor!
Everything I did was long, tiresome groundwork
to come steal the time machine today.
Defy causality, overcome convergence...
It’s the grand plan of my future self,
all so I can shape the
ways of this world on my own.
You would go that far?!
Once you obtained the time machine,
what were you planning to do?!
Lintahlo... You fail to grasp
the essence of science.
The thing about scientists...
We experiment in hopes
that our theories prove true,
and observing just that is what we live for.
The future me has such a theory
and the past me will set out to prove it.
That’s all it is. It’s what I always do.
You’ll make a time paradox!
Aren’t you afraid of breaking
the world beyond repair?!
If that sort of thing does happen,
I’d like to see it for myself.
I guess if she’s dead, all that future
brainwashing doesn’t help all too much.
You...
You’re a true mad scientist!
I couldn’t ask for a better
compliment than that, Lintahlo!
Could you step out of my way now?
This place will be a battlefield before long.
With this time machine at the center of it all.
Battlefield?
There’s Dr. Nakabachi’s paper
who defected to Russia.
Plus, there’s the info regarding the
time machine I handed over to Stratfoc.
That information war evolves into both sides
showing up in force this very day, of all days.
History says the
time machine is destroyed here.
But it doesn’t exist for another 25 years
when it’s developed based on the theory.
Though, what if someone
stole it at the perfect time?
What if they fake its destruction
and went into the past?
Is that what your plan is?!
It’s been 10 odd years since meeting Kagari.
Such a long time...
—I’ve come so far, but it’s time—
—I hear...
I hear...
...the voice of God.
Get your hands off me.
It’s too early to get knocked out!
Kagari suffered a
thousand times worse than this!
Way worse! Way worse!
—She hurt way worse than this!
—Stop it, Suzuha!
Get up! You damn... You damn...!
Suzuha!
Let go! Don’t stop me!
That’s enough, Suzuha.
Dad...
If you kill the guy, you’re the same as him.
Kagari-chan...
Kagari-chan!
Kagari-chan? Look, it’s Suzu-san.
It’s the same hand that...
held mine when... I was... scared.
So warm...
Kagari...
I’m sorry, Big Sis Suzuha...
Sorry...
Kagari... Kagari!
Why?
Why did it come to this?
What the—
Run!
Mayuri!
It’s okay! She’s not hurt!
Find the professor!
This is...
Suzu-san, let’s go!
The time machine will be destroyed soon, right?
We have to go before that!
Go, and change the future!
Is that DURPA?!
For Kagari-chan too!
Get in!
Right!
W-Wait, Mayuri!
Okarin!
Why?
Why do you think you’ve got to do this?!
Mayuri! Mayuri!
Mayushii has to go!
Because, this is...
...Operation Arc-light!
Arc-light?
Big Sis Mayu!
Mayuri! Wait, Mayuri!
Suzuha...
Shit! Secure the target!
Owowow...
Is this seriously happening in Tokyo?!
Mayuri!
Here we go.
Right!
Mayuri!
This is... the time machine’s.
Did they not make it in time?
Suzuha...
Mayuri...
Okabe-san?
Mayuri!
Mayuri... Mayuri!
It’s still incomplete.
Why?
Why did this happen?
Okarin...
I... I chose this world line because
I thought it was the best choice!
Orihime-sama niwa narenai
I still can’t become your Orihime
This... This was the one and only
world line built upon Kurisu’s sacrifice!
Watashi no chikara ja sasaekirenai kedo
I don’t have the strength to support you, but even so
And yet... And yet, why?
Hanarebanare ga kowakute
I’m terrified of losing you for good
Why?
Why?!
Oinori wo suru yo
So I’ll pray for your happiness
Soremo ai nano kana?
Isn’t that also a form of love?
Read the mail
1 new mail
Mayuri
Read the mail
1 new mail
Mayuri
Read the mail
1 new mail
Mayuri
Read the mail
1 new mail
Mayuri
Mayuri?
Subete no, bamen ga koishisugite
I long for all the scenes, back in those days
Dear Okarin.
Tutturu! It’s Mayushii!
The truth is, I wanted to talk to you in person,
but I didn’t know if could get it all out.
Bokura wa mata ano basho he to
And so we head once again toward that place...
Plus, I was worried Okarin might
try to stop me, so I’ll just say it here.
Donna mabushii hikari no sekaisen mo
In that world line, shining with the most radiant light
I’m going with Suzu-san to the past.
Kanashimi toka yorokobi wakare mo atte
Where you said your most bittersweet farewell
You’ll probably be upset and are wondering why.
But, this is something I have to do.
Naita mama de anata no hoho wo tataku
I will strike your cheek, crying all the while
Because that day, I was the one who did it.
Sono shunkan nanika ga kawaru yo
Changing everything in that moment
No matter how bad things got,
my strong, strong Hikoboshi would
get back up with a great big laugh.
Me niwa utsuranai mamoru beki nanika he
To protect your vision not yet reflected in our eyes
But I’m the one who hid him
behind a bunch of dark clouds.
You see, I think I was wrong.
Inochi sae sasagu sore ga minna no sentaku
We will dedicate our lives—that is the choice of all of us
Everyone wasn’t pushing the
weight of the future solely on Okarin.
Steins Gate must be
something we all find together.
Everyone’s at your side.
Daru-kun’s there, Suzu-san’s there...
Ooinaru umi watatte
We will cross the vast ocean
...Luka-kun’s there,
Faris-chan’s there, Yuki-san’s there...
Tsuginaru taisetsu na bunkiten
Toward the next important divergence point
...and even Maho-san’s there too.
So now it’s my turn.
Atarashii mirai no monogatari no shujinkou he
So that someday, in a new future
After all, since I’m Lab Member 002,
this’ll be my first very big mission!
Itsuka aeru ne sono hi made
I can meet the protagonist of that story, but until then...
I’m sure Okarin will be worried,
but it’ll all be okay.
Besides, even if something does happen,
I know in my heart that you’ll come to save me.
The Hououin Kyouma I love so much will
come swooping in on a brand-new time machine.
That’s why I’ve decided to go.
I promise I’ll come back,
so just wait for me, okay?
I... love Hououin Kyouma.
Kirameku hoshi yozora ni te wo nobaseba
Whenever I stretch my hand out toward the sparkling stars in the night sky
But, guess what?
I love Okabe Rintaro even more!
Yomigaeru ne omoi mo nukumori no hi mo
Feelings and warm moments reawaken within me
MUWAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA
Afuredasu yo ano toki ano bamen de
Memories of those times, of those scenes, all come flooding back
Kimi no kotoba naitewaratta
All the words you spoke to me, all the times we laughed and cried
Kioku no subete ga kakikawaru toshitemo
Even if all our memories are rewritten,
Dejabu mitai ni kokoro no oku de yureteru
They’ll still waver deep within our hearts as déjà vu
I wish to meet my Hikoboshi
Mayushii