U-Um...
It’s great that Kagari-san
finally got her memories back.
Yeah... It sure is.
Mommy...
Um...
Hey, Kagari-san.
Chan!
Eh?
It’s Kagari-chan, right?
K-Kagari-chan?
What is it, Mommy?
Want to eat a banana with me?
Banana?
How about I feed it to you instead?
Huh? That’s okay, I can do it myself...
Aww...
When I used to feed you before,
it made Mommy so happy.
Th-Then, could you do it for me?
Yup!
Say ahh!
Okarin...
What?
What do you think? Could this be
a possible Yuri breakthrough?
It’s a tough one...
U-Um...
Could I ask you something?
How is Mayuri-chan her mommy?
Well...
Mommy, I love you!
This world is a false reality
It’s merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn’t merely something that’s expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
Wow! This is for me?!
Yup!
I’m so happy! Thank you, Mommy!
Sure!
I think it’s pretty amazing how well
Mayu-shi grasped the situation.
I feel like it’s less that she grasps it
and more that she’s just accepting it...
She’s Mayushii’s... daughter?
That’s right.
Huh?! Sh-She can’t be!
Mayushii hasn’t given birth to a kid yet!
I’m saying it’s not like that.
She came here along with Suzuha from the future.
From the future?
Mommy took me in because
I didn’t have any living relatives.
Mayushii did?
But, Mayushii doesn’t remember that at all...
Of course, you wouldn’t.
From your perspective,
that all happens in the distant future.
Mommy!
I’d worry for her sanity if
she wasn’t skeptical, you noob.
That’s true.
Okarin-san!
Look, look at this! How cool!
Hmm?
Ta-da!
Oh?
Mommy gave it to me!
They match! Neat, right?
Yeah, it sure is.
Man, Kagari-tan.
Your personality sure changed a bit.
Because her memories of the
future with Mayuri came back?
It’s like you’re so cheerful now...
and you’re so lively now.
Eh? You think?
I guess this must be her original personality.
Mayushii thinks this Kagari-sa—
Kagari-chan is wonderful too!
Really? I’m glad to hear it!
Ah! Where’s Big Sis Suzuha?
Now that you mention it...
She actually left a little while ago.
Oh, shoot!
I’ve got to hurry back to work!
Gotta go, Mommy! Bye!
See you later!
Hmm?
In the end, I guess only her
childhood memories came back.
Wasn’t she around six years old
when she became Mayu-shi’s daughter?
Supposedly.
But after that, in the year 2036,
she time traveled to the past
with Suzuha when she was 10.
Suzuha had to use the IBN 5100
in order to fix the Y2K problem.
So, she swung by 1975
before time traveling to 1998.
But that’s where Kagari-tan
got separated from her.
And the last thing she remembers
is 12 years later in 2010.
From after she was found collapsed
at the border of Chiba Prefecture.
Then the other day,
the shock from that accident may have
brought her childhood memories back again.
But from age 10 to 22, there’s a 12-year void.
Yeah...
Even for how peaceful a place Japan is,
there’s no way a 10-year-old girl
could survive here alone.
It’s only normal to think somebody,
somewhere, was taking care of her.
Even so, we’ve got no information to go on.
And Kiryu-shi is still investigating,
but there’s not a clue to be found...
Until she remembers what happened
on her own, is there’s nothing we can do?
If only there was a hint
or something we could look into...
Um...
I’m so sorry for coming late...
Huh?
Boss? Are you there?
He went out.
I see! In that case, I could’ve
spent more time with Mommy.
J-Just kidding! I would never skip work!
Oh, yeah. Big Sis Suzuha.
I got a matching smartphone case from Mommy!
Yeah? Good for you.
And um, she said we’ll go out somewhere for fun.
Why don’t you come with us too, Big Sis—
No, I’m good.
Why not?
I don’t have time to screw around.
Could it be... that you hate me or something?
Why would you think that?
Because, you say stuff like
that with a scary face.
I was born with this face.
Besides, I have a mission to do.
You looked happy enough
stuffing your face with curry.
Well that’s... You can’t fight
on an empty stomach!
Hmm?
What’s that face mean?
I was born with this face.
I don’t care if you play with
your mommy, but keep me out of it.
Must be nice to be you...
You’ve had all the time in the world
to play with your mom and dad in this era.
Say what?!
It’s true! You’ve been with Uncle Daru
and Yuki-san for half a year already!
But when it comes to me, I’m not allowed
to spend time and have fun with Mommy?!
You little...! Do you have any
idea how hard it’s been for me?!
I spent a ton of precious fuel
just searching for you!
I’m sorry, but—
Not once did you try to contact me!
And then you finally appear
but conveniently forget everything!
It’s not like I... Like I forgot
because I wanted to.
Besides, if it’s anyone’s fault,
it’s yours for abandoning me!
That day, if you hadn’t gone running off like
you did, I wouldn’t have been left all alone!
Wait, Kagari... What did you say?
You heard me! When we were walking
that day, you disappeared on me!
After that was so...
I was so helpless...
Oh?
The hell you two standing around for?
If your hands are free, go clean something!
Keep slacking like that and
you ain’t getting paid.
Kagari’s memory seems odd?
Well, that’s what I’ve heard from Suzuha.
It’s like, the stuff that Kagari-tan
remembers seems to be different
than how Suzuha remembers it going.
Then again, it’s from when she was little,
so her memory of things might not be perfect.
That’s true, but...
Hmm?
Kagari-san?
Ah, Mommy.
What’s wrong?
Ever since my memory came back,
everyone looks so troubled...
I’m thinking... maybe it’s better
if I hadn’t remembered?
Kagari-chan...
The causes of memory loss?
Yes. What’s more,
only part of it won’t come back.
Don’t you find that odd?
Yeah, that does seem a bit too convenient.
The thing is, I’m no expert.
I’m fine with that.
Please tell me anything you can think of.
To list off the normal reasons,
you can have an accident, illness,
or stress and emotional shock.
That about sums it up.
But if it’s not one of those,
could a third party have meddled
and done something artificially?
Is that what you’re thinking?
Well?
I don’t know...
But... it might... be just that.
Hmm...
In that case, only one thing comes to mind.
And that’s?
Brainwashing.
Mind control.
Mother
Goose
of
Diffractive
Recitativo
Fun for All Ages with Mozart
July 17–August 28
Uh...
You’re... still living here?
That’s it?
Mmm.
Found one
Within a 5km range
of where Shiina
Kagari collapsed
Within a 5km range
of where Shiina
Kagari collapsed
Just one place
A building that’s
not on records and
shouldn’t be there
A building that’s
not on records and
shouldn’t be there
Congrats
Uh-huh uh-huh.
There’s really something there?
We won’t know for sure unless we go.
What do you think?
Well, that doesn’t seem like you at all.
Yeah... I’m thinking I said too much.
In a way, I think it’s because I’m envious.
Of Kagari-tan?
Yeah...
If I could forget the whole mission...
Live freely, spoiled by everyone...
If you want to be spoiled,
here’s looking at you, kid.
Dummy.
Then again...
If you regret what you said,
why not just apologize to her?
I’m not very good at that
sort of thing. It’s the timing...
If only... I had an opportunity.
So, yeah. That’s why
I’m thinking of throwing a party!
A party?
Yup! To celebrate Kagari-chan
getting back her memories.
Kagari-chan?
Yeah! But, I don’t know...
Do you think Kagari-chan would like that?
It’s a great idea.
If you’re planning it, I’m sure she’ll love it.
Really? Then I’ll let everyone know
and start making preparations!
Mayushii’s gonna be busy!
Ready to investigate
Can leave tomorrow
morning~
Long drive is going to be
a pain
Fun for All Ages with Mozart
Tomorrow night?
Yeah. Since it’s a Sunday,
can you come to the lab at five?
Of course, I can.
Oh... But if you’re there, I’ll ask
the boss to let me go early and come—
Ah... You’re not allowed to come early.
Eh? Why not?
Well that’s... a secret!
I’ve got it. Must be a party.
Eh?!
Wh-Why say that?
Because, whenever you act
suspicious like this, it’s always a party.
So? Am I right?
W-We’ll just see about that...
A-Anyways, you can’t come before five o’clock!
Okay.
Oh, and...
Mind if I invite Suzu-san?
Why are you asking me that?
That’s because... You and Suzu-san
haven’t been talking much lately.
I don’t know what happened between you, but...
Both you and Suzu-san are very precious to me,
so I just want you two to get along.
Mommy...
All right.
Big Sis Suzuha has been through a lot too.
Mmm...
Tomorrow, when I come
and meet her, I’ll apologize.
And hopefully, we can talk
things through from the top.
Yeah!
Looks like somebody splurged yet again, nya!
The food and drinks are all taken care of, nya!
They’ll deliver right before it starts, nya!
And we’ve got enough plates and cups.
Hello...
Suzu-san! Thanks for coming!
Y-Yeah...
Thanks for the message.
By the way, where are the others?
Daru-kun is out shopping for a
few things with Yuki-san and the others.
Okarin has been gone on
some business since this morning,
but he said he’ll be back for the party.
In that case, it’s brainwashing.
Brainwashing?
I don’t know the exact method how they’re
able to make or break memories as they please.
But using drugs or some sort of technique,
they say memories can be forcibly repressed.
What I’m saying,
is that it’s not entirely impossible.
If there’s guys out there who
did something like that to Kagari...
Congrats Kagari-chan!
Hello!
Welcome!
You all made it, nya!
Whew... No more shopping, I beg you...
Yoo-hoo! We’re here!
Hello!
Thanks for having me!
Nae-sama! Welcome, Nae-sama!
Hello, Mr. Smileybear.
Bear?
Wh-Whoa! Aren’t you going too fast?!
Mountain days are short.
If we don’t hurry, it’ll get dark.
And dark... is dangerous.
Huh? Eh? Ahhh!
Can you please try to drive safe?!
All right. It’s safer if we get there faster.
Noooo!
Sweets Akihabara
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Sweets Akihabara
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Sweets Akihabara
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Sweets Akihabara
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Sweets Akihabara
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Sweets Akihabara
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Sweets Akihabara
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
Shohei Bridge
2 Chome Sotokanda
Kanda Shrine
Mansei Bridge
Kanda Post Office
This way.
Eh?
It’s really up ahead?
This is...
It seems like it was used until recently.
Huh? It’s got to be years since anyone—
A guise.
Eh?
It’s scattered around to look like that,
but the glass and fragments are relatively new.
It’s been half a year,
maybe one year at the longest.
Want to investigate deeper?
Let’s go.
Thank you very much.
It’s a bit early, but...
No big deal!
I wonder if Big Sis Suzuha will like it or not?
So, what are you saying, Doctor?
Kagari-chan still needs more treatment?
She may appear to be completely healed, but...
In order to completely cure
her PTSD brought about by war,
it takes a significant amount of time.
But I hate the treatment.
It makes my head hurt.
Can you tough it out a little more?
Mommy will be right with you, okay?
Okay... I will.
Come on, Kagari-chan.
Let’s do our best again today.
I... hear it...
The voice... of God...
Kaga-nyan is late, nya.
She promised to come straight here...
I wonder if something happened?
Mayushii will try calling again.
Right.
I’m going to look for her.
Suzuha!
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
No signal
Okabe-kun.
There is peace, the truth within us
What’s up? What was that sound?
I found a switch,
Emptiness erodes your heart
pressed it, and found this.
A hidden passage?
’Cause you’re free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Okabe-kun.
Wake up now, it’s time to lead new souls
In here.
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Orbit of photon and universe
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
Mommy MommyMommy
Mommy    Mommy  Mommy
I miss you
I miss you mommy
Mommy       Mommy Mommy
Mommy Mommy
I am just a part of its plan
Mommy       Mommy Mommy
Mommy Mommy
Th-This is...
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Kagari was... here after all?
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
But... Who would have done this?!
And for what purpose?!
The last game
Hello?
Thank goodness you picked up! Okarin!
What’s wrong, Mayuri?
Listen, it’s Kagari-chan! Kagari-chan is...
She’s missing?!