Amadeus and Salieri...
Kurisu and me...
One was gifted with
natural talent, Amadeus Mozart.
The other viewed him as
a lifelong rival, Antonio Salieri.
K331.
Mozart's Piano Sonata No. 11
in A Major, first movement.
You like Mozart's music?
I dabble in it sometimes.
I like the quote “Death means not
getting to listen to Mozart anymore.”
I've never heard of that one.
Strictly speaking, there's no record
that Einstein ever said those words.
You see, I think it's a very logical statement.
Logical?
After all, you can't listen
to Mozart if you're dead.
Isn't that much obvious?
Yes, it is obvious.
If you die, you can't listen.
The statement is true.
See? Logical, right?
July 28, 2010...
Makise Kurisu left this world.
Amadeus and Salieri...
Those two hold a very special meaning to me.
I loved Kurisu...
I respected Kurisu...
I aspired to be like Kurisu...
I...
This world is a false reality
It's merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn't merely something that's expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
Tokyo Denki University
Hmm?
Global Brain Science
Organization Office Prep Room.
A fundraising plea by Leskinen.
If everyone who read this donated
just one dollar, I could eat a can of oden.
Oden
The Professor never
gets tired of joking around...
Yo, Maho! Welcome to
our powered-up prep room!
By that you mean the table and couch?
Yes! It is said, “Keeping it simple is the
secret on the long journey towards truth.”
And whose quote is that?
That would be mine.
So? How's Amadeus?
I just finished running the final checks.
We should be able to launch without issue.
Should I start it?
Of course!
Long time no see, Senpai.
Well? No problems so far?
Nope. Not as far as I'm aware, at the least.
All right. I'll let Okabe-san know we're good.
Okay. Though even if you say I'm restored,
I'm not sure he'll want to talk to me...
You think?
I'm sure he enjoys talking
to you a whole lot more.
You seem to like it too.
Would you stop saying stuff like that?
I'm telling you, it's not true!
After lengthy observation and analysis,
I'm certain that I'm correct.
How so? You're just letting delusions
of love run amok in your head.
I sure missed you two going at it.
Well, shall we get our meeting started?
Pandora of Provable Existence
Sure!
What the hell is this?
This room's unbelievable!
Oh, Okabe-san? You're here early.
Why are you here?
Sheesh! I told you once
already >_<
Hmph!     Pout!
I was asked to be Dr.
Hiyajo's bodyguard~
Sheesh! I told you once
already >_<
Hmph!     Pout!
I was asked to be Dr.
Hiyajo's bodyguard~
Sheesh! I told you once
already >_<
Hmph!     Pout!
I was asked to be Dr.
Hiyajo's bodyguard~
Sheesh! I told you once
already >_<
Hmph!     Pout!
Sheesh! I told you once
already >_<
Where the hell did the room go?
It's worse than it was a few days ago.
The lapse of time changes
both people and things.
What do you think? Functional, right?
I could go exploring in here!
Anyways, Amadeus is all restored now.
Is it?
What will it be? If you want to
keep testing, I can reset it for you.
Yeah, please.
Are you sure? Really?
A lot has happened since then...
I've been thinking...
It's about time I moved forward.
I wonder why Faris told me to bring
Mayuri along when I came?
Because Mayushii has a brilliant mind!
I think I get Faris-chan!
She must've wanted this room to be cleaned!
And if you're here, it'll get cleaned?
More like, if Mayushii comes over,
she'll think to bring that person along!
That person?
Sergeant Clean!
I will be your drill instructor!
Refer to me as Sergeant Clean!
You mean Nae, right?
Listen up! Until this room is clean,
you are nothing more than inchworms!
All you're good for is squirming
around on top of leaves!
You're the lowest life form on Earth!
Do you understand?!
What the hell is this?
When it comes to cleaning,
Nae-chan's personality changes a little.
That's putting it lightly...
But when cleaning's over, maybe she'll
open up and act all mushy and sweet!
Why the hell are you here?
Who was that?! Which of you
said something creepy?!
I-It was me!
What are you smirking for?!
Listen up! From now on, you're Mr. Smileybear!
Got it, Mr. Smileybear?!
Y-Yes, Nae-sama!
That's more like it, Mr. Smileybear.
Now go sweep up and down
the hall 10 times in 30 seconds!
Nae-sama, yes, Nae-sama!
He's enjoying every second of this...
What exactly are we doing here?
Until we're done, Hiyajo-san
and Kiryu-san are supposed to leave.
Eh?
No one told me.
Orders from the honyaner. Can't refuse.
—Not nearly good enough, Mr. Smileybear!
—Well? Did you figure out anything new?
—It's not?
No progress, sadly.
I've got a guess about the culprits,
but no way to know for sure.
Can't let it end up like SERN...
SERN?
Uh, that's... Forget it...
Still, I find it hard to believe.
I never imagined Kurisu
was researching time machines...
It's the truth.
I didn't say you were lying.
On one hand it seems crazy,
but nothing from her surprises me.
Salieri?
It's my user name at university.
Didn't I tell you?
Yeah... Does it have some special meaning?
Not really...
I see...
Antonio Salieri.
The man whose life was thrown into chaos
by Amadeus Mozart... Do you know him?
Like the movie, right? I've heard of it.
Salieri had a promising future as a musician,
but he grew envious of Mozart's talents
and was driven into despair.
In the end, the hounding and
pressure from Salieri led to his demise.
Hiyajo-san...
Don't worry. I don't believe
that's the case myself, but...
Okabe-san?
It's been a while.
You haven't changed a bit.
Same goes for you.
Of course not. I'm AI.
Subject: Regarding
mmmiiiiiLaptop
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
Subject: Regarding Laptop
Retrieving from locker tonight.
Will contact again once analysis
is complete.
I don't know... It just doesn't feel right.
I'll have to fix it to my liking later.
The others will kill you
if they hear you say that.
Okarin! Sorry to keep you!
She fell asleep, huh?
Yup! Being Sergeant Clean
must take it all out of her.
Want me to carry her?
Sure, if you want to eat a full-powered
straight right from Tennouji-san.
Full-powered straight right! Huff huff...
All that drill training
must've scrambled his head...
So... If you can't find something
you need, let me know!
All right. Where are Faris-san and Kiryu-san?
They said they'll be right back.
Kyouma!
I said don't call me that.
We're back.
Yeah... What's with the bag?
She said she wanted to shop.
Sorry, but tonight is no boys allowed!
Not even Kyouma, nya!
No boys allowed?
Yup, nya! The operation
in store for tonight is...
Meow!
The All-Night Cinderella Girls Secret Party!
So sleepy someone slips secrets, nya!
What's wrong, you two?
Where's your excitement, nya?
Come on! I even picked out some pricey
ice cream and cake for us, nya!
Well, all right...
The thing about Maho-nyan is,
she's cute like a doll so
everything looks good on her, nya.
Quit calling me that.
Huh?
Kiryu-san?
Moe-nyan finally laughed, nya!
S-Stop it...
Wh-What incredible boobs, nya!
These are just begging to be tickled, nya!
Stop it!
Uh-oh! This is making me feel naughty, nya!
—N-No, stop! Ah! S-Stop!
—I think she likes it!
I'm getting some juice, nya.
What the heck...
What are you writing?
A memo... for my novel.
A novel? You're writing one?
Mmm, because I'm not special in any way.
Practically anyone can take my place.
What are you talking about?
You are you. Nobody can replace you.
But...
You can't be replaced,
so don't belittle yourself.
If you compare yourself to others and
live your whole life feeling inferior, that's so...
Never mind...
I think she likes it, nya...
S-Stop...
A lot has happened since then...
It's about time I moved forward.
Why are you so...
This circuit board pattern is
so pretty, it's like a work of art!
Is this an IFX008 image sensor?!
What's it doing here?!
Y-Yeah...
Who knew Akihabara had places like this?!
This is the true Maho-senpai.
Who would've thought
she's so obsessed with parts?
I love putting things together.
When I was little, I made
Japanese plastic models all the time.
Did you build a germanium radio?
Burned myself soldering one a good bit.
It happens to everyone!
I know!
Uh, I think it's only you two...
Why did I not come here sooner?
You should've said it was like this!
I had no idea you'd like it this much.
Are there any more places like that one?
There used to be stores like
that all over the place, but lately...
More importantly, didn't you want to talk?
It can wait.
You're not busy, right?
Let's hang out some more.
Well, that's fine with me, but...
Oh!
Check it out!
Hmm?
An @channel character?
@channel?
Guess what? Kurisu had one
of these characters in her bedroom!
Kurisu did? She had one sent to America?
Senpai! Say no more!
That's a closet @channeler for you...
Wh-What are you talking about?
What's an @channeler?
Nullpo...
Gah!
Okabe!
You deserved it.
Care if I give it a shot?
Um... I've just gotta use this arm
and drop it over the hole, right?
Here goes nothing...
Argh! Why?! Why is it
breaking the laws of physics?!
Otherwise they wouldn't profit from it.
But I'm pretty sure I loosened it up!
Next time I'll get it for sure!
I'm grabbing some change!
She's totally suckered in...
This is no time to be saying that!
Huh?
This is where you prove
you're a man, Okabe-san!
M-Me?!
Good! With this much I should be able...
Huh?
An employee came by and loosened it a bit.
You can have it.
Are you sure?
There's no point in me keeping it.
Then, in that case...
You wanted it that badly?
After Kurisu passed away...
Her mother knew Kurisu liked it so much,
so she put it in her room as a decoration.
But it was burned in the fire, so...
I had no idea...
That's why I want to give this
to Kurisu's mother as a present.
Is that okay?
Of course. That'd be nice...
Uh, wanna go inside?
There's racing games too!
I had no idea we were there so long.
Man, I had no idea you were
such a pro at racing games.
I might've got a bit carried away...
What should we do next?
Grab a bite or something?
No... It's already getting pretty late.
But there's somewhere I have to visit
before I go back to America...
This place, huh?
Yeah... The place where
Makise Kurisu lost her life.
The last place she was...
If you don't want to, just tell me where.
I can go in alone.
No...
It's so quiet in here.
Most of the shops have moved already,
since it's going to be rebuilt.
It's not really used much anymore.
This way.
Right in here.
I see... So it was right here...
Kurisu...
I'm not a physicist or anything,
so I don't know the details
of the theory of relativity, but...
If space and time are unified,
why can we move around in space,
but not move freely through time?
Right now, I stand in the same
spatial axis where Kurisu died.
And yet, just because the time axis is
a little off, I can't stop it from happening.
You can't stop it.
Eh?
Even if you returned to the same time axis...
...you can't change anything.
What makes you so sure?
I discussed it with Kurisu.
I see...
With Kurisu...
Okabe-san?
Okabe-san!
Sorry...
I'm sorry. It's my fault for lacking delicacy.
You cared for Kurisu so much that...
No, don't worry about it.
Hey... Did you really just
meet her at a seminar?
It doesn't seem that way at all.
From time to time,
I wonder how long it could've been.
One month? Two months? No...
You talk like you knew her well beyond that.
That's...
How do you know so much about Kurisu?
I...
Because I... Kurisu...
I'm sorry.
I understand.
I can tell something went on
you don't want to talk about.
That's enough for me.
Hiyajo-san...
Every time I see you,
I think the same thing...
Why do you always look so sad?
It's the same thing
when you talk about Kurisu.
It's the same when you talk with everyone.
As if you're regretting some choice...
As if struggling alone against something...
And then there's Mayuri-san and me...
It's like you're trying
to protect us from something.
And the thing is, we were really attacked...
Is that what it seems like to you?
Yeah...
I'm not going to ask you
to tell me everything, but...
I want to support and
empower that feeling of yours, so...
So?
I promised myself
I wouldn't tell anybody, but I will.
I...
I actually have it.
Kurisu's...
Makise Kurisu's legacy.
Kurisu's... legacy?
Yes...
Her notebook computer.
With all her research data...
With her theories... with her private data too.
Her own computer.
The thief that broke into
my hotel must've been after that.
Where is it?
I can't figure out her password,
so I'm having a trustworthy source analyze it.
You can't!
That computer is Pandora's Box!
It mustn't be opened!
The data inside is a curse that leads
to the destruction of the world!
What do you mean?
I told you already!
The race for a time machine is what
makes Russia and America fight one another!
Both countries are after the data and will
do whatever it takes to get their hands on it!
It's the spark that ignites World War III!
World War III?!
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
'Cause you're free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now, it's time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just a part of its plan
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
The last game