What the—?!
Hey! What was that?!
I'll raise your rent!
Window! Open a window!
Okey-dokey!
Never saw that coming...
Why did it start spewing fire?!
Maybe 'cuz I swiped it from a pile of trash.
Good grief! I'll turn on the AC.
You can't! If we run both,
the breaker will trip.
What a dump. And you call this a lab?
We only say that because
Okarin gave it the name.
Kurisu actually managed to put it
together in a shoddy lab like this?
Tokyo Denki University
This “vision” we call life
Is yet unaware that it's an illusion
Even antinomic paradoxes
Can be tricked into existence by an infinite amount of worldlines
If the natural trajectory dictated by emotional decisions
Supersedes even common sense
Then my—and merely my—
Suffering, and my mistakes, will still neatly follow the algorithm
Words and tokens of love—memories growing ever stronger
Guarantee I will not leave you behind a second time
I am forever by your side
We're joined together as one
Out of this quantum entanglement, “0” will manifest
Therefore...
As seen on page 21 of the textbook, direct and
indirect speech can, depending on the words—
We'll pick this back up next time.
By the way, Okabe-kun?
Y-Yeah?
Tokyo Denki University
Ah, Okarin!
Sorry to keep you.
Don't be. The professor wanted to talk?
Yeah. Seems like he's interested in Daru too.
They want to meet him.
Really? That's our super hacka for you!
Wanna grab something to eat?
Huh? Not going to the lab?
Daru-kun's there, I think.
I can just message him.
But, I bet he'd be happier
to talk with you in person.
Plus, so much has happened
with Daru-kun and Yuki-san.
You know what I think?
He needs you there for him.
Yeah, but next week—
Understood
If you find out anything, let me
know
Nothing yet
If you find out anything, let me
know
Nothing yet
Your normie life sure is taking off.
I wouldn't say that's true.
But, since I got the chance,
I might as well try to study overseas.
I see... So it's something that you want to do.
Yeah...
In that case, I think you should go for it.
It might work out for Daru too.
Plus, if I end up transferring,
I'll be able to lend Hiyajo-san a hand.
It works out best for everyone... this way.
Oh, right! Look, look, it's Suzu-san!
Don't you think she looks so silly?
Yeah, she sure does.
Oh, and this lab coat is the one
Okarin used to wear, by the way.
The new one is stored safe and sound.
It's no big deal... Could've used it.
Eh?
But, when I tried to give it to
Suzu-san before, you got super angry...
Did I really?
It's just a cheap coat.
It's green.
Mayushii just remembered I've got
something I need to take care of.
Really?
Hey, Okarin?
What?
No, never mind.
See you!
1 new RINE message
Stop it!
It's not right to force him.
Why? Why do you push the weight
of the future solely on Okarin?
Sorry, but I forgot my umbrella.
It's okay! Luckily, Mayushii was
walking around outside too!
We're sharing an umbrella like lovers!
You're embarrassing me...
Wow! What a huge Tanabata decoration!
It's that season already.
Mayushii does it every year too!
I even buy a branch of bamboo!
Oh, really? Do you write and hang a wish?
Yup! Ever since I was a child,
I wished I could become Orihime.
After all, Mayushii is a romantic chuunibyou.
You will become that, for sure.
Eh?
Okabe-san's Orihime.
Eh? Hey now... Mayushii never
said anything about Okarin.
But, Mayuri-chan, you've always
supported him for so long.
You're perfect for the job.
You're wrong...
Mayushii isn't the one inside Okarin's heart.
Eh?
Okarin's Orihime...
won't be shining anymore.
Mayuri-chan...
You're very kind, Luka-kun.
No, but I'm not...
It's just, this is all I'm able to do...
Damn heat...
In just a few minutes,
I wanna try that experiment again.
'Kay...
Also, if you dare to sneak a peek
at me, I'll call Suzuha-san.
Don't you worry about that.
I don't even think my heart could take it.
Uh!
Huh? Hey, Daru?
O-Okarin!
O-Okabe-san? Crap!
Crap!
Hey, Daru! Mayuri? Anyone in there?
J-Just a minute!
Huh?
Come on in.
Eroge again?
N-No. I-I mean, yeah...
I was just finishing up when—
Please, don't say it.
Smells like smoke.
Uh! Um...
I was heating up a bento when
the microwave I got blew up on me.
Blew up? We'll get evicted
if you're not careful.
Anyways, what brings you here?
Mayu-shi isn't around.
Uh, well...
Kiryu-san got some info that said
Kagari might be in the area.
Know anything?
N-No, nothing at all.
Done with the PC?
Uh... J-Just a second!
All yours.
Quit it with the illegal stuff.
I've got some good news for you.
But I refuse!
I haven't even said anything yet!
Yesterday, I had lunch with Professor Leskinen.
He was saying—
Is this about going overseas?
Just listen till the end.
He was saying him and the other
professors were interested in you.
Viktor Chondria University has a computer
science department and they want you there too.
Me?
With skills like yours, you'll get by.
I'm a super hacker, for crying
out loud, of course I would.
Don't want to?
It's not that I don't want to, but...
Given the situation,
that's not exactly on my mind...
Suzuha wanting to go back to the past and all...
Huh?
channel
Something up on @channel?
No, but there's a bunch of rumors about
the Chiba facility I went to with Kiryu-san.
On the occult board, I bet. Those guys
just make shit up for a living, I swear.
—Don't believe anything they say.
—Hmm?
253 Name:KuriGohan and Kamehameha[sage]  ID FT2Sm
What you're saying makes no sense. Are you a normie
or something? Your statement is asinine and absurd.
This handle name...
Name:
S
Sa
Sal
Sali
Salie
Salier
Salieri
Salieri'
Salieri's
Uh...
You idiot!
Is that a bunch of bananas?
No, uh... Um, well...
S-Suzuha made me... It's a banana diet, okay?
That's so...
Okarin, wait! Um...
That takes me back...
Mayuri used to get so angry and say
we shouldn't be wasting food like that...
Y-Yeah...
Uh!
What's this?
What is this?!
Well, that secret didn't last long...
So much for trying to keep it
under wraps for a while...
It's PhoneWave (name subject to change) Unit-02.
You actually... rebuilt it?
I wasn't sure to call it Version 2 or—
Who gives a shit about the name?!
Really? That's not like you at all, Okarin.
You made a huge deal about naming Future
Gadgets with round table meetings and—
Did you forget about everything I told you?!
It's too dangerous! This thing shouldn't exist!
But, wait... We have to make a time
machine in the future, don't we?
The way I see it, working on this
is the first step in researching—
Daru!
I explained this to you over and over!
You should know what it's responsible for!
You should know what
this thing put me through!
Because this was made, Mayuri gets killed!
Because this was made,
Kurisu has to be sacrificed!
your own daughter even killed herself!
Because this was made!
Okarin...
If you still don't get it, I'll tell you again!
Are you that big of an idiot?!
Will you not understand unless you go
through it yourself, you stupid idiot?!
You're the idiot!
Okabe Rintaro!
Hiyajo-san? Why are you here?
Eh? Uh...
That just happened on impulse...
Impulse?
Legal loli for the win!
One look and I'll sue you!
Sorry to make you wait.
So you're saying you were hiding
from me this whole time?
I was.
Is that why you came to Japan?
Yes... The real reason I came was to work on the
terribly named PhoneWave (name subject to change).
Wrong. Hashida-san wasn't
the one who asked me.
Maho-tan...
While it's true that he contacted me first,
he was doing it for Suzuha-san.
For Suzuha?
You should know, Okarin.
The time machine only has enough
remaining fuel to jump back one year.
It's not long until the day Makise-shi died.
After that, we won't be able to go back
and change the worldline branch.
So...
If we fail and have to try again,
we'll need the time leap machine.
So, you pulled Hiyajo-san into it?
At first, I was hoping I could somehow finish it
all on my own, but in the end, I was stumped...
And you? You admit to helping?
I do, that's right.
But why?!
I explained it to you too!
You should know what D-Mails brought about!
You should know what changing the past means!
And you intend to repeat that?!
Don't you get it?!
If you go and change the past,
it means taking away somebody's life!
It means killing Mayuri!
Wait. That's not what I—
Saving Kurisu means Mayuri dies!
It's unavoidable! No matter what
you do or how hard you try!
You trying to complete that machine
means you're trying to change the past!
You'll throw away Kurisu's sacrifice for this
world and go right back to an Alpha worldline!
You'd be killing off Mayuri!
Do you wanna be a murderer?!
Okarin!
Apologize! Apologize to Maho-tan, right now!
Wa— Hashida-san!
I get what you're saying, Okarin!
I can't even begin to imagine all the suffering
that you've been through, but still!
That doesn't give you any right to
trample over everyone's feelings!
Hashida-san, enough!
Suzuha came here to stop
World War III from happening!
Maho-tan cared so much about Makise-shi
that she came to work on the time leap machine!
Nobody's doing it for shits and giggles!
Mayu-shi's no different!
You have no idea what
she's been through for you!
That's enough!
Let's clean up your face.
Come on!
Daru... hit me...
It's because of the dumb things you said.
My bad.
I didn't mean to say that...
I know.
I think better of him now.
For getting angry for someone else...
He's usually so gentle, it stings even more...
Just so you know, we weren't trying to do
anything else but build the time leap machine.
We never considered sending D-Mails.
I see...
And yet, you still look disappointed.
I think the rain stopped.
Let's get some fresh air.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
The way I see it, this world exists
because of a choice Kurisu made.
Because of Kurisu, Mayuri can live safely.
I must protect that choice.
That is this world's law.
This world's law?
In reliving time, I learned one thing...
That certain events converge
as if orchestrated by God.
Trying to change them... it's challenging God.
And God does not tolerate human arrogance.
Perhaps... I may be a scientist,
but I have no plans to provoke God.
In that case...
However, I think you're wrong
about God and the laws of this world.
Hiyajo-san...
If there are in fact laws dictating our world...
If all things are decided
like fate by some God...
There's no point in our living, no point
in our trying, and no point in our choices.
I'm not saying everything's decided!
Just that some things are!
Then tell me.
Tell me what can't be changed by the laws
of this world, and what can be changed.
That's...
Any scientist would ask that question.
The way I see it, the laws
of this world are a formula.
It's just a formula that
makes this world possible.
There's no saying we can't solve it.
People have wills, use their minds,
make decisions, and act.
That makes a world what it is.
It may not be an easy feat, but if we painstakingly
work towards a solution, surely, we can solve it.
But, going back in time is—
Steins Gate.
I thought about what Suzuha-san told me.
Shiina Mayuri lives, Makise Kurisu lives,
and World War III is avoided.
If that's what you call Steins Gate,
to me, that's the formula.
It's all about finding that one solution.
Hiyajo-san...
This world is full of infinite possibilities.
Among them, it's there somewhere.
So find it! Look and look again!
One thousand, ten thousand, one million times!
Find a solution to Steins Gate!
Just like you and Kurisu used to!
—I can't!
—Okabe-san!
It's easy for you to say that,
but it rips apart my heart!
You don't know what it's like
to fail over and over!
I do!
You don't!
I do! Plenty of times next to Kurisu!
Thousands and ten thousands of times!
This is different than research!
Formulas don't have feelings!
But all of them have been solved
by humans! And you know it!
Okarin?
I'm sorry...
Is Okarin... hopeless?
No, there's still hope.
Really?
I lost to Kurisu in our experiments,
lost in our theories, lost in fame...
But I looked at myself in the mirror
and kept pushing on.
Because if I gave up, it's all over.
Then I'd never be able to win.
Right now, Okabe-san...
He has the same face I used to have.
Mayuri?
O-Okarin? Why are you here?
Well, I was just passing by.
You?
Yeah... Something like that.
We used to come here all the time.
Yeah...
That was back before Daru-kun was around.
Once Mayushii was done with school,
I used to wait in the lab by myself.
Even though I was alone,
it didn't seem that lonely at all.
It felt happy...
But now, the lab... It seems lonely.
Nothing's changed, right?
It's the same me, Daru, and you.
I wonder if that's true.
I feel like the lab was packed with
more people... More lively and fun...
That can't... be true...
But...
Hey, Okarin?
Hmm?
I wonder if Mayushii made the wrong choice...
If I should have sent you off instead...
Mayuri?
Okarin... Maybe you should have
gone to Makise-san... To save her...
But instead of that, you gave up
on everything to save Mayushii.
Because of me, you stopped coming to the lab...
And you always look like you're suffering...
You're wrong!
But...
You heard, right? Us talking at the lab...
But, it's true...
Don't think that!
Don't think about anything,
Mayuri! Don't think about it!
But...
All is well, okay?!
Right now, all is well with everything!
I don't want anything to
destroy this time we have!
Then why?!
Eh?
Then why?! Why do your eyes
look like you're suffering?!
Ever since that one day, it's like
you've been suffering so much...
You know Orihime?
It's the star called Vega.
But, guess what? Overseas,
they call it something else too...
It's the Arc-light of the Sky.
Mayuri...
Altair
of
the
Point
at
Infinity
Baibureeshion todokanai emooshion
Vibration, an undelivered emotion
Hello Amadeus, I'm waiting for your call
Kono basho wa reiyaado no you ni
This place exists as a sequence of layers
Tagenteki, The world in the world
Of worlds recursing within worlds
Toki wa fukagyaku nanoni
Although time is irreversible
Michi naru sekuta
These sectors remain unaccessed
Marude furasshu fowaado naze?
Why did I receive this vision of a kiss
Kissu no bijon
Like a flash-forward?
Konna ni chikakute tohoumonai kyori
It came from so close—an outrageously large distance
Kasanariau rogosu musuu no “zero” or “one”
I can only conclude that our existence is defined by “0”s and “1”s
Watashi wa koko ni iru yo
In which I can be found right here
Tell you my feelings I keep inside
I'll tell you my feelings that I keep inside
Kodoku no mama kakaetekita
I remain in solitude, while in hold of
Kazoekirenai mugen no yunibaasu
A countless number of infinitely expansive universes
Dakara sou ima dake wa
That's why I'll make sure
Anata no asu anata no tame ni
For the sake of your tomorrow
Uchuu naru kami no world boutoku
That the blasphemy of the God ruling this universe
Kurikaesanai de
Will never be repeated
There is inside worldline
There is inside world layer