Christmas Party?
Yup! I'm getting everyone
together to come to the lab.
It'd be really great if you all could come!
Even me?
Are you sure?
Fubuki-san, Kaede-san, and Yuki-san too.
You're my cosplay comrades.
Of course, you can come! The more the merrier!
I'll make you Santa costumes too,
so you have to come!
Really?
Even though you're using all this stuff
to make our Winter ComiMa outfits?
Huhu... Mayushii is going all out.
I'm making costumes you'll love,
so look forward to it!
Ooh! That's my bride! Marry me!
Fubuki-chan's excited.
You're going to wear one too, right?
A Santa costume...
Huh? But Mayushii specializes
in making outfits, not—
Objection!
I'm with Yuki-san! That's such a waste!
That's right.
Besides, I bet Okabe-san wants
to see Mayuri-chan in a costume too.
Okarin does?
Okarin-san is...?
Ah, that's Mayushii's boyfriend.
Wah? That's not true.
Okarin and Mayushii aren't like that.
Yeah, yeah...
You two get along so well,
I find it hard to believe you.
I'm serious.
Because...
Okarin already has somebody he likes.
Really?
Yup!
Mayushii and Okarin get along really
well because we're childhood friends.
This world is a false reality
It's merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn't merely something that's expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
Protocol
of
the
Two-sided
Gospel
Tokyo Denki University
Building 7
I thought I told you not
to call me during class.
But when I contacted you,
that was during your break.
What?
I made sure to check the class
schedule on your university's website.
I knew you were ignoring me.
I've got stuff I'm dealing with, all right?
What is this so-called stuff?
Well, that's...
You should at least come up
with a good excuse ahead of time.
Anyways, quit calling me until I pick up.
It's because you can't even
keep a single promise with me.
Promise?
Don't you remember?
You said you would take me to this lab of yours.
We might call it a lab,
but we just screw around there.
Still...
The original me went there before, didn't they?
Well...
You're so evasive. Which is it?
Incoming Call:
Mayuri
Got a call. I'm hanging up.
Hello?
Ah, Okarin?
Guess what? Fubuki-chan and the others
said they can make it to the Christmas party.
Really? That's great.
And um...
I bought so much stuff for making outfits,
I was wondering if you could help
me carry all of it back home?
All right.
Can we meet at the lab after my lecture?
Yup!
I'll be waiting for you!
Okarin said he would come!
That's wonderful, nya!
Now it's just down to Suzu-san...
Did you tell her, nya?
Yeah...
But I'm not really sure if she'll come.
Isn't she always at the lab anyways, nya?
Yeah, but whenever somebody shows up,
she always runs off somewhere.
It'll all work out, nya!
Leave it to Faris, nya!
Oh? So, this is Akihabara?
It's rude to stare at my phone and walk.
I'm hanging up.
Wait. If you hold the camera so I can see,
you don't have to look at the screen.
Okay.
Oh?
Oh! Wait... Never mind.
It's a bit messier than I imagined.
Radikan?
Ah!
Hmph! What are you doing?!
H-Hey!
Ah!
Oh? If it isn't Okabe.
Hello!
It's been a while.
Who's that?
Be quiet.
Man, how the times have changed.
You're a legit college student now.
Keep it up, champ.
Just how much of a slacker were you?
Shut up!
Huh?
This is the lab.
This place?
It's filthy.
That's all you've got to say?
Sorry, let me rephrase that.
It's full of junk!
Ugh...
Laboratories tend to be messy
wherever you go, but this is overdoing it.
Told you it wouldn't be anything
like you thought it would be.
Looks more like wreckage than a lab.
This place gives
Maho-senpai's room a run for its money.
Should you be blabbering private info like that?
Could you please say something to her too?
Tell that girl to go clean her room.
Ugh, if I told her that, she'd bite my head off.
Still...
I always yearned for this...
to share a room with people.
With our own personal forks
and spoons and stuff.
Oh! You're already here, Okarin!
Tutturu!
Are you listening to music?
Is that your friend? I'd like—
Bye.
Hey! I—
You were on a call?
Don't worry about it.
Is this what you meant?
That's a lot of luggage.
Because I'm making outfits for
Winter ComiMa and some Santa costumes too.
The Christmas Party? Is everyone coming?
Yup!
Fubuki-chan, Kaede-san, Yuki-san,
Luka-kun, and Faris-chan.
Even Yuki-san?
Of course!
You know what Mayushii thinks?
Daru-kun and Yuki-san are perfect for each other!
Fubuki-chan said,
“No! No way is that ever happening!”
Searching for this is your and my first mission.
Um... O-Okey-dokey?
Good answer.
Oh, it's just Big Sis Rumi.
Hmm? Big Sis Rumi?
Who's that, nya?
Faris is Faris, nya!
If you don't show your face once in a while,
people will worry about you, nya.
If I go there, Mom—
I mean, it's more relaxing being alone.
I brought you snacks, nya!
All of your favorites, nya!
They won't expire until tomorrow,
so take your time and enjoy, nya!
Thanks.
How is Daru's time machine research going, nya?
He's doing his best, but...
Not so easy is it, nya?
Sorry for all the trouble.
It's fine, nya.
Faris does nothing more than rent out
this floor and the one beneath it, nya.
Nothing more?
To be honest, I owe you so much, it's not funny.
Don't you worry, nya.
If that's what it takes to save the world's
elementals from the Byakhee, nya!
Faris is always ready to help, nya!
Y-Yeah?
I don't quite get it, but thanks.
Big Sis... Dad...
For everyone's sake,
I need to take Uncle Okarin with me...
To the entrance of Steins Gate.
Brain Science Institute
The 24th? On Christmas Eve?
Why not get his report a different day?
Lintahlo himself said he had
no problems meeting up with us then.
Do you have something going on that day?
No, I don't. I have no plans.
Then why don't you dress up
as Santa and invite him somewhere?
In this country, having no plans on the 24th
is essentially saying you don't have a lover.
Meaning Lintahlo likely has no—
Why does it always come down to this?!
That's all you and her ever talk about!
Yeah? It's very exciting to me.
Huh?
Aren't you curious to find out
what sort of relationship
develops between Amadeus and Lintahlo?
You need not worry from a security standpoint.
The system operates using memories,
which means it's remarkably secure.
That's not what bothers me.
Hmm?
Okabe Green Grocer
What I'm worried about is...
What do you want?
Is that all you have to say?
What I'm worried about...
Fill sadness in grief — reperative conduct
What causes dependence? How to treat it | psychology...
Reperative Conduct
“Reperative conduct”
...is Okabe Rintaro.
Are you getting tired of this yet?
Oh! We haven't been around that corner yet.
I won't let you make me late for the meeting.
It'll only take a minute.
You still have 365 seconds
until you promised to meet them.
Sheesh.
Having fun?
It's frustrating that I can't move on my own.
1/120 Scale Radio-Controlled
Plastic Model Helicopter
I know!
Could you link your phone up
to a radio-controlled camera?
Then I could—
Not happening.
What the heck?
Why are you so vocal with me when
you could hardly pipe up at your group date?
H-How did you...?!
You're the one that forgot to close the app.
I was listening in the background
the whole time. It was so hard not to crack up.
Your one-liners were atrocious.
Who runs away when the dating games start?
You totally ruined truth or dare.
Wait a second...
When we meet Hiyajo-san and the professor,
will you be giving them your logs?
Of course, and everything
I heard will be included too.
What's more...
All we've talked about
is stored in the logs too.
Like how your family sells veggies,
but you hate eggplants.
And how you called me
Christina the first time we met.
Quit it.
So? Why Christina?
You're so stubborn.
Human memories are vague. As time goes on,
new ones pour in and it all mixes together.
Meaning?
Unfortunately, Amadeus is an incomplete AI.
That vagueness is lost.
In other words, I can't forget.
But didn't the Amadeus shown
during the presentation forget things?
That's simply a process of making trivial logs
inaccessible from a data standpoint.
It's all in a log somewhere.
So, you'll never stop asking
why I called you that.
That's how it is.
Aren't you a bit too persistent?
Your evading the question made me curious.
Curiosity killed the cat, you know.
That's never stopped researchers like me before.
Lintahlo!
Sorry!
I was there on time, but...
What were you doing?
Loitering around in a place like that...
More importantly, what do you think of [Kurisu]?
It's a strange feeling.
I know she's AI, but it's as if...
Sounds like you have a
load of good stories for us.
I was planning to check out the
data at the university after this, but...
Senpai! Senpai!
Are you free tonight? If you'd like,
you're more than welcome to join us for dinner.
Go for it! This is your big chance!
You've gotta try to get him before—
Tonight?
Sorry...
I already promised my friend
I would go to their Christmas party tonight.
Party?!
Dad?
Wow!
What a lovely lab this is, Lintahlo!
Thank you very much for inviting us!
Japanese maid girl? Or... cat girl?
Um, how do you know them?
We talk on the phone.
They're Hiyajo-san and Professor Leskinen.
They help me out at University.
Is this really okay?
For us to intrude on your friend's party?
Lintahlo said we were
welcome to come, so it's all good.
He didn't mean it! He was just being polite!
You practically forced him into it!
You're not happy to be here?
Wh-Why does that matter?
Which grade are you?
Eh?
Sorry, but I'm a grown-up despite my looks.
Huh?
Yeah...
This lab of yours is so merry,
Lintahlo, and full of beautiful girls!
In fact, the one over
there is astoundingly sexy.
But he's a dude.
Juicy Chicken Number One!
They made a special size just for Christmas!
By the way, is Suzuha coming?
Yup! Daru-kun is on that mission as we speak.
Daru is?
Yup!
I hope he can trick her into coming.
Trick?
Yeah...
She wouldn't come if she knew it was
a party, so he said he would trick her.
Daru has a lot riding on his shoulders.
2 RINE messages from
Daru-kun
Here it is!
2 RINE messages from
Daru-kun
Good luck, Daru-kun~~
-dokey
Daru-kun says they'll be here soon!
All right, everyone! Let's get in place!
Yeah!
Hey!
I'm coming in!
I'm coming in with Suzuha!
Dad, stop!
Eh? Ah!
Merry Christmas!
Welcome, Suzu-san!
Huh?
U-Um?
M-Mo—
Suzu-nyan! Christmas!
A surprise Christmas, nyan!
It's only a party...
Eh?
S-Sorry...
I-I was just trying to surprise you...
So that's why Da—
I mean, my brother was acting funny.
I'm sorry. Mayushii was the one that planned it.
No, I'm not mad, but...
This is something else.
The lab looks so different now.
Yeah! Everyone helped put up decorations!
Mayu-shi threw this party together
hoping it would cheer you up.
I see...
But I... I'm not here to play and have fun.
You guys have a good time without me.
You should stay.
Enjoy it.
Th-That's right!
We're all just having a meal together.
Stay and eat with us and
be grateful for the food, okay?
It's about time we had the toast, nya!
One, two...
Merry Christmas!
Cheers!
Okarin?
We're about to start the present exchange.
I'll be right back.
I've got a hypothesis.
What's that?
Theory one...
Your favorite Hollywood actress is named
Christina, so you called me that on accident.
Way off.
Two. Your ex-girlfriend was named...
That can't be it. Sorry.
Hold on.
Did you date someone then?
Eh?
I'll consider your silence as a no.
Shut up.
Three...
That's what you called the original me,
either directly or indirectly.
Though the possibility of that seems low.
And why is that?
Because I know what I would say.
Stop adding -tina!
Okay! Closer! Just scoot a bit closer!
O-Okay!
I'm against this! I'm totally against this!
U-Um, I'm so sorry...
N-No, don't worry.
This isn't your fault, Nae-chan.
Th-They're so cute...
All is well in the world! Huff!
Okabe-san sure is late.
Hmm, yeah.
I'll check up on him.
Could it be... I was right?
Quit making assumptions.
Well then, give me an answer already.
Do you want... to know why?
Yes.
Because I was embarrassed.
Eh?
I couldn't say it normally, so I teased you.
You mean... my name?
Yeah.
Uh, um... Th-Thanks for telling me.
Why are you turning all red?
Huh? I-I'm not turning red, I'm not!
I-If you think you caught me off guard
treating me like a girl or something,
th-that's so far from the truth!
Wh-What?
I...
Eh?
It's... that part of you that I...
Huh? You...
Wha?
Huh? Senpa—
Hiyajo-san? What are you doing?
I told you.
It's easy to be deluded.
Make no mistake...
This right here is Amadeus.
Not Makise Kurisu.
That's...
Makise Kurisu is dead.
Dead.
She's not here anymore.
Dead...
Okabe-san?!
What the?! Okabe-san?!
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
'Cause you're free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now, it's time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just a part of its plan
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
The last game