All right. We're going to the store.
If you remember something
you need, feel free to message us.
Okay.
You're fine with this, Mayuri-chan?
Even if Mayushii stays, I won't be of any help.
That way's the long way to...
You lost your memories?!
Yes...
So this whole time, you can't
remember anything that happened...
You're kidding...
Suzuha, why is it that
you think she's Shiina Kagari?
I told you already! Because of that Upa!
It's something she got from her mom.
It was Kagari's charm...
One that she always cherished.
Where did you get that, Kana-san?
I don't know...
When they found me collapsed and unconscious,
this is the only thing I had with me.
Unconscious?
I was lying near the border of Chiba Prefecture
when a priest passing by
must have stumbled across me.
So how did you end up at Lukako's?
They felt it wasn't right for a girl
to stay long at a practicing temple.
At Big Bro Luka's? To think she was so close!
Um, am I... Is my name actually Shiina Kagari?
Do the two of you know something about me?
I—
Wait. Calm down...
Sorry.
Kana-san, does hearing the name
Shiina Kagari make you remember anything?
I don't know...
But... In a way, it sounds very nostalgic.
Tell me, that person just now...
You mean Mayuri?
Mayuri-san... was her name?
Kagari...
Shiina Kagari...
Shiina Kagari.
In 2036... she was Mayuri's... daughter.
This world is a false reality
It's merely a vision projected into our eyes
The arbiter at the point at infinity
Is overwriting the abnormalities of this universe
If an arrogant God, imperceptible by our eyes
Maintains control over us with the speed of light
Then I—and merely I—
Will be sufficient, as a miraculous and fatal minority
If that moment, that place, was special to you
Then the past isn't merely something that's expanding our distance
All the pain and misery
Of that crucial scene—
Its light will now manifest “0”
So you're saying Kana-sa—I mean...
Kagari-san is somebody
that you know, Suzuha-san?
W-Well, I suppose you could say that.
In that case, don't you know where
Kagari-san lived, or somebody in her family?
Uh, well, actually...
Sh-She moved away when they were just kids.
Suzuha doesn't know anything after that.
I see...
Oh, but at least we found out your real name.
Hey, hey.
Kagari-san's name is Shiina Kagari, right?
Y-Yes...
That means you're just like me!
Because Mayushii is Shiina Mayuri.
Shiina Mayuri-san...
I heard from Luka-kun,
but is it true you have amnesia?
Yes...
So... You don't even remember
anything about who you are?
Yes...
I see...
This... has to be so painful for you.
Because, that means you forgot
about all the people you love, right?
That's... the saddest thing
that can happen to someone, I think.
So, um, I... I don't know how to put it, but...
Mayushii wants to help you out too!
So, let's do our best!
What's the matter?
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
N-No...
For some reason I'm really happy...
to hear that from you.
It's not just Mayushii.
I-If there's anything
I can do to help, I'll do it!
Thank you so much!
Coin
Locker
Looks like we found Shiina Kagari ourselves.
Where at?
Staying at a shrine of a friend of mine.
She was found collapsed at the edge of Chiba.
Why?
No idea.
She's lost all of her memories.
I see.
Any update on the crew
that was searching for her?
Nothing yet.
Sorry. This time of year
is busy enough as it is.
Work is work.
What now? Should I keep at it?
To be honest, it'd help a lot if you did.
All right.
I see...
They found her...
This is Hiyajo.
You're in my contacts.
Thanks for inviting me to the Christmas
party.
And sorry about the professor
No worries.
This is Hiyajo.
You're in my contacts.
Thanks for inviting me to the Christmas
party.
And sorry about the professor
No worries.
Thanks for inviting me to the Christmas
party.
And sorry about the professor
Mayuri said everyone's going
to the shrine for New Year's
and you're welcome to come.
No worries.
Mayuri said everyone's going
to the shrine for New Year's
and you're welcome to come.
Mayuri said everyone's going
to the shrine for New Year's
and you're welcome to come.
Mayuri said everyone's going
to the shrine for New Year's
and you're welcome to come.
We need to talk about Amadeus, but
We need to talk about Amadeus, but|
We need to talk about Amadeus, bu|
We need to talk about Amadeus, b|
We need to talk about Amadeus, |
Maho!
Hey! What's the big idea, Professor?!
Let me guess, it's a message from him?!
Not even close.
Why can't you and Leskinen just drop it already?
Besides, love as a concept
is completely worthless.
Oh? That's where you're wrong.
As a matter of fact, your love life
is my most curious field of study.
Even so, there's no point in treating
me like one of your test subjects.
I'll never allow myself to be
fooled by the delusion of love.
Oh? A shame.
By the way, Professor...
Hmm?
Um, I'm sorry for everything...
You shouldn't be!
Mayushii wants to help out too,
so say if you need something!
Yes, thank you.
Lukako, got a minute?
Try to keep Kagari-san from going outside?
But, that's...
If she has to, make
sure someone goes with her.
As for why... I can't say yet.
If that's what you say, Okabe-san...
Sorry.
We still don't know
who else was searching for Kagari.
And until we do, it's best if
we take all the precautions we can.
In any case, it's great that
we finally found Kagari-tan.
Now you can relax for once.
Yeah, I guess...
Not exactly the relieved face I was expecting...
That girl... Where has she been until now?
Amnesia, huh?
I've been wondering the same thing myself.
But it's not like you can do
anything about it in the first place.
Stuff like that, don't they say
it comes back out of nowhere?
All we can do now is wait.
That might be true, but...
On the other hand,
we could try scaring it out of her...
Like this!
H-He— u-uh—
U-Uh— h-he u-uh u-uh...
You can't do something like that.
I hear... a voice...
Kagari!
Suzuha...
Eclipse
of
Orbital Ordering
Hey, Okarin...
New Year greetings
Aren't we supposed to be going
to the shrine for New Year’s?
Y-Yeah...
Th-Then why... are we in this weird situation?
Hey!
If you've got something to say,
then speak up nice and loud.
N-No, it's nothing!
Oh?
W-We were hoping to enter the lab, but...
Nope!
Wh-Why not?! This is tyranny!
We promised to meet the others here
to go to the shrine together for New Year’s…
Sorry to keep you!
Huh?
Nae!
You're so adorable!
Of course you are, you're my daughter!
Y-You're hurting me, Dad.
Good thing she looks nothing like—
Dad, I can't wait! I'm so excited
to see Big Sis Mayuri as a shrine priestess!
Oh, yeah?
You listen to the girls and behave, all right?
'Kay!
You're not coming along?
Got some business to take care of.
If not for that, I wouldn't be leaving
my cutie daughter in your care, would I?
And let me be clear,
if anything happens to Nae...
Sir! Yes, sir!
See you later, Dad!
Come on! Let's get moving!
Right.
Oh, before that...
We're forgetting something important.
Happy...
New Year!
Can't wait to see Mayushii's
shrine priestess cosplay!
Silly! It's not cosplay today,
it's her uniform!
Oh, right!
Isn't Suzuha-san working there too?
That should be fun.
Having a shrine priestess sister is one thing...
But if you've gone that far, might as
well make her a nurse while you're at it
and push her moe score through the roof.
The perverseness is strong with Hashida-san.
Hey... Sorry about this.
I know it was Mayuri's idea, but she
got recruited to work as a shrine priestess.
That doesn't bother me.
I wanted to talk to you anyways.
By the way, aren't you attending
an American university, Hiyajo-san?
Huh? Yeah...
Your research sounds really cool!
What was it again? Aye-ayes?
The lemur?
It's AI, Fubuki-chan.
Yeah, yeah! That!
AI, as in you research
artificial intelligence, right?
I'm really interested in that, actually!
Okarin!
You okay over there?
It's nothing... Let's go.
Ah!
Okarin! Over here, nya!
Happy New Year!
Happy New nyaa!
Ooh! It's a shrine priestess paradise!
Is this heaven?
Suzuha-san, you're lovely!
Th-Thank you.
It looks great on you, right?
Suzuha...
Try saying... Bend over,
Big Brother, it's time for your shot.
Quit saying crap like that!
No wonder you're not progressing with Mom!
My bad!
You two sure get along well.
W-Well yeah, because she's my daugh—
W-Would you like to offer saké?
Or how about a fortune slip?
I can't... believe you.
Um, did I do something?
Luka-kun is as beautiful as ever.
Th-That's not—
I refuse to believe it.
How is that a boy?
It's the truth.
Would you like to see proof?
Wha?! How so?
Eh?
Eh?!
So... Is it good?
Yeah, you look great in it.
Really? Thank goodness!
Mayuri-san didn't want to believe us
when we told her that a hundred times.
She kept worrying if you'd like it.
Y-You weren't supposed to say that.
Sorry.
Sheesh! But you were worried
about the same thing too.
Eh? Yeah, because for someone like me...
Don't say that! You look gorgeous!
Right, Okarin?
Yeah...
Looks pretty good.
Lucky you, nya!
Better
fortune
Ooh, I like it!
I was shocked.
She's exactly like Kurisu.
You think?
Yeah, they look almost identical.
I... can't say I agree.
I think you know what I'm trying to say.
About Amadeus, right?
Things can't stay as they are,
or you'll never have closure.
You need to make a decision
before the year gets too far.
Are you kidding me?
Aww...
Guess they didn't make it in time.
Lintahlo!
Professor?!
Happy New Year, Lintahlo!
I told them to come since
it's a special occasion.
Where are shrine maidens?!
Uh, famous shamans, where?!
Shamans?
Oh, you mean the shrine priestesses.
They're all done for today.
We're all about to leave
since they're done cleaning.
Holy Cow! That's why I said
we should have come earlier!
You're the one that couldn't stop shopping.
Come on. Let's go visit the shrine.
No! You've got to wash your hands here first!
And don't walk in the middle of the path!
Okarin!
Luka-kun's mom gave us
a ton of New Year's food!
Sorry to keep you.
Rintaro! We'll see you later!
Eh? You're leaving already?
He says there's no point
in staying without shrine priestesses.
Catch you later! Bye!
Sorry! Took longer than expected.
It sure did.
Anyways, we should get going ourselves.
Oh, sorry. I'll have to call it a day.
Huh? You're not coming to the lab?
There's a shortage of staff at work. Sorry...
I see... That's too bad.
I'll just have to come back
and play another day!
Should we head back?
Yup!
Is everyone ready for a New Year's party?!
Yeah!
Let's hear it one more time!
Happy New Year, everyone!
Happy New Year!
Cheers!
Mm-mmm! This zoni soup hits the spot!
It's from MayQueen's New Year's menu, nya!
In other words, I'm tasting a bit of Faris-tan?
Hashida-san, you're such a pervert.
These beans are delicious.
They seem packed with nutrition.
Help yourself, Nae-chan!
These kinton are yummy too!
Th-There's no way I could eat all that...
It you don't eat up, you'll never get big!
Down the hatch!
Huh? Are we already out of tea, nya?
Ah, we'll run to the store and buy some.
Huh?
Ah, hello!
It's the landlord guy!
Done with your shrine visit?
Where the others at?
We're throwing a little party.
Us two are just hitting the store.
Yeah? In that case,
I'll stop by and pick up Nae later.
Can you tell Okabe to let me
know when your party is over?
Sure thing.
That's right, nya!
How about this one?
Hmm?
It's true, nya! I like, nya!
Ah, Senpai? Where in the world are...
Huh? Is that where I think it is?
Hey, what's that?
A friend of Maho-nyan's, nya?
Ah, um... I'm...
A person from overseas, nya?
I'm not a person, I'm artificial intelligence.
That is, an AI created by Maho-senpai.
Eh?
AI?
Not a lemur!
Seriously? Is that really AI?
I see...
You must all be members of Okabe-san's lab.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Amadeus, an artificial intelligence
based off the memories of Makise Kurisu.
Makise Kurisu-san?
I take it all of you were
acquaintances of the original me?
Uh, actually it's more like...
I know about you from your article in Science Magazine.
Oh, I see. Though, if you read that magazine,
you must be interested in science.
Uh, well... I sort of specialize
in networks and systems.
Yeah?
Hey, hey, Miss AI? Are you part of
a game or something? Love & Death?
I'm not a game.
I'm right here, listening to the
conversation and talking back to you.
I'm sorry.
After saying all those things to you,
bringing her out here...
I think of what I want
to say and talk to you.
I apologize.
No, it might be better this way.
It hurts, but I have to keep moving forward.
Even if Kagari resembles Kurisu in
a way, she's not Kurisu herself.
Amadeus too. Even if it's based off
of her, it exists as a separate entity.
I can't let her drag me down...
is what you wanted to say to me, right?
That's right.
She protected it all...
this world with Mayuri and everyone.
And I have to keep protecting it...
without ever looking back.
Suzuha... She may not be
convinced at this point, but...
Right now, we know
absolutely nothing about Kagari.
But, someday...
By the way, isn't Okabe-san—
Huh?
What's wrong?
It cut off all of a sudden.
Lemme see.
Hmm? My phone seems
to be working just fine...
I wonder what's up?
I can't connect to the Amadeus server...
Huh?
My watch isn't working...
That's strange...
I just wound it not long ago...
Think the server is updating or something?
If it is, I never heard about it.
Okabe Rintaro!
Wh-What's going on?
A surprise?
Don't move!
What the...
Okarin!
What the hell...
...is this?!
Come to me, embrace my tears
Let me guide you down into my soul
And let us pray for the world to realize
There is peace, the truth within us
Emptiness erodes your heart
'Cause you're free from pain and sorrow
The future is just too bright to show you ways
Wake up now, it's time to lead new souls
Orbit of photon and universe
I am just a part of its plan
Me ni wa mienai yuganda sora
The eye cannot see the distortion of the sky
Hito wa doko he to aruite yuku no?
Where does man think they are walking towards?
The last game