Basically, no matter how much you time leap,
the time machine keeps getting destroyed?
Yeah.
Can't you rush to Radikan
and stop Mayu-shi before she hops in?
Of course... And that even might
save Mayushii and Suzuha.
However, there's a strong chance
that makes things unpredictable.
What do you mean?
I don't know if the time machine's
destruction is a convergence or not.
Though, there's no mistaking it's
a major element for starting WWIII.
So, it's highly likely.
Where are you going?
To get some fresh air and think.
Okarin.
You time leaped over and over
from the future to get here, right?
Yeah.
In that case, what's the future you like?
How you are right now?
Not like “Epic chuunibyou, bro?”
Chuunibyou?
I always thought he'd come back someday...
I decided... to never give up, yet...
When it comes down to it...
Get a hold of yourself...
...Okabe Rintaro.
[Kurisu]?
Oh yeah... The Professor hasn't taken her yet.
Didn't you see the future?
Plus... didn't you come back to change it?
If you're a scientist,
as long as the chance isn't 0...
...giving up is not an option.
But you'll have my full support.
What's so funny?
Nothing. It's just, no matter
the time I find myself in,
all of you lab mems,
you really never change at all.
Heh...
Heh?
You fool! This was all a mere act
to throw the Organization off my trail!
Huh?
Assistant one... and two!
Assistant?
We've got a meeting to start.
You best follow me.
What in the world was that?
Who knows?
Hurry up, you experiment-loving kids!
Wha...?
In other words, there are
two large factors that stir up WWIII.
America
Stratfo
America and Russia, plus...
America
Stratfo
Russia
...the time machine.
Time machine
You said that earlier.
The organizations responsible are...
America
Stratfo
Leskinen
Time machine
...Stratfo with Leskinen...
Leskinen
Stratfo
Time machine
...and another American faction, DURPA.
America
Stratfo
Leskinen
Time machine
Stratfo
Leskinen
Time machine
DURPA
Stratfo
Leskinen
Time machine
DURPA
There's also Russian intelligence,
so that makes three organizations.
Isn't this a bit far-fetched?
It's like the Organization
you used to rant about.
Precisely.
I happen to be a genius.
Long have I known which countries
plunge our world into chaos.
And they've begun to move.
Senpai...
What?
Did Okabe-san hit his head on something?
Or has he been traumatized by—
Silence, Christina!
Don't add -tina!
Aren't you embarrassed to talk like that?
You don't think I am?
How can this not be embarrassing?
I think it's great.
Eh?
The Okarin that I know is
so obnoxious and annoying, it's unreal.
He argues no matter what you say,
and he's chuunibyou all the way to the bone.
But, that's exactly why his absurd logic
can overcome the impossible.
Daru...
Now explain why you stepped
outside looking all gloomy
but came back with
Maho-tan and a new attitude?
What happened? What'd you two do, Okarin?!
—Eh? Huh? Uh... Eh?
—A smooch? A smoochy?!
Even though you have Mayu-shi?! I'm jealous!
—Nothing happened between us!
—You smooched?! She smooched you?!
—Besides, Daru... You're forgetting
the most important thing.
—You smooched?! She smooched you?!
—Besides, Daru... You're forgetting
the most important thing.
—Huh? Huh?!
Eh?
I'm not Okabe Rintaro...
My name is... whoosh!
Hou... ou... in!
Kyouma!
Behold! This is the true form
of a mad scientist!
Peel your eyes and
burn my glory into your mind!
Is he okay?
It's me.
The final stage of the plan is closing in.
Once it begins, all the intel in
the world doesn't stand a chance.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I know.
Who's he talking to?
Enough already. Hurry up and get on with it.
You should have said so from the start.
Loli Girl.
Like I was saying...
These three organizations
are after the time machine.
Stratfo
Leskinen
All the previous failures
Stratfo
Leskinen
DURPA
were caused by these
three organizations interfering.
DURPA
Time Machine
Foreign Intel
However, that's not to
say they can't be dealt with.
So the time machine's destruction
isn't necessarily a convergence?
Basically, we let them board the time machine,
but it's that exact moment
they leave for the past
that we can't allow interference.
Still, we've foiled Stratfo and Leskinen.
Stratfo
Leskinen
Likewise, we've managed to put
a halt on DURPA and their soldiers.
Stratfo
Leskinen
DURPA
In other words...
Only Russia's left.
Mmm.
Do you have some sort of plan then?
Nope.
What?!
You've been talking all this time
and haven't thought of anything?
Yeah, yeah. LOL.
What's that?
Shaddap!
Leskinen and DURPA were thwarted by
my exceptional wits and masterful plan!
What have you done? Can't you come
up with a single plan of your own?
Didn't know anything till just now.
Ah...
So be it...
In times like this, you've got
to look into why things happen.
Find out what they're trying to do
and establish a chain of causality.
Foreign Intel
Time machine
In this case, Russia is...
Whoa!
Russ... ia... is...
It's here! The promised pose
of Maho-tan we all hoped for!
Says who?!
It must be done.
—Here.
—Eh?
Go ahead. Draw.
First of all, how do the American
and Russian organizations
know that we have a time machine here?
For the Americans, it's because of Leskinen.
The future Leskinen used Kagari
to tell the current Leskinen
about the time machine.
But, Kagari-san would have
met the professor years ago.
Why didn't he make his move then?
Nothing could be changed.
Eh?
It's like a time paradox.
If his actions defied history,
worldline convergence
would correct anything he does.
Worldline...
However, Leskinen's plan
was to use that to his advantage.
I see...
Essentially, in the future, on July 7th, 2011,
the conflict over the
time machine boiled over.
On July 7th, the time machine was destroyed.
Which means, he thought
he could snatch it on that exact day.
Where did DURPA get their info from?
It's the same country, so...
It's just Russia to think about...
Did they steal info from the Americans?
If the professor heard
about WWIII from his future self,
I'm sure that info would've been guarded.
They wouldn't want Russia
to know more than anyone.
Daru, you've gotta look something up.
All right, but what?
I want you to search for Dr. Nakabachi.
Talk about a close call!
If this hadn't set off the metal detectors,
—my paper would've burned up!
—I knew it. Dr. Nakabachi defected to Russia.
Daddy...
Daddy?
Let's save that for later.
Dr. Nakabachi took the time machine theory
and defected to Russia with it.
But the thing is, Russia
hasn't developed anything yet.
What do you mean?
Because if they completed one,
there wouldn't be conflict.
Half a year ago when we were attacked,
Kurisu's PC was destroyed by the Russians.
They had made a connection
between Nakabachi's theory and Kurisu
and didn't want another faction to get it.
Is there anything else
left of hers that we know of?
Her notes or her work...
Her knowledge...
I guess that's how it is, huh?
Inside of me are all Makise Kurisu's memories.
I have her thought patterns as well.
If someone was making a time machine,
they'd want me for sure.
That time...
...when Amadeus was taken over,
the worldline changed.
What's up?
If we went back before Russia's involved,
could we somehow protect Amadeus?
Before they're involved, meaning when?
I don't know for sure.
It has to be as early as possible.
When did you first take Kurisu's memory data?
It was before Kurisu left for Japan, so...
Around spring of last year, I think.
If I time leap back to then—
C-Can you even?
Last spring, it wasn't...
For starters, your PhoneWave
wasn't even finished until last summer.
No matter what, you can't go back that far.
In that case, D-Mail! Daru!
You sure about that?
You were always against the idea...
True... SERN will catch on if we use that.
Which leads to...
We'll just have to look for another method.
Um, sorry for not mentioning it earlier,
but I've got something to say...
D-RINE?
Yeah.
Using the same principles as D-Mail,
I made it sendable over RINE.
Can it be sent without being caught by SERN?!
Yeah...
Thing is, RINE was still in beta last spring
and I was the only one with it installed.
I think last New Year's might be our limit.
So, we can't send it
to anyone but Hashida-san.
Will it work?
It's possible.
You'll get a message from
your future self saying to safeguard
Makise Kurisu's memory data in VCU.
And if it's you, you'll follow it.
If you see it though, you'll lose your shit.
Wait.
That won't be enough
to stop the info from leaking.
You're up against a huge nation.
They'll come after it
for as long as there's access.
They'll probably copy and distribute it too.
That's a good point...
Then what do we do?
You have to wipe it out.
You have to access Kurisu's memory
data right after the original backup
and self-destruct the system,
so it can't be recovered.
[Kurisu]?!
That's the only way, Senpai.
If it's all wiped out at spring last year,
there's no way to rebuild Amadeus.
But, that means you'll...
In other words...
Make it so Amadeus... never happened?
Rinascimento
of
Entwurf
What's going on?
No use in asking me...
At this rate, the time machine
will get destroyed again tomorrow.
That's seeming pretty likely.
Then, isn't it obvious what has to be done?
It is, but...
I think I understand his side.
And... I'm sure you do too.
I think... Okabe-san...
What's up?
Just passing along a message.
Amadeus wants to talk to you.
Inbox
From: Hiyajo-san
To: Okabe Rintaro
Subject: (No subject)
H-Hello...
Yeah.
It feels like ages since I've been outside.
Could you show me the view?
Not much of a view to speak of, but...
Wow... To think there's a place like this!
First time out at night?
You have to ask?
If only I had legs,
I could walk around all I want.
But I'm a program.
If you're actually hesitant to erase me,
that speaks volumes
about Amadeus as a program.
To influence somebody's heart,
that means I must be AI comparable to a human.
You'll disappear...
I knew you were hung up on that.
Since we're outside anyways,
could you show me around some more?
Everything's so different than daytime.
Well, yeah.
Are other cities like this?
No, it depends on the place.
Shinjuku and Shibuya
are bustling even at night.
But around Ginza,
I bet it's even quieter than here.
Really? You think?
Which way now?
Let's see... Oh!
Take me up there!
All right.
Remember walking around like this before?
Yeah.
By the way, what happened
to your funny voice?
Mwahahaha and all that.
You like it when I talk that way, Assistant?
Please, don't. I'll want to make fun of you.
What a neat place...
You like it?
Very.
It's all so disorderly here,
with no rules or anything.
The world that I exist in...
...everything has a reason and purpose.
Things which have no purpose are erased.
Waste is trimmed
so things can be made more efficient.
But the world I see before me now,
you could say it's chaotic.
Useless things are kept around,
and actions utterly wasteful
happen on a daily basis.
You can know the right choice
to make, and yet choose wrong.
But that brings forth chance,
ensuring meaning for the irrelevant.
It's all jumbled together,
allowing miraculous things to occur.
Encounters ensue...
A program like me can't
even begin to touch such a world.
[Kurisu]...
Okabe Rintaro.
I can understand if you're sentimental
and don't want to erase me.
It makes me happy, honestly.
In that case—
But, you spoke of the Steins Gate worldline.
The life of Shiina Mayuri...
Plus, the life of the original me...
A worldline where both lives
can be saved is right in front of you.
I've said it many times,
but I'm no more than a program.
Even if you—
I understand that!
Then why?
I...
Back then, I killed the original you.
Eh?
In that situation, I could only
save either Mayuri or Kurisu.
I chose Mayuri, and then...
...I gave up trying to save you.
And I agreed with it?
Yeah.
You told me over and over
that decision wasn't wrong.
That choosing Mayuri was the right choice.
I can imagine.
My pride won't allow
a sacrifice to be made for me.
You know what you have to do, don't you?
Save Shiina-san and Suzuha-san,
and don't allow the war to start by—
But then you...!
But...
It'll be like you never existed.
You won't just be gone.
No one will... even remember you existed...
But, you'll remember me, won't you?
And what if I fail?
What if I can't find it?
Isn't that how you acted before now?
But you regretted that and decided
to time leap 3000 times to come fix it all.
Since the original me died,
I've often asked myself...
What exactly is my existence?
For what purpose do I exist?
Though now, there's not much joy
in existing as the spark that starts WWIII.
Is that my only reason for being?
But, if it's within my power
to save the original Kurisu...
If it's to save this beautiful world...
If that can be the reason I exist...
Don't you think that's more logical...
and even romantic?
[Kurisu]...
Show me the sky.
It's so bright, don't you think?
Yeah.
All of you live in a world more
beautiful than you even know.
As time flows, chaos and chance
make miracles, and certainties are shaped.
In this world...
Right?
I'm done setting up.
Ready, Senpai?
You sure?
Yes.
Break into the servers of Viktor
Chondria University's Brain Science
Institute and destroy all the data
concerning the Amadeus AI.
Open the door with the attached key
below.
Okay. All that's left is to send
Maho-tan's attachment to the past me.
Amadeus... Ready input for control code.
Der alte... würfelt nicht.
Control code received.
System transitioning to emergency mode.
Run command from Hiyajo Maho,
top-level administrator.
Transfer selected patch
program to designated file.
Modify to commence
processing upon system reset.
Command confirmed.
Executing command from Hiyajo Maho,
top-level administrator.
Hiyajo-san...
Senpai!
Do your best and don't give up!
The possibilities are endless!
I know you better than anyone, Senpai.
That's why I can say this with confidence...
You'll surpass my research
by leaps and bounds
and accomplish things
I could never dream of!
And someday, we'll reach
the world we should be in!
I know we can! We'll get there!
Amadeus!
Someday, I swear! On that
promised day where time intersects...!
Daijina kioku wa
Important memories
Without a doubt, we will reach that place!
Betsu no rironshiki de uchikesareru
Contradict a different theoretical formula
And we will meet again!
Jishou no chihei mo
And thus, the event horizon, and everything thereafter
Senpai!
Take care of Hououin Kyouma for me!
Banbutsu no sore sae kakikaeta
Will be overwritten
[Kurisu]!
Hako ni tojikometa ai no danpen wa
The fragments of love enclosed within the box
Break into the servers of Viktor
Chondria University's Brain Science
Institute and destroy all the data
concerning the Amadeus AI.
Open the door with the attached key
below.
Go!
Chikaku tousugiru jigen no saihate
Are within reach, but too distant in the higher dimension
Kaihen no purosesu wa totemo mujaki ni
The process of alteration is all too simple:
Kami sae mo azumuku fikkushon
Fabricate fiction to deceive even God
Yakusoku no ano basho he
Bringing us closer to that promised place...
Mousugu tokei no kane ga hibiki
Soon, the bells of the clock will chime
Zero no geeto hiraku yo
And the gate to Zero will open
Mabushii hikari ni
Enveloping us in a most radiant light
Tsutsumare yuku
Kiseki wo unmei ni kakikaete
With miracles we will overwrite fate
Waraigoe ga afureru
Cackling at the notion of destiny
Ano jikan ano basho de
And in that hour, in that place,
Kimi no “toki” ga mouichido hajimaru
Your “time” will begin once more