Okarin!
Huh?
Okabe.
Okarin.
Okabe-san.
Kyouma!
Okabe-kun.
Uncle Okarin.
Good, everyone’s here.
As of now, the 65536th
round table meeting will...
Yeah... Everyone’s here.
And yet, it’s so lifeless... dark... and cold.
As if... all the bones in
my body were made out of metal.
Okabe.
Why... are you here?
It’s not just me.
Mayuri and Hashida are here too.
Eh?
As of now...
...the 65536th round
table meeting will commence!
Where am I?
My body’s... so heavy.
This is...
What happened... to me?
Where is this?
Is this... really me?
Barrel Titor here.
Where the hell am I?
Wasn’t I doing a time leap...?
What the hell?
This...
This is...
It can’t be...
Akiba?
Oh yeah, the lab...
What happened to the others?
You there! What are you doing here?!
Answer me! This area is off-limits to civilians!
Put your hands over your head
and state your name and ID.
What’s your name and ID?!
You little...
S-Suzuha!
Who are you?
How do you know my name?
Wait! What do you mean?!
Have you forgotten me?!
What are you saying?!
It’s Okabe!
Okabe Rintaro!
Okabe...
...Rintaro?
That can’t be!
Mansei Bridge
Suehirocho
Moe moe for you.
Bakkyun-kyun.
This way.
Finally opened your eyes, eh?
Okarin.
Can’t you tell?
I’ll try talking like I used to.
Long time no see, Okarin.
Daru... is that you?
Come on, man. How could you
possibly forget a stud like me, noob?
Right, Suzuha?
Maybe if you slimmed down a bit.
Even so, I’m a lot slimmer than I used to be.
All that matters is the present.
Daru... tell me.
What year is it now?
2036.
The world has fallen into pure chaos.
2036...
Hard to believe?
No... Believing is all I can do.
It’s been 25 years since then.
We’re old geezers now.
It doesn’t make sense...
In 2025, I’m supposed to...
That’s what I wanna know.
Why is Uncle Okarin alive and well?
You told me he’s been dead for a while now.
I never lied to you.
Okarin was dead.
Huh?
How far back do you remember, Okarin?
I...
I was using the time leap machine
to go into the past...
To save Mayuri...
But, when I came to...
That day, the time leap machine didn’t work.
Eh?
We don’t even know the exact reason.
But the time leap machine failed us.
And so, in order to get back to that time,
we exceeded the 48-hour limit.
All while the world plunged into chaos
rivaling for the time machine theory.
So you’re saying, Mayuri...
Mayuri...
A few years after Mayu-shi disappeared...
We decided to build the
time machine all on our own.
That was the start of Valkyrie.
Valkyrie?
But in doing so, that’s what began
our war with the world.
The world?
Countries all over the world were
desperate for the time machine theory.
And it was believed those with Makise Kurisu’s
theory were closest to completing it.
That is, Okabe Rintaro
and this organization, Valkyrie.
Dad and the others were hunted down
from one side of the world to the other.
And then, that day in 2025...
Daru, I’ve got bad news.
Wh-What happened?
I’ve been trapped by Stratfo.
For real? Shoot! Get over here!
No way.
I’m not putting the lab members in danger.
Hey, Daru...
Back then...
Thanks for encouraging me
when I was about to break.
Daru, I’m counting on you
to complete the time machine.
Okarin?
The rest is up to you.
Wai... Okarin!
After that, you fell into the hands of
Stratfo and were tortured relentlessly.
By the time Dad came to save you,
they said you were already...
Yes, by the time we found him...
...the endless torture and experiments
had already done too much damage.
His mind was as good as dead.
So you’re saying...
Yeah.
You could say his heart had died inside.
Even if his body healed,
his will to live was gone.
But his body still functioned.
Then, why did you say he was dead?
That was our only choice.
Those guys would’ve kept fighting over Okarin,
even in the shape he was in.
I still don’t get why
you never told me the truth.
So I was lying there for 11 whole years?
Yeah.
Under the care of a
select few who knew the truth.
Hold on... Then why did Uncle Okarin
wake up after all this time?
The time leap machine?
Correct.
What do you mean?
Using the time leap machine, they overwrote
my brain with memory data from 2011.
I see...
It just so happened that recently,
we managed to salvage it from an old PC.
Of course, it working was a big gamble.
I can’t believe this.
Deceiving the world is one thing,
but how could you lie to me?
Deceive the world?
I’m sure you need time for your mind
to catch up, so take it easy for now.
I’ll contact the others
and let them know you woke up.
Contact?
Yeah.
You’ve been out for 11 years.
The lab members have been
waiting long for this day.
Rinascimento
of the
Unwavering
Promise
No issues here.
Fine here.
This is the place, right?
Should be, nya.
We’ll pick up the stuff like usual.
This is Barrel Titor. Report in.
Cheshire Cat here. What’s up, nya?
Is Warrior with you?
Yeah, nya.
I need the both of you to listen up.
Mmm?
Okarin has woken.
Eh?!
Are you serious?
That was...
Luka-shi and Faris-tan.
They’re the ones who cared
for you this whole time.
So that’s how it was...
Wait a sec.
Why is Big Sis Rumi out there fetching rations?
There was no plan like that for today.
Eh?
Meow? Are you sure about that?
We got a message late last night
saying to be here today...
It’s a trap.
Big Bro Luka! Big Sis—
Dad!
Okey-dokey!
Hold on! I’m coming too!
But, with the shape that you’re in...
Please!
Thanks.
Not good, nya! We’ll be wiped out, nya!
I’ll hold them off.
Everyone go with Faris-san
and bring back reinforcements.
Eh?
That’s insane, nya!
There’s no way, Luka-nyan!
I’ll be fine.
There’s no way I’ll die before
seeing Okabe-san again.
Luka-nyan...
Let’s go!
But...
Hang in there, Luka-nyan!
Suzuha! 12 o’clock!
Faris-san!
Suzu-nyan! Daru-nyan!
Faris!
Kyou... ma.
Kyouma...
Kyouma!
Kyouma! Kyouma! You’re awake!
Sorry to worry you.
Big Bro Luka?
That’s right! Luka-nyan’s in trouble!
He stayed back to let us escape.
Eh?!
I can’t hear any combat.
This way! Found him!
Big Bro Luka!
Luka-nyan!
Lukako...
Luka... ko?
Lukako!
Kyouma-san?
It’s me! Lukako!
That name you call me...
It’s really you, Kyouma-san...
Lukako!
Thank goodness.
Now that you’re back, Kyouma-san...
...I can rest... assured now.
What are you...?
Hey, Kyouma-san.
I... did it.
You taught me, Kyouma-san...
The Seishin Zanma sword-fighting style...
I protected them... with it.
Do you think... I’m finally... a lab member now?
I... with this... maybe I’m worthy enough...
...of being everyone’s... comrade now.
You idiot...
You were, from the very start... always!
You were always... our comrade!
Lab Mem 006!
I see... Heh...
I’m so glad...
With this...
I can face Mayuri-chan... and be proud...
Lukako!
That’s a relief.
Luka-shi wanted to see you more than anything.
He was waiting for the day you woke up.
In the end... his wish came true.
It’s been a while, Okabe-san.
Hiyajo-san...
Sorry it’s not very strong.
We’re always low on everything.
Right.
I have to say, seeing you
and Faris surprised me.
You mean how I look like
a kid no matter how old I am?
Well, when you get to my age,
it might be a compliment.
Does it seem like we’re all so cold?
Eh?
Urushibara-san just died, and yet
everyone’s so calm about it... don’t you think?
No...
That day...
From July 7th, 2011 till now,
so many people have died.
Family... relatives... friends...
Adults and children...
We can’t just sit and grieve all day.
That’s what our reality has become.
I thought I knew...
Suzuha told me time and time again.
That down the worldline I chose,
this kind of future was waiting.
I thought I understood.
But...
I was only telling myself I understood!
I was only telling myself!
Just running away from the truth!
Even after I watched Kurisu die,
I lose Mayuri and Suzuha too!
And Kagari!
And Yuki-san!
And Lukako!
In the end, I didn’t understand a damn thing!
Eleven years ago...
Eleven years ago,
you always said the same thing.
Daru?
That you didn’t understand a damn thing.
But you also said this:
Nothing is meaningless,
even if it seems that way.
There’re countless failed futures.
Pasts we can never recover.
But even so...
Beyond all those, there must be
a path which leads to Steins Gate.
Steins...
...Gate...
Countless... failed futures...
Past...
Future...
The world...
Hiyajo-san. Daru.
Right now, my memories are from 2011.
Because using the time leap machine...
...you successfully rewrote
my memories from now, in 2036?
Is that how it is?
Yeah.
When it comes down to it, that’s basically it.
In other words...
The time leap machine still exists?
Get it ready.
Ready the time leap machine.
Okarin?!
You’re...
One more time...
...I’m going back to find Steins Gate!